{
  "name": "JPDB 30K",
  "cards": [
    {
      "question": "有人",
      "answer": "ゆうじん",
      "meaning": "manned, occupied, piloted"
    },
    {
      "question": "血煙",
      "answer": "ちけむり",
      "meaning": "spurt or spray of blood"
    },
    {
      "question": "化膿",
      "answer": "かのう",
      "meaning": "suppuration, festering, coming to head"
    },
    {
      "question": "犀",
      "answer": "さい",
      "meaning": "rhinoceros"
    },
    {
      "question": "太后",
      "answer": "たいこう",
      "meaning": "empress dowager, queen mother"
    },
    {
      "question": "壕",
      "answer": "ほり,ごう",
      "meaning": "moat, fosse, canal, ditch, trench, underground air-raid shelter, dugout"
    },
    {
      "question": "悪性",
      "answer": "あくしょう,あくせい",
      "meaning": "evil nature, licentiousness, lewdness, malignant (cancer), virulent, pernicious (anemia, anaemia)"
    },
    {
      "question": "子細",
      "answer": "しさい",
      "meaning": "reasons, circumstances, significance, particulars, hindrance, obstruction, interference"
    },
    {
      "question": "復権",
      "answer": "ふっけん,ふくけん",
      "meaning": "rehabilitation, reinstatement, restoration of rights"
    },
    {
      "question": "商売道具",
      "answer": "しょうばいどうぐ",
      "meaning": "stock-in-trade, tools of one's trade"
    },
    {
      "question": "摑まる",
      "answer": "つかまる",
      "meaning": "to be caught, to be arrested, to hold on to, to grasp, to find (e.g. proof), to get (e.g. a taxi), t"
    },
    {
      "question": "安全保障",
      "answer": "あんぜんほしょう",
      "meaning": "security guarantee (e.g. military security, network security, etc.)"
    },
    {
      "question": "不敗",
      "answer": "ふはい",
      "meaning": "invincibility"
    },
    {
      "question": "自転",
      "answer": "じてん",
      "meaning": "rotation (usu. on an axis), turning, spin"
    },
    {
      "question": "線香花火",
      "answer": "せんこうはなび",
      "meaning": "toy fireworks, sparklers"
    },
    {
      "question": "常道",
      "answer": "じょうどう",
      "meaning": "normal practice, proper practice"
    },
    {
      "question": "通算",
      "answer": "つうさん",
      "meaning": "total, sum, aggregate"
    },
    {
      "question": "気色",
      "answer": "きしょく,けしき",
      "meaning": "mood, humor, humour, looks, countenance, sign, indication"
    },
    {
      "question": "資金繰り",
      "answer": "しきんぐり",
      "meaning": "fundraising, financing, cash flow"
    },
    {
      "question": "転身",
      "answer": "てんしん",
      "meaning": "changing (job, career, lifestyle, social position, beliefs, etc.)"
    },
    {
      "question": "異な",
      "answer": "いな,けな",
      "meaning": "strange, odd, unusual, exceptional, praiseworthy, laudable"
    },
    {
      "question": "隷",
      "answer": "しもべ,れい",
      "meaning": "servant, manservant, menial, clerical script (ancient, highly angular style of kanji)"
    },
    {
      "question": "歌い手",
      "answer": "うたいて",
      "meaning": "singer"
    },
    {
      "question": "蒸留",
      "answer": "じょうりゅう",
      "meaning": "distillation"
    },
    {
      "question": "電卓",
      "answer": "でんたく",
      "meaning": "calculator (electronic), pocket calculator"
    },
    {
      "question": "常勝",
      "answer": "じょうしょう",
      "meaning": "invincible, ever-victorious, unconquerable, unbeaten"
    },
    {
      "question": "自分探し",
      "answer": "じぶんさがし",
      "meaning": "finding oneself, self-discovery, journey of self-discovery, search for self"
    },
    {
      "question": "常用",
      "answer": "じょうよう",
      "meaning": "habitual use, daily use"
    },
    {
      "question": "未踏",
      "answer": "みとう",
      "meaning": "untrodden, unexplored"
    },
    {
      "question": "憂える",
      "answer": "うれえる",
      "meaning": "to worry about, to be anxious about, to be concerned about, to lament, to grieve, to feel sorrow for"
    },
    {
      "question": "生き写し",
      "answer": "いきうつし",
      "meaning": "lifelike, exact resemblance"
    },
    {
      "question": "定型",
      "answer": "ていけい",
      "meaning": "fixed form, regular shape, standard-size mail"
    },
    {
      "question": "当社",
      "answer": "とうしゃ",
      "meaning": "(this) shrine, (this) company, (this) firm"
    },
    {
      "question": "難き",
      "answer": "かたき",
      "meaning": "difficulty, trouble"
    },
    {
      "question": "目途",
      "answer": "めど,もくと",
      "meaning": "aim, goal, prospect, outlook"
    },
    {
      "question": "連れ子",
      "answer": "つれこ",
      "meaning": "child from previous marriage, child of a former spouse, stepchild"
    },
    {
      "question": "遺棄",
      "answer": "いき",
      "meaning": "abandonment, desertion"
    },
    {
      "question": "誘き出す",
      "answer": "おびきだす",
      "meaning": "to lure out of, to decoy out of, to drive to (tears, sleep, etc.), to evoke (sympathy, etc.), to abd"
    },
    {
      "question": "乗り回す",
      "answer": "のりまわす",
      "meaning": "to drive (a car) around, to ride (a bicycle) around"
    },
    {
      "question": "採算",
      "answer": "さいさん",
      "meaning": "profit"
    },
    {
      "question": "いの一番",
      "answer": "いのいちばん",
      "meaning": "first of all, first thing"
    },
    {
      "question": "牢番",
      "answer": "ろうばん",
      "meaning": "prison guard, jailer, gaoler"
    },
    {
      "question": "破邪",
      "answer": "はじゃ",
      "meaning": "(sense of) crushing evil"
    },
    {
      "question": "砂金",
      "answer": "さきん,しゃきん",
      "meaning": "gold dust"
    },
    {
      "question": "下請け",
      "answer": "したうけ",
      "meaning": "subcontract, subcontractor (person or company)"
    },
    {
      "question": "奨励",
      "answer": "しょうれい",
      "meaning": "encouragement, promotion, inducement, incitement, stimulation"
    },
    {
      "question": "別嬪",
      "answer": "べっぴん",
      "meaning": "beautiful woman, pretty girl"
    },
    {
      "question": "丸顔",
      "answer": "まるがお",
      "meaning": "round face, moon face"
    },
    {
      "question": "失業",
      "answer": "しつぎょう",
      "meaning": "unemployment, losing one's job, becoming unemployed"
    },
    {
      "question": "落ち目",
      "answer": "おちめ",
      "meaning": "on the wane (e.g. popularity of something), decline of one's fortunes"
    },
    {
      "question": "一巻",
      "answer": "いっかん,ひとまき,いちまき",
      "meaning": "one roll, one book, one volume, first volume, rolling once, wrapping once around, one entire scroll"
    },
    {
      "question": "目力",
      "answer": "めぢから,めじから",
      "meaning": "strong impression conveyed by one's eyes, eyes that convey a strong sense of purpose"
    },
    {
      "question": "夜霧",
      "answer": "よぎり",
      "meaning": "night fog"
    },
    {
      "question": "梨花",
      "answer": "りか",
      "meaning": "pear blossoms"
    },
    {
      "question": "座卓",
      "answer": "ざたく",
      "meaning": "low table"
    },
    {
      "question": "罪作り",
      "answer": "つみつくり",
      "meaning": "deceitful, cruel"
    },
    {
      "question": "夢にも",
      "answer": "ゆめにも",
      "meaning": "(not) in the slightest, (not) at all"
    },
    {
      "question": "常温",
      "answer": "じょうおん",
      "meaning": "normal temperature, room temperature, constant temperature, fixed temperature"
    },
    {
      "question": "引っ込み",
      "answer": "ひっこみ",
      "meaning": "retreat, retirement, depression (hole)"
    },
    {
      "question": "腹を割る",
      "answer": "はらをわる",
      "meaning": "to be frank, to drop all pretense"
    },
    {
      "question": "許婚",
      "answer": "いいなずけ,いいなづけ,きょこん",
      "meaning": "fiance, fiancee"
    },
    {
      "question": "恣意的",
      "answer": "しいてき",
      "meaning": "arbitrary"
    },
    {
      "question": "だだ漏れ",
      "answer": "だだもれ",
      "meaning": "big leakage, uncontained leak"
    },
    {
      "question": "死相",
      "answer": "しそう",
      "meaning": "look of death, shadow of death"
    },
    {
      "question": "弱り切る",
      "answer": "よわりきる",
      "meaning": "to faint, to be exhausted"
    },
    {
      "question": "閉め出す",
      "answer": "しめだす",
      "meaning": "to shut out, to bar, to lock out, to exclude"
    },
    {
      "question": "艦首",
      "answer": "かんしゅ",
      "meaning": "bow (of a warship)"
    },
    {
      "question": "明神",
      "answer": "あきつかみ,みょうじん",
      "meaning": "emperor, living god, great god, gracious deity, miracle-working god"
    },
    {
      "question": "三途の川",
      "answer": "さんずのかわ",
      "meaning": "Sanzu River (Buddhist equivalent of the River Styx)"
    },
    {
      "question": "作為",
      "answer": "さくい",
      "meaning": "artificiality, pretence, contrived act, commission (of a crime), feasance"
    },
    {
      "question": "引き上げ",
      "answer": "ひきあげ",
      "meaning": "pulling up, drawing up, salvage, re-flotation, raising, increase, upward revision, repatriation, eva"
    },
    {
      "question": "声変わり",
      "answer": "こえがわり",
      "meaning": "change of voice (during puberty), break of voice"
    },
    {
      "question": "急病",
      "answer": "きゅうびょう",
      "meaning": "sudden illness"
    },
    {
      "question": "生け垣",
      "answer": "いけがき",
      "meaning": "hedge"
    },
    {
      "question": "甘口",
      "answer": "あまくち",
      "meaning": "sweet flavour, sweet flavor, mildness, flattery, stupidity"
    },
    {
      "question": "見応え",
      "answer": "みごたえ",
      "meaning": "(being) worth seeing, impressive"
    },
    {
      "question": "今彼",
      "answer": "いまかれ",
      "meaning": "current boyfriend"
    },
    {
      "question": "客寄せ",
      "answer": "きゃくよせ",
      "meaning": "attracting customers"
    },
    {
      "question": "退廃的",
      "answer": "たいはいてき",
      "meaning": "degenerate, decadent"
    },
    {
      "question": "物は試し",
      "answer": "ものはためし",
      "meaning": "the proof of the pudding is in the eating, the proof is in the pudding, don't knock it till you've t"
    },
    {
      "question": "着こなし",
      "answer": "きこなし",
      "meaning": "dressing well"
    },
    {
      "question": "宝物殿",
      "answer": "ほうもつでん",
      "meaning": "(shrine) repository or treasure house, (shrine) sanctuary"
    },
    {
      "question": "夢魔",
      "answer": "むま",
      "meaning": "nightmare, incubus, succubus, demon appearing in a dream"
    },
    {
      "question": "耐熱",
      "answer": "たいねつ",
      "meaning": "heat-resisting"
    },
    {
      "question": "吸盤",
      "answer": "きゅうばん",
      "meaning": "suction cup, suction pad, sucker"
    },
    {
      "question": "低速",
      "answer": "ていそく",
      "meaning": "low speed, slow speed"
    },
    {
      "question": "人恋しい",
      "answer": "ひとこいしい",
      "meaning": "longing for others, wanting company"
    },
    {
      "question": "丸暗記",
      "answer": "まるあんき",
      "meaning": "rote memorization (memorisation), rote learning, indiscriminate memorizing (memorising)"
    },
    {
      "question": "幼年",
      "answer": "ようねん",
      "meaning": "childhood, infancy"
    },
    {
      "question": "取り壊し",
      "answer": "とりこわし",
      "meaning": "demolition, pulling down, destruction, dismantling"
    },
    {
      "question": "隣家",
      "answer": "りんか",
      "meaning": "neighbouring house, neighboring house"
    },
    {
      "question": "一兵卒",
      "answer": "いっぺいそつ",
      "meaning": "private, foot soldier, infantryman, underling, low level worker, minor player"
    },
    {
      "question": "強制労働",
      "answer": "きょうせいろうどう",
      "meaning": "forced labor, forced labour, slave labor, slave labour"
    },
    {
      "question": "不眠",
      "answer": "ふみん",
      "meaning": "sleeplessness, insomnia, wakefulness"
    },
    {
      "question": "出禁",
      "answer": "できん",
      "meaning": "ban on entering a building, venue, etc."
    },
    {
      "question": "捻り出す",
      "answer": "ひねりだす",
      "meaning": "to work out, to think up, to devise, to come up with, to manage to find (money, time, etc.), to scra"
    },
    {
      "question": "勇み足",
      "answer": "いさみあし",
      "meaning": "overeagerness, rashness, forward step-out"
    },
    {
      "question": "創意工夫",
      "answer": "そういくふう",
      "meaning": "being imaginative and creative, creative originality"
    },
    {
      "question": "物的証拠",
      "answer": "ぶってきしょうこ",
      "meaning": "material or physical evidence"
    },
    {
      "question": "幕切れ",
      "answer": "まくぎれ",
      "meaning": "fall of the curtain, last scene, end of act"
    },
    {
      "question": "元老院",
      "answer": "げんろういん",
      "meaning": "(Roman) senate"
    },
    {
      "question": "寵",
      "answer": "ちょう",
      "meaning": "favor, favour, affection"
    },
    {
      "question": "車庫",
      "answer": "しゃこ",
      "meaning": "garage, carport, depot (trains, buses, etc.)"
    },
    {
      "question": "囲み",
      "answer": "かこみ",
      "meaning": "enclosure, box, siege"
    },
    {
      "question": "空き瓶",
      "answer": "あきびん",
      "meaning": "empty bottle"
    },
    {
      "question": "私見",
      "answer": "しけん",
      "meaning": "personal opinion"
    },
    {
      "question": "寮母",
      "answer": "りょうぼ",
      "meaning": "housemother, dorm mother"
    },
    {
      "question": "走査",
      "answer": "そうさ",
      "meaning": "scanning (e.g. TV), traversal"
    },
    {
      "question": "検体",
      "answer": "けんたい",
      "meaning": "specimen, sample, object to be examined"
    },
    {
      "question": "逆巻く",
      "answer": "さかまく",
      "meaning": "to surge (water or waves)"
    },
    {
      "question": "力及ばず",
      "answer": "ちからおよばず",
      "meaning": "unable to accomplish"
    },
    {
      "question": "本腰",
      "answer": "ほんごし",
      "meaning": "strenuous effort, earnestness, seriousness"
    },
    {
      "question": "夜行",
      "answer": "やぎょう,やこう",
      "meaning": "the 'ya' column of the Japanese syllabary table (ya, yu, yo), walking around at night, night travel,"
    },
    {
      "question": "書記官",
      "answer": "しょきかん",
      "meaning": "secretary"
    },
    {
      "question": "長者",
      "answer": "ちょうじゃ,ちょうしゃ,ちょうざ",
      "meaning": "millionaire, one's superior, one's elder, one's senior, virtuous and gentle person, female owner of"
    },
    {
      "question": "公約",
      "answer": "こうやく",
      "meaning": "public commitment, public promise, campaign pledge, official vow"
    },
    {
      "question": "実践的",
      "answer": "じっせんてき",
      "meaning": "practical, pragmatic, hands-on, nuts and bolts"
    },
    {
      "question": "墳墓",
      "answer": "ふんぼ",
      "meaning": "grave, tomb"
    },
    {
      "question": "九百",
      "answer": "きゅうひゃく,くひゃく",
      "meaning": "900, nine hundred, fool, idiot"
    },
    {
      "question": "是正",
      "answer": "ぜせい",
      "meaning": "correction, revision, redressing, rectifying"
    },
    {
      "question": "糖",
      "answer": "とう",
      "meaning": "sugar"
    },
    {
      "question": "河童",
      "answer": "かっぱ,かわっぱ",
      "meaning": "kappa, mythical water-dwelling creature, excellent swimmer, cucumber, cucumber sushi wrapped in nori"
    },
    {
      "question": "清冽",
      "answer": "せいれつ",
      "meaning": "cool and clear"
    },
    {
      "question": "明け透け",
      "answer": "あけすけ",
      "meaning": "open, frank, outspoken, unreserved, straightforward, honest"
    },
    {
      "question": "評論家",
      "answer": "ひょうろんか",
      "meaning": "critic, reviewer, commentator"
    },
    {
      "question": "留め置く",
      "answer": "とめおく",
      "meaning": "to detain, to keep, to lock up, to retain, to leave (letter) till called for"
    },
    {
      "question": "接地",
      "answer": "せっち",
      "meaning": "(electrical) ground, earth, grounding, earthing, touching the ground, landing (an airplane)"
    },
    {
      "question": "死に急ぐ",
      "answer": "しにいそぐ",
      "meaning": "to hasten one's death"
    },
    {
      "question": "関白",
      "answer": "かんぱく",
      "meaning": "chief advisor to the Emperor (adviser)"
    },
    {
      "question": "機首",
      "answer": "きしゅ",
      "meaning": "nose (of plane)"
    },
    {
      "question": "木星",
      "answer": "もくせい",
      "meaning": "Jupiter (planet)"
    },
    {
      "question": "井戸水",
      "answer": "いどみず",
      "meaning": "well water"
    },
    {
      "question": "危険信号",
      "answer": "きけんしんごう",
      "meaning": "danger signal, red light"
    },
    {
      "question": "一芝居",
      "answer": "ひとしばい",
      "meaning": "trick, act"
    },
    {
      "question": "新体操",
      "answer": "しんたいそう",
      "meaning": "rhythmic sports gymnastics"
    },
    {
      "question": "爆煙",
      "answer": "ばくえん",
      "meaning": "fumes from an explosion"
    },
    {
      "question": "現職",
      "answer": "げんしょく",
      "meaning": "present post, current office, (an) incumbent"
    },
    {
      "question": "小技",
      "answer": "こわざ",
      "meaning": "delicate technique (in sumo, judo, etc.), little trick, subtle maneuver"
    },
    {
      "question": "特殊性",
      "answer": "とくしゅせい",
      "meaning": "special characteristics, peculiarity, distinctiveness"
    },
    {
      "question": "嘆願書",
      "answer": "たんがんしょ",
      "meaning": "(written) petition"
    },
    {
      "question": "噎せる",
      "answer": "むせる",
      "meaning": "to choke, to be choked by, to be stifled by"
    },
    {
      "question": "凍傷",
      "answer": "とうしょう",
      "meaning": "frostbite, chilblains"
    },
    {
      "question": "一筆",
      "answer": "いっぴつ,ひとふで",
      "meaning": "one stroke (of a brush), a few lines (of writing), note, short letter, (dropping) a line, writing in"
    },
    {
      "question": "独善的",
      "answer": "どくぜんてき",
      "meaning": "self-righteous"
    },
    {
      "question": "神技",
      "answer": "しんぎ",
      "meaning": "divine or supernatural skill"
    },
    {
      "question": "片端から",
      "answer": "かたはしから",
      "meaning": "absolutely every little bit, everything from A to Z, systematically, thoroughly, one after another"
    },
    {
      "question": "六角形",
      "answer": "ろっかっけい,ろっかくけい",
      "meaning": "hexagon"
    },
    {
      "question": "水鏡",
      "answer": "みずかがみ",
      "meaning": "reflective water surface, reflecting water"
    },
    {
      "question": "葦",
      "answer": "あし,よし",
      "meaning": "common reed (Phragmites australis)"
    },
    {
      "question": "放牧",
      "answer": "ほうぼく",
      "meaning": "pasturage, grazing"
    },
    {
      "question": "今生",
      "answer": "こんじょう",
      "meaning": "this life, this world"
    },
    {
      "question": "秘め事",
      "answer": "ひめごと",
      "meaning": "secret"
    },
    {
      "question": "玉に瑕",
      "answer": "たまにきず",
      "meaning": "fly in the ointment, small flaw in otherwise perfect object, only trouble, only fault"
    },
    {
      "question": "秋月",
      "answer": "しゅうげつ",
      "meaning": "autumn moon, harvest moon"
    },
    {
      "question": "衛門",
      "answer": "",
      "meaning": ""
    },
    {
      "question": "其の",
      "answer": "その",
      "meaning": "that, the, part (as in 'part two'), um ..., er ..., uh ..."
    },
    {
      "question": "下女",
      "answer": "げじょ",
      "meaning": "maid servant"
    },
    {
      "question": "老兵",
      "answer": "ろうへい",
      "meaning": "old soldier"
    },
    {
      "question": "食肉",
      "answer": "しょくにく",
      "meaning": "meat (for consumption)"
    },
    {
      "question": "揉み合う",
      "answer": "もみあう",
      "meaning": "to jostle, to shove and push, to struggle with one another"
    },
    {
      "question": "水夫",
      "answer": "すいふ,かこ",
      "meaning": "sailor, seaman"
    },
    {
      "question": "震災",
      "answer": "しんさい",
      "meaning": "earthquake disaster, Great Kanto Earthquake (1923)"
    },
    {
      "question": "視姦",
      "answer": "しかん",
      "meaning": "ogling, eyeing (lecherously), leering, staring"
    },
    {
      "question": "小姑",
      "answer": "こじゅうとめ,こじゅうと",
      "meaning": "sister-in-law"
    },
    {
      "question": "小生",
      "answer": "しょうせい",
      "meaning": "I, me, my humble self"
    },
    {
      "question": "証文",
      "answer": "しょうもん",
      "meaning": "bond, deed, contract"
    },
    {
      "question": "蛆虫",
      "answer": "うじむし",
      "meaning": "maggot, worm, scum"
    },
    {
      "question": "静岡",
      "answer": "しずおか",
      "meaning": "Shizuoka (city, prefecture)"
    },
    {
      "question": "殺虫剤",
      "answer": "さっちゅうざい",
      "meaning": "insecticide, pesticide"
    },
    {
      "question": "熱愛",
      "answer": "ねつあい",
      "meaning": "love passionately, ardent love, devotion"
    },
    {
      "question": "横恋慕",
      "answer": "よこれんぼ",
      "meaning": "illicit love"
    },
    {
      "question": "荊",
      "answer": "いばら",
      "meaning": "thorny shrub, wild rose, briar, thorn, cusp"
    },
    {
      "question": "親衛",
      "answer": "しんえい",
      "meaning": "monarch's guards"
    },
    {
      "question": "前年",
      "answer": "ぜんねん",
      "meaning": "the preceding year, the previous year, last year"
    },
    {
      "question": "梳かす",
      "answer": "とかす",
      "meaning": "to comb out, to brush, to untangle, to unravel"
    },
    {
      "question": "身売り",
      "answer": "みうり",
      "meaning": "selling oneself (into bondage) (esp. for prostitutes)"
    },
    {
      "question": "筆箱",
      "answer": "ふでばこ",
      "meaning": "pencil case, pencil box, writing brush case"
    },
    {
      "question": "脱衣",
      "answer": "だつい,だつえ",
      "meaning": "undressing, taking off one's clothes"
    },
    {
      "question": "明るむ",
      "answer": "あかるむ",
      "meaning": "to brighten, to grow light"
    },
    {
      "question": "地下街",
      "answer": "ちかがい",
      "meaning": "underground shopping center, underground shopping centre"
    },
    {
      "question": "武技",
      "answer": "ぶぎ",
      "meaning": "martial arts"
    },
    {
      "question": "鳶色",
      "answer": "とびいろ",
      "meaning": "reddish brown"
    },
    {
      "question": "船頭",
      "answer": "せんどう",
      "meaning": "boatman, ferryman"
    },
    {
      "question": "死に体",
      "answer": "しにたい",
      "meaning": "losing posture, falling position from which it is impossible to recover, lame duck, hopeless situati"
    },
    {
      "question": "母子家庭",
      "answer": "ぼしかてい",
      "meaning": "single-mother household, fatherless family"
    },
    {
      "question": "言葉の綾",
      "answer": "ことばのあや",
      "meaning": "figure of speech"
    },
    {
      "question": "天賦",
      "answer": "てんぷ",
      "meaning": "natural (e.g. talent), innate, inborn, inherent"
    },
    {
      "question": "人馬",
      "answer": "じんば",
      "meaning": "man and horse, rider and horse, centaur"
    },
    {
      "question": "最前",
      "answer": "さいぜん",
      "meaning": "frontmost, some time ago, just now"
    },
    {
      "question": "装身具",
      "answer": "そうしんぐ",
      "meaning": "personal accessories (ornaments, adornments)"
    },
    {
      "question": "集合住宅",
      "answer": "しゅうごうじゅうたく",
      "meaning": "apartment building, housing complex"
    },
    {
      "question": "座す",
      "answer": "ざす",
      "meaning": "to sit, to squat, to be implicated"
    },
    {
      "question": "出合う",
      "answer": "であう",
      "meaning": "to meet (by chance), to come across, to run across, to encounter, to happen upon, to meet (e.g. of r"
    },
    {
      "question": "情報局",
      "answer": "じょうほうきょく",
      "meaning": "intelligence agency, intelligence bureau, Cabinet Intelligence Bureau (1940-1945)"
    },
    {
      "question": "金星",
      "answer": "きんせい,きんぼし",
      "meaning": "Venus (planet), dazzling victory, win of a rank-and-file wrestler over the grand champion"
    },
    {
      "question": "懇親会",
      "answer": "こんしんかい",
      "meaning": "social gathering, get-together, (friendly) meeting"
    },
    {
      "question": "入電",
      "answer": "にゅうでん",
      "meaning": "incoming telephone call, telegram received"
    },
    {
      "question": "水汲み",
      "answer": "みずくみ",
      "meaning": "drawing water"
    },
    {
      "question": "発送",
      "answer": "はっそう",
      "meaning": "sending, forwarding, shipping"
    },
    {
      "question": "張り手",
      "answer": "はりて",
      "meaning": "slapping the opponent with the open hand"
    },
    {
      "question": "聞き違い",
      "answer": "ききちがい",
      "meaning": "mishearing"
    },
    {
      "question": "立て看板",
      "answer": "たてかんばん",
      "meaning": "standing signboard, billboard, hoarding"
    },
    {
      "question": "大団円",
      "answer": "だいだんえん",
      "meaning": "denouement, ending, conclusion, (grand) finale"
    },
    {
      "question": "一貫性",
      "answer": "いっかんせい",
      "meaning": "consistency"
    },
    {
      "question": "常務",
      "answer": "じょうむ",
      "meaning": "managing director, executive director, routine business, regular business"
    },
    {
      "question": "徴税",
      "answer": "ちょうぜい",
      "meaning": "tax collection, taxation"
    },
    {
      "question": "床面",
      "answer": "ゆかめん",
      "meaning": "floor, floor surface"
    },
    {
      "question": "客車",
      "answer": "きゃくしゃ,かくしゃ",
      "meaning": "passenger car"
    },
    {
      "question": "劣等",
      "answer": "れっとう",
      "meaning": "inferiority, low grade"
    },
    {
      "question": "星形",
      "answer": "ほしがた",
      "meaning": "star shape, pentagram"
    },
    {
      "question": "肥やし",
      "answer": "こやし",
      "meaning": "manure, night soil, dung, fertiliser, fertilizer, something that will help one develop in the future"
    },
    {
      "question": "興醒め",
      "answer": "きょうざめ",
      "meaning": "spoiled fun, loss of interest, damper (e.g. on the party), wet blanket, turn-off"
    },
    {
      "question": "風土",
      "answer": "ふうど",
      "meaning": "natural features, topography, climate, spiritual features"
    },
    {
      "question": "鍾乳洞",
      "answer": "しょうにゅうどう",
      "meaning": "limestone cave, limestone cavern"
    },
    {
      "question": "二者",
      "answer": "にしゃ",
      "meaning": "two things, two persons"
    },
    {
      "question": "疚しい",
      "answer": "やましい",
      "meaning": "feeling guilty, having a guilty conscience, having qualms about"
    },
    {
      "question": "軟派",
      "answer": "なんぱ",
      "meaning": "seducer, smooth talker, ladies' man, playboy, playgirl, picking up women, hitting on women, moderate"
    },
    {
      "question": "肖像",
      "answer": "しょうぞう",
      "meaning": "portrait, likeness, picture"
    },
    {
      "question": "扇状",
      "answer": "せんじょう",
      "meaning": "fan form (shape)"
    },
    {
      "question": "名店",
      "answer": "めいてん",
      "meaning": "well-known store"
    },
    {
      "question": "相席",
      "answer": "あいせき",
      "meaning": "sharing a table with someone you don't know (e.g. at a restaurant)"
    },
    {
      "question": "口唇",
      "answer": "こうしん",
      "meaning": "lips"
    },
    {
      "question": "場数",
      "answer": "ばかず",
      "meaning": "experiences"
    },
    {
      "question": "司令長官",
      "answer": "しれいちょうかん",
      "meaning": "Commander-in-Chief, C-in-C"
    },
    {
      "question": "城砦",
      "answer": "じょうさい",
      "meaning": "fortress, stronghold, citadel"
    },
    {
      "question": "小径",
      "answer": "こみち,しょうけい",
      "meaning": "path, lane, small diameter, small radius"
    },
    {
      "question": "令状",
      "answer": "れいじょう",
      "meaning": "warrant, summons, written order"
    },
    {
      "question": "食い逃げ",
      "answer": "くいにげ",
      "meaning": "leaving a restaurant without paying, dine and dash, bilking"
    },
    {
      "question": "刈り込む",
      "answer": "かりこむ",
      "meaning": "to prune, to trim, to cut back, to clip, to reap (a crop) and put into storage, to harvest, to prune"
    },
    {
      "question": "担ぎ込む",
      "answer": "かつぎこむ",
      "meaning": "to carry something into a place"
    },
    {
      "question": "席を譲る",
      "answer": "せきをゆずる",
      "meaning": "to give one's seat to someone, to offer one's seat"
    },
    {
      "question": "接客業",
      "answer": "せっきゃくぎょう",
      "meaning": "hospitality industry, service trade (hotel and restaurant), service industry"
    },
    {
      "question": "蟬",
      "answer": "せみ,せび",
      "meaning": "cicada, locust, small-sized pulley"
    },
    {
      "question": "尺",
      "answer": "しゃく,あた,さし",
      "meaning": "shaku (unit of distance approximately equal to 30.3 cm), rule, measure, scale, length, distance betw"
    },
    {
      "question": "等価",
      "answer": "とうか",
      "meaning": "equivalence, equal value, parity, (logical) equivalence"
    },
    {
      "question": "孝",
      "answer": "こう,きょう",
      "meaning": "filial piety"
    },
    {
      "question": "篇",
      "answer": "へん",
      "meaning": "compilation (of a text), editing, volume (of a text), completed literary work"
    },
    {
      "question": "菫色",
      "answer": "すみれいろ",
      "meaning": "violet (colour)"
    },
    {
      "question": "浚う",
      "answer": "さらう",
      "meaning": "to sweep away, to wash away, to dredge"
    },
    {
      "question": "抗戦",
      "answer": "こうせん",
      "meaning": "resistance"
    },
    {
      "question": "自治体",
      "answer": "じちたい",
      "meaning": "municipality, local government, self-governing body, autonomous body"
    },
    {
      "question": "彦",
      "answer": "ひこ",
      "meaning": "boy"
    },
    {
      "question": "生産者",
      "answer": "せいさんしゃ",
      "meaning": "manufacturer, producer"
    },
    {
      "question": "吹き荒ぶ",
      "answer": "ふきすさぶ",
      "meaning": "to blow fiercely, to rage, to play (a flute, etc.) for fun"
    },
    {
      "question": "体捌き",
      "answer": "たいさばき",
      "meaning": "defensive body movement (judo, kendo, etc.)"
    },
    {
      "question": "死なす",
      "answer": "しなす",
      "meaning": "to let die"
    },
    {
      "question": "不勉強",
      "answer": "ふべんきょう",
      "meaning": "idleness, lack of application, lazy study habits"
    },
    {
      "question": "時間外",
      "answer": "じかんがい",
      "meaning": "overtime, outside of hours (school, office, surgery, etc.)"
    },
    {
      "question": "護衛艦",
      "answer": "ごえいかん",
      "meaning": "escort vessel, destroyer (Japan Maritime Self-Defense Force)"
    },
    {
      "question": "山村",
      "answer": "さんそん",
      "meaning": "mountain village"
    },
    {
      "question": "半べそ",
      "answer": "はんべそ",
      "meaning": "half-crying, being on the verge of crying"
    },
    {
      "question": "貪り食う",
      "answer": "むさぼりくう",
      "meaning": "to devour greedily, to wolf down, to gobble up"
    },
    {
      "question": "戌",
      "answer": "いぬ",
      "meaning": "the Dog (eleventh sign of the Chinese zodiac), hour of the Dog (around 8pm, 7-9pm, or 8-10pm), west-"
    },
    {
      "question": "男神",
      "answer": "おがみ,おのかみ,おとこがみ",
      "meaning": "male god, male deity"
    },
    {
      "question": "楠",
      "answer": "くすのき,くす",
      "meaning": "camphor tree (Cinnamomum camphora), camphorwood, camphor laurel"
    },
    {
      "question": "新潟",
      "answer": "にいがた",
      "meaning": "Niigata (city, prefecture)"
    },
    {
      "question": "袈裟斬り",
      "answer": "けさぎり",
      "meaning": "slashing a sword diagonally from the shoulder"
    },
    {
      "question": "舳先",
      "answer": "へさき",
      "meaning": "bow (of a ship), prow"
    },
    {
      "question": "内閣",
      "answer": "ないかく",
      "meaning": "cabinet (of a government), ministry"
    },
    {
      "question": "寝過ぎる",
      "answer": "ねすぎる",
      "meaning": "to oversleep"
    },
    {
      "question": "相克",
      "answer": "そうこく",
      "meaning": "rivalry"
    },
    {
      "question": "山林",
      "answer": "さんりん",
      "meaning": "mountain forest, forest on a mountain, montane forest, mountains and forest"
    },
    {
      "question": "白装束",
      "answer": "しろしょうぞく",
      "meaning": "white clothing"
    },
    {
      "question": "身の毛",
      "answer": "みのけ",
      "meaning": "body hair"
    },
    {
      "question": "貢物",
      "answer": "みつぎもの",
      "meaning": "tribute"
    },
    {
      "question": "競走",
      "answer": "きょうそう",
      "meaning": "race"
    },
    {
      "question": "南蛮",
      "answer": "なんばん",
      "meaning": "southern barbarians (formerly used by the Chinese to refer to non-ethnic Chinese to the south), Sout"
    },
    {
      "question": "釣竿",
      "answer": "つりざお",
      "meaning": "fishing rod"
    },
    {
      "question": "柱時計",
      "answer": "はしらどけい",
      "meaning": "wall clock, grandfather clock"
    },
    {
      "question": "断食",
      "answer": "だんじき",
      "meaning": "fasting, fast"
    },
    {
      "question": "茄子",
      "answer": "なす,なすび",
      "meaning": "eggplant (Solanum melongena), aubergine"
    },
    {
      "question": "舞踊",
      "answer": "ぶよう",
      "meaning": "dancing, dance"
    },
    {
      "question": "忖度",
      "answer": "そんたく",
      "meaning": "surmise (about somebody's feelings), guess, conjecture"
    },
    {
      "question": "踏襲",
      "answer": "とうしゅう",
      "meaning": "following (a precedent, former policy, etc.), continuing with, sticking to, observing"
    },
    {
      "question": "今少し",
      "answer": "いますこし",
      "meaning": "a little more"
    },
    {
      "question": "必要条件",
      "answer": "ひつようじょうけん",
      "meaning": "necessary condition, requirement"
    },
    {
      "question": "駅弁",
      "answer": "えきべん",
      "meaning": "boxed lunch bought at a station (often a local specialty), sexual position in which one person stand"
    },
    {
      "question": "前輪",
      "answer": "ぜんりん,まえわ",
      "meaning": "front wheel, saddle fork"
    },
    {
      "question": "議",
      "answer": "ぎ",
      "meaning": "discussion, deliberation, thought, opinion"
    },
    {
      "question": "国営",
      "answer": "こくえい",
      "meaning": "government management, state management"
    },
    {
      "question": "低血圧",
      "answer": "ていけつあつ",
      "meaning": "low blood pressure"
    },
    {
      "question": "事後報告",
      "answer": "じごほうこく",
      "meaning": "ex post facto report, report after the event"
    },
    {
      "question": "政争",
      "answer": "せいそう",
      "meaning": "political strife"
    },
    {
      "question": "手相",
      "answer": "てそう",
      "meaning": "palm reading"
    },
    {
      "question": "預金",
      "answer": "よきん",
      "meaning": "deposit, bank account"
    },
    {
      "question": "一箱",
      "answer": "ひとはこ,いっぱこ",
      "meaning": "a (one) box"
    },
    {
      "question": "横付け",
      "answer": "よこづけ",
      "meaning": "bringing alongside (ship, vehicle, etc.), coming alongside, mooring"
    },
    {
      "question": "完全犯罪",
      "answer": "かんぜんはんざい",
      "meaning": "perfect crime"
    },
    {
      "question": "斬り払う",
      "answer": "きりはらう",
      "meaning": "to clear away, to clear land, to prune, to lop off"
    },
    {
      "question": "何たって",
      "answer": "なんたって",
      "meaning": "no matter what, whatever you say, in the end, after all"
    },
    {
      "question": "自然治癒",
      "answer": "しぜんちゆ",
      "meaning": "self-healing, spontaneous recovery"
    },
    {
      "question": "語感",
      "answer": "ごかん",
      "meaning": "sense of language, feeling of a word, impression a word makes, nuance"
    },
    {
      "question": "白魚",
      "answer": "しらうお,しろうお",
      "meaning": "icefish (Salangidae spp., esp. the Japanese icefish, Salangichthys microdon), noodlefish, whitebait,"
    },
    {
      "question": "隆盛",
      "answer": "りゅうせい",
      "meaning": "prosperity, flourishing, thriving"
    },
    {
      "question": "血が通う",
      "answer": "ちがかよう",
      "meaning": "to be flowing (of blood), to be alive, to be humane, to show signs of humanity"
    },
    {
      "question": "和泉",
      "answer": "いずみ",
      "meaning": "Izumi (former province located in the southwest of present-day Osaka Prefecture)"
    },
    {
      "question": "毒矢",
      "answer": "どくや",
      "meaning": "poisoned arrow (dart)"
    },
    {
      "question": "中部",
      "answer": "ちゅうぶ",
      "meaning": "center, centre, middle, heart, Chūbu region (incl. Aichi, Nagano, Shizuoka, Niigata, Toyama, Ishikaw"
    },
    {
      "question": "我が妻",
      "answer": "わがつま",
      "meaning": "my spouse (esp. used to refer to one's wife), my wife, my husband"
    },
    {
      "question": "語呂",
      "answer": "ごろ",
      "meaning": "sound (of a sentence), euphony"
    },
    {
      "question": "自衛官",
      "answer": "じえいかん",
      "meaning": "Japanese Self-Defense Force official, Self-Defense Force official"
    },
    {
      "question": "変顔",
      "answer": "へんがお",
      "meaning": "making a strange face, strange face"
    },
    {
      "question": "英文",
      "answer": "えいぶん",
      "meaning": "English writing, English sentence, English text, English literature, English lit"
    },
    {
      "question": "意訳",
      "answer": "いやく",
      "meaning": "free translation, liberal translation"
    },
    {
      "question": "人間臭い",
      "answer": "にんげんくさい",
      "meaning": "human-like, quite human"
    },
    {
      "question": "柏木",
      "answer": "かしわぎ",
      "meaning": "oak tree, imperial palace guard"
    },
    {
      "question": "奉じる",
      "answer": "ほうじる",
      "meaning": "to present, to dedicate, to obey, to follow, to believe in, to serve, to proudly bear"
    },
    {
      "question": "人骨",
      "answer": "じんこつ",
      "meaning": "human bones"
    },
    {
      "question": "来歴",
      "answer": "らいれき",
      "meaning": "history, career"
    },
    {
      "question": "溶液",
      "answer": "ようえき",
      "meaning": "solution (liquid)"
    },
    {
      "question": "帰らぬ人",
      "answer": "かえらぬひと",
      "meaning": "dead person, deceased person"
    },
    {
      "question": "教主",
      "answer": "きょうしゅ",
      "meaning": "founder of a religious sect"
    },
    {
      "question": "隼",
      "answer": "はやぶさ",
      "meaning": "falcon (esp. the peregrine falcon, Falco peregrinus)"
    },
    {
      "question": "二等",
      "answer": "にとう",
      "meaning": "second class"
    },
    {
      "question": "付する",
      "answer": "ふする",
      "meaning": "to affix, to append, to attach, to entrust, to refer, to handle (as such), to follow (the leader), t"
    },
    {
      "question": "目次",
      "answer": "もくじ",
      "meaning": "table of contents, contents"
    },
    {
      "question": "腰元",
      "answer": "こしもと",
      "meaning": "chamber maid, female servant, area around the hips, waist area"
    },
    {
      "question": "割り当て",
      "answer": "わりあて",
      "meaning": "allotment, assignment, allocation, quota, rationing"
    },
    {
      "question": "後出し",
      "answer": "あとだし",
      "meaning": "waiting to see one's opponent's move before doing anything (e.g. as a disallowed act in rock, paper,"
    },
    {
      "question": "養育費",
      "answer": "よういくひ",
      "meaning": "child-rearing expenses, child-support payments (following divorce)"
    },
    {
      "question": "皮肉る",
      "answer": "ひにくる",
      "meaning": "to make a cynical remark, to make fun of"
    },
    {
      "question": "形容詞",
      "answer": "けいようし",
      "meaning": "adjective, i-adjective (in Japanese)"
    },
    {
      "question": "生傷",
      "answer": "なまきず",
      "meaning": "fresh wound, fresh bruise"
    },
    {
      "question": "稲荷",
      "answer": "いなり",
      "meaning": "Inari (god of harvests, Uka-no-Mitama), Inari shrine, Fushimi Inari shrine (in Kyoto), fox (said to"
    },
    {
      "question": "素数",
      "answer": "そすう",
      "meaning": "prime number"
    },
    {
      "question": "裁断",
      "answer": "さいだん",
      "meaning": "cutting (cloth, paper), judgement, judgment, decision"
    },
    {
      "question": "水っぽい",
      "answer": "みずっぽい",
      "meaning": "watery, soggy, racy, titillating, sexy, suggestive"
    },
    {
      "question": "触診",
      "answer": "しょくしん",
      "meaning": "palpation"
    },
    {
      "question": "一円",
      "answer": "いちえん",
      "meaning": "one yen, throughout (an area), whole district"
    },
    {
      "question": "人間業",
      "answer": "にんげんわざ",
      "meaning": "the work of man, human feat, something humanly possible"
    },
    {
      "question": "駿河",
      "answer": "するが",
      "meaning": "Suruga (former province located in the central and northern parts of present-day Shizuoka Prefecture"
    },
    {
      "question": "警部補",
      "answer": "けいぶほ",
      "meaning": "assistant inspector"
    },
    {
      "question": "団扇",
      "answer": "うちわ",
      "meaning": "uchiwa, type of traditional Japanese handheld fan"
    },
    {
      "question": "普通科",
      "answer": "ふつうか",
      "meaning": "infantry (in the Japan Ground Self-Defense Force), general education curriculum"
    },
    {
      "question": "旅程",
      "answer": "りょてい",
      "meaning": "itinerary, travel plans, distance (of a trip), journey"
    },
    {
      "question": "一顧",
      "answer": "いっこ",
      "meaning": "(take no) notice of"
    },
    {
      "question": "活ける",
      "answer": "いける",
      "meaning": "to arrange (flowers), to plant"
    },
    {
      "question": "手編み",
      "answer": "てあみ",
      "meaning": "(hand) knitting"
    },
    {
      "question": "通過儀礼",
      "answer": "つうかぎれい",
      "meaning": "rite of passage"
    },
    {
      "question": "表面化",
      "answer": "ひょうめんか",
      "meaning": "coming to a head, coming to the surface, becoming an issue, breaking"
    },
    {
      "question": "一括り",
      "answer": "ひとくくり",
      "meaning": "lump together, put all together"
    },
    {
      "question": "変わり目",
      "answer": "かわりめ",
      "meaning": "turning point, change, transition, turn (of the tide, century, etc.), point of difference"
    },
    {
      "question": "蛹",
      "answer": "さなぎ",
      "meaning": "chrysalis, pupa"
    },
    {
      "question": "試行",
      "answer": "しこう",
      "meaning": "making an attempt, trial run"
    },
    {
      "question": "税率",
      "answer": "ぜいりつ",
      "meaning": "tariff, tax rate"
    },
    {
      "question": "一席",
      "answer": "いっせき",
      "meaning": "sitting, feast, speech"
    },
    {
      "question": "予備知識",
      "answer": "よびちしき",
      "meaning": "background knowledge, prerequisite knowledge"
    },
    {
      "question": "保管場所",
      "answer": "ほかんばしょ",
      "meaning": "depository, storage area, storage location, storage site"
    },
    {
      "question": "土蔵",
      "answer": "どぞう",
      "meaning": "storehouse with thick (earthen) walls, godown"
    },
    {
      "question": "構造体",
      "answer": "こうぞうたい",
      "meaning": "structure"
    },
    {
      "question": "雨乞い",
      "answer": "あまごい",
      "meaning": "praying for rain"
    },
    {
      "question": "女嫌い",
      "answer": "おんなぎらい",
      "meaning": "misogyny, woman-hater, misogynist"
    },
    {
      "question": "重火器",
      "answer": "じゅうかき",
      "meaning": "heavy weapons"
    },
    {
      "question": "全米",
      "answer": "ぜんべい",
      "meaning": "all-America, pan-American, all of America"
    },
    {
      "question": "助命",
      "answer": "じょめい",
      "meaning": "sparing a life, clemency, reconsideration of an employee's dismissal"
    },
    {
      "question": "集る",
      "answer": "あつまる,たかる",
      "meaning": "to gather, to collect, to assemble, to crowd round, to swarm, to flock, to sponge (off someone), to"
    },
    {
      "question": "ガス抜き",
      "answer": "ガスぬき",
      "meaning": "degassing, gas drainage, gas venting, punching down (dough), letting off steam, letting out stress,"
    },
    {
      "question": "沙羅",
      "answer": "しゃら,さら",
      "meaning": "sal (tree) (Shorea robusta), saul, Japanese stewartia (Stewartia pseudocamellia)"
    },
    {
      "question": "整合",
      "answer": "せいごう",
      "meaning": "adjustment, coordination, integration, conformity"
    },
    {
      "question": "雷雨",
      "answer": "らいう",
      "meaning": "thunderstorm"
    },
    {
      "question": "折半",
      "answer": "せっぱん",
      "meaning": "halving, splitting evenly, sharing equally"
    },
    {
      "question": "歩み寄り",
      "answer": "あゆみより",
      "meaning": "compromise, concession"
    },
    {
      "question": "余白",
      "answer": "よはく",
      "meaning": "blank space, margin, blank canvas"
    },
    {
      "question": "顔パス",
      "answer": "かおパス",
      "meaning": "getting free admission on the strength of one's name, being let in somewhere because one is recogniz"
    },
    {
      "question": "熟読",
      "answer": "じゅくどく",
      "meaning": "perusal, careful reading"
    },
    {
      "question": "恩賞",
      "answer": "おんしょう",
      "meaning": "reward"
    },
    {
      "question": "字幕",
      "answer": "じまく",
      "meaning": "subtitles, captioning"
    },
    {
      "question": "真贋",
      "answer": "しんがん",
      "meaning": "genuineness or spuriousness, authenticity, the genuine and the spurious"
    },
    {
      "question": "信号機",
      "answer": "しんごうき",
      "meaning": "traffic light, signalling mechanism, semaphore (apparatus)"
    },
    {
      "question": "折り目",
      "answer": "おりめ",
      "meaning": "fold, crease, pleat, manners, courtesy, responsible behavior (behaviour)"
    },
    {
      "question": "押し付け",
      "answer": "おしつけ",
      "meaning": "imposition (i.e. of rules, of a decision), compulsion"
    },
    {
      "question": "批判的",
      "answer": "ひはんてき",
      "meaning": "critical, judgmental"
    },
    {
      "question": "焼け跡",
      "answer": "やけあと",
      "meaning": "ruins of a fire, fire-devastated area"
    },
    {
      "question": "隔たる",
      "answer": "へだたる",
      "meaning": "to be distant"
    },
    {
      "question": "粛正",
      "answer": "しゅくせい",
      "meaning": "regulation, enforcement"
    },
    {
      "question": "流行病",
      "answer": "りゅうこうびょう",
      "meaning": "epidemic"
    },
    {
      "question": "書き綴る",
      "answer": "かきつづる",
      "meaning": "to put into written form, to communicate or express by writing, to chronicle"
    },
    {
      "question": "出来映え",
      "answer": "できばえ",
      "meaning": "result, effect, performance, success, workmanship, execution, shape and quality (of an article), fin"
    },
    {
      "question": "捨て犬",
      "answer": "すていぬ",
      "meaning": "stray dog"
    },
    {
      "question": "猛省",
      "answer": "もうせい",
      "meaning": "serious reflection, soul-searching, penitence"
    },
    {
      "question": "静音",
      "answer": "せいおん",
      "meaning": "low noise (of a machine, appliance, etc.), silent (device)"
    },
    {
      "question": "揮う",
      "answer": "ふるう",
      "meaning": "to swing, to wield (physically), to exert, to exercise (e.g. power, ability), to exhibit, to display"
    },
    {
      "question": "氷河",
      "answer": "ひょうが",
      "meaning": "glacier"
    },
    {
      "question": "大道芸人",
      "answer": "だいどうげいにん",
      "meaning": "street performer (comedian)"
    },
    {
      "question": "定刻",
      "answer": "ていこく",
      "meaning": "appointed time, timetable, schedule"
    },
    {
      "question": "再放送",
      "answer": "さいほうそう",
      "meaning": "rebroadcasting, rerun"
    },
    {
      "question": "貯金箱",
      "answer": "ちょきんばこ",
      "meaning": "savings box, moneybox, piggy bank"
    },
    {
      "question": "秘奥",
      "answer": "ひおう",
      "meaning": "secrets, mysteries"
    },
    {
      "question": "常夏",
      "answer": "とこなつ",
      "meaning": "everlasting summer"
    },
    {
      "question": "小手",
      "answer": "こて",
      "meaning": "gauntlet (used in Kendo), bracer, fencing glove, forearm"
    },
    {
      "question": "組み手",
      "answer": "くみて",
      "meaning": "wooden joints, paired karate kata, beltwork"
    },
    {
      "question": "独裁",
      "answer": "どくさい",
      "meaning": "dictatorship, despotism"
    },
    {
      "question": "貧乏性",
      "answer": "びんぼうしょう",
      "meaning": "parsimonious spirit, tendency to be frugal, inclination to scrimp and save, tendency to fuss over tr"
    },
    {
      "question": "一言多い",
      "answer": "ひとことおおい",
      "meaning": "saying too much"
    },
    {
      "question": "轍を踏む",
      "answer": "てつをふむ",
      "meaning": "to repeat a mistake (of somebody), to make the same mistake as that of ..., to follow the rut (left"
    },
    {
      "question": "真壁",
      "answer": "しんかべ",
      "meaning": "wall with exposed timber pillars"
    },
    {
      "question": "赤褐色",
      "answer": "せっかっしょく",
      "meaning": "reddish brown, rufous"
    },
    {
      "question": "肉質",
      "answer": "にくしつ",
      "meaning": "fleshiness, meat quality"
    },
    {
      "question": "痩せ",
      "answer": "やせ",
      "meaning": "losing weight, slimming, lean person"
    },
    {
      "question": "金城",
      "answer": "きんじょう",
      "meaning": "impregnable castle, inner castle citadel, golden castle (nickname for Nagoya Castle)"
    },
    {
      "question": "坐る",
      "answer": "すわる",
      "meaning": "to sit, to squat, to assume (a position), to hold steady, to hold still"
    },
    {
      "question": "頽れる",
      "answer": "すたれる,くずおれる",
      "meaning": "to go out of use, to become obsolete, to die out, to go out of fashion, to collapse (physically or e"
    },
    {
      "question": "腹ぺこ",
      "answer": "はらぺこ",
      "meaning": "hungry, starving"
    },
    {
      "question": "禁じ手",
      "answer": "きんじて",
      "meaning": "forbidden move (sumo, shogi, go, etc.), prohibited move, foul"
    },
    {
      "question": "晴れ姿",
      "answer": "はれすがた",
      "meaning": "appearing in one's finest clothes, appearing in one's hour of triumph"
    },
    {
      "question": "氷壁",
      "answer": "ひょうへき",
      "meaning": "ice wall, ice ridge"
    },
    {
      "question": "美脚",
      "answer": "びきゃく",
      "meaning": "beautiful legs, great legs"
    },
    {
      "question": "報道陣",
      "answer": "ほうどうじん",
      "meaning": "press corps"
    },
    {
      "question": "均す",
      "answer": "ならす",
      "meaning": "to make even, to make smooth, to make level, to flatten, to average"
    },
    {
      "question": "粗悪",
      "answer": "そあく",
      "meaning": "coarse, crude, inferior"
    },
    {
      "question": "黒地",
      "answer": "くろじ",
      "meaning": "black ground, black cloth"
    },
    {
      "question": "重病",
      "answer": "じゅうびょう",
      "meaning": "serious illness"
    },
    {
      "question": "皇室",
      "answer": "こうしつ",
      "meaning": "Imperial household"
    },
    {
      "question": "諫言",
      "answer": "かんげん",
      "meaning": "admonition, remonstrance, expostulation"
    },
    {
      "question": "瑕疵",
      "answer": "かし",
      "meaning": "flaw, defect, fault"
    },
    {
      "question": "天宮",
      "answer": "てんきゅう,ティアンゴン",
      "meaning": "heavenly palace, sky, Tiangong (Chinese space program)"
    },
    {
      "question": "明星",
      "answer": "みょうじょう",
      "meaning": "morning star, Venus, preeminent person (within their own field), star (of the stage, silver screen,"
    },
    {
      "question": "三国志",
      "answer": "さんごくし",
      "meaning": "Records of the Three Kingdoms, Annals of the Three Kingdoms"
    },
    {
      "question": "市民権",
      "answer": "しみんけん",
      "meaning": "citizenship, civic rights, civil rights, widespread acceptance, social recognition, common use"
    },
    {
      "question": "証書",
      "answer": "しょうしょ",
      "meaning": "document (of proof), certificate, paper, bond, deed"
    },
    {
      "question": "鉄筋",
      "answer": "てっきん",
      "meaning": "rebar, (iron) reinforcing bar, reinforcing steel, reinforced concrete"
    },
    {
      "question": "愛弟子",
      "answer": "まなでし",
      "meaning": "favorite pupil, favourite pupil, teacher's pet"
    },
    {
      "question": "湾岸",
      "answer": "わんがん",
      "meaning": "gulf coast, bay coast"
    },
    {
      "question": "列席",
      "answer": "れっせき",
      "meaning": "attendance"
    },
    {
      "question": "原本",
      "answer": "げんぽん",
      "meaning": "the original, original copy, script"
    },
    {
      "question": "暗算",
      "answer": "あんざん",
      "meaning": "mental arithmetic"
    },
    {
      "question": "雌雄",
      "answer": "しゆう",
      "meaning": "male and female (animals), the two sexes, victory and defeat, strengths and weaknesses"
    },
    {
      "question": "入籍",
      "answer": "にゅうせき",
      "meaning": "entry in family register"
    },
    {
      "question": "解約",
      "answer": "かいやく",
      "meaning": "cancellation of a contract"
    },
    {
      "question": "早晩",
      "answer": "そうばん",
      "meaning": "sooner or later, in time, eventually"
    },
    {
      "question": "質実剛健",
      "answer": "しつじつごうけん",
      "meaning": "unaffected and sincere, with fortitude and vigor (vigour)"
    },
    {
      "question": "泣き真似",
      "answer": "なきまね",
      "meaning": "feigned tears, crocodile tears"
    },
    {
      "question": "麻布",
      "answer": "あさぬの,まふ",
      "meaning": "hemp cloth, linen"
    },
    {
      "question": "綴じる",
      "answer": "とじる",
      "meaning": "to bind, to file, to top with egg (e.g. donburi)"
    },
    {
      "question": "透く",
      "answer": "すく",
      "meaning": "to be transparent, to leave a gap"
    },
    {
      "question": "火線",
      "answer": "かせん",
      "meaning": "firing line"
    },
    {
      "question": "酸化",
      "answer": "さんか",
      "meaning": "oxidation, oxidization"
    },
    {
      "question": "御覧",
      "answer": "ごらん",
      "meaning": "(please) try to, (please) look, seeing, looking, watching"
    },
    {
      "question": "片す",
      "answer": "かたす",
      "meaning": "to move, to put elsewhere, to tidy, to put in order"
    },
    {
      "question": "特区",
      "answer": "とっく",
      "meaning": "special ward, special economic zone (China), special administrative region of China (e.g. Hong Kong)"
    },
    {
      "question": "潜行",
      "answer": "せんこう",
      "meaning": "underwater navigation, going underground, going into hiding, travelling incognito, traveling incogni"
    },
    {
      "question": "降嫁",
      "answer": "こうか",
      "meaning": "marriage of an Imperial princess to a subject"
    },
    {
      "question": "拡大解釈",
      "answer": "かくだいかいしゃく",
      "meaning": "broad interpretation"
    },
    {
      "question": "反吐",
      "answer": "へど",
      "meaning": "vomit, vomiting"
    },
    {
      "question": "広義",
      "answer": "こうぎ",
      "meaning": "wide sense (e.g. of a word), broad sense"
    },
    {
      "question": "口撃",
      "answer": "こうげき",
      "meaning": "verbal attack"
    },
    {
      "question": "世迷言",
      "answer": "よまいごと",
      "meaning": "grumbling, muttering, nonsense"
    },
    {
      "question": "物寂しい",
      "answer": "ものさびしい",
      "meaning": "lonely"
    },
    {
      "question": "詠",
      "answer": "えい",
      "meaning": "recitation (of a poem), chanting, singing, composition (of a poem), composed poem"
    },
    {
      "question": "炎熱",
      "answer": "えんねつ",
      "meaning": "sweltering heat"
    },
    {
      "question": "所見",
      "answer": "しょけん",
      "meaning": "view, opinion, finding, findings"
    },
    {
      "question": "牽く",
      "answer": "ひく",
      "meaning": "to pull, to tug, to lead (e.g. a horse), to draw (attention, sympathy, etc.), to attract (e.g. inter"
    },
    {
      "question": "牡蠣",
      "answer": "かき,ぼれい",
      "meaning": "oyster, oyster shell"
    },
    {
      "question": "水質",
      "answer": "すいしつ",
      "meaning": "water quality"
    },
    {
      "question": "膀胱",
      "answer": "ぼうこう",
      "meaning": "urinary bladder"
    },
    {
      "question": "閉塞",
      "answer": "へいそく",
      "meaning": "blockage, blockade, blocking up, stoppage, obstruction, occlusion"
    },
    {
      "question": "賞味",
      "answer": "しょうみ",
      "meaning": "relish, gusto, appreciation"
    },
    {
      "question": "籐",
      "answer": "とう",
      "meaning": "rattan, (rattan) cane (e.g. used in wicker furniture)"
    },
    {
      "question": "親権",
      "answer": "しんけん",
      "meaning": "parental authority"
    },
    {
      "question": "件名",
      "answer": "けんめい",
      "meaning": "subject, title, subject (of an email), subject line"
    },
    {
      "question": "特異体質",
      "answer": "とくいたいしつ",
      "meaning": "idiosyncrasy"
    },
    {
      "question": "ポン酢",
      "answer": "ポンず",
      "meaning": "juice pressed from a bitter orange, ponzu (Japanese sauce made primarily of soy sauce and citrus jui"
    },
    {
      "question": "版図",
      "answer": "はんと",
      "meaning": "territory"
    },
    {
      "question": "時勢",
      "answer": "じせい",
      "meaning": "spirit of the age, trends, conditions"
    },
    {
      "question": "本流",
      "answer": "ほんりゅう",
      "meaning": "main course (of a river), mainstream, main current (e.g. of thought)"
    },
    {
      "question": "配色",
      "answer": "はいしょく",
      "meaning": "color scheme, colour scheme"
    },
    {
      "question": "眸",
      "answer": "ひとみ",
      "meaning": "pupil (of eye), eye"
    },
    {
      "question": "福島",
      "answer": "ふくしま",
      "meaning": "Fukushima (city, prefecture)"
    },
    {
      "question": "レジ袋",
      "answer": "レジぶくろ",
      "meaning": "(disposable) shopping bag, carrier bag"
    },
    {
      "question": "入り江",
      "answer": "いりえ",
      "meaning": "inlet, cove, creek, bay"
    },
    {
      "question": "辛み",
      "answer": "からみ,つらみ",
      "meaning": "hot taste, sharp taste, pungent taste, salty taste, pent-up resentment, grudges and hard feelings"
    },
    {
      "question": "流産",
      "answer": "りゅうざん",
      "meaning": "miscarriage, (spontaneous) abortion, abortive birth"
    },
    {
      "question": "荒縄",
      "answer": "あらなわ",
      "meaning": "straw rope"
    },
    {
      "question": "鎮静剤",
      "answer": "ちんせいざい",
      "meaning": "sedative, tranquilizer, tranquiliser"
    },
    {
      "question": "帰国子女",
      "answer": "きこくしじょ",
      "meaning": "child who has returned to Japan after living abroad, returnee child, (Japanese) person who lived abr"
    },
    {
      "question": "仄めかす",
      "answer": "ほのめかす",
      "meaning": "to hint at, to intimate, to suggest, to allude to, to imply"
    },
    {
      "question": "小骨",
      "answer": "こぼね",
      "meaning": "small bones"
    },
    {
      "question": "持て囃す",
      "answer": "もてはやす",
      "meaning": "to praise extravagantly, to lionize, to lionise, to make much of"
    },
    {
      "question": "和音",
      "answer": "わおん",
      "meaning": "chord, 'on' reading of a kanji"
    },
    {
      "question": "廃校",
      "answer": "はいこう",
      "meaning": "closing of a school, closed school"
    },
    {
      "question": "前作",
      "answer": "ぜんさく,まえさく",
      "meaning": "previous work, preceding work, first crop grown in a double-cropped field, preceding crop"
    },
    {
      "question": "相乗り",
      "answer": "あいのり",
      "meaning": "riding together, sharing a car (taxi, etc.), doing in collaboration, backing of the same candidate b"
    },
    {
      "question": "栄養失調",
      "answer": "えいようしっちょう",
      "meaning": "malnutrition"
    },
    {
      "question": "屍体",
      "answer": "したい",
      "meaning": "dead body, corpse, cadaver, carcass"
    },
    {
      "question": "古式",
      "answer": "こしき",
      "meaning": "old style, ancient rites"
    },
    {
      "question": "天晴れ",
      "answer": "あっぱれ",
      "meaning": "splendid, praiseworthy, admirable, brilliant, well done!, bravo!"
    },
    {
      "question": "招聘",
      "answer": "しょうへい",
      "meaning": "(courteous) invitation, call"
    },
    {
      "question": "天寿",
      "answer": "てんじゅ",
      "meaning": "natural span of life, 250 years old"
    },
    {
      "question": "家庭訪問",
      "answer": "かていほうもん",
      "meaning": "home visitation (esp. a teacher visiting a student's home), home visit, house call"
    },
    {
      "question": "上掛け",
      "answer": "うわがけ,うわかけ",
      "meaning": "quilt, bedspread, bedcover, cover (for a kotatsu quilt), cloak, smock, second dyeing, topping, overl"
    },
    {
      "question": "雪道",
      "answer": "ゆきみち",
      "meaning": "snow-covered road"
    },
    {
      "question": "飲",
      "answer": "いん",
      "meaning": "drinking (sometimes esp. alcohol), drink, drinking party"
    },
    {
      "question": "頭身",
      "answer": "とうしん",
      "meaning": "head and body, heads tall (ratio of total height to length of the head), heads long"
    },
    {
      "question": "承服",
      "answer": "しょうふく",
      "meaning": "accepting, consenting, agreeing, submission, compliance, agreement, consent"
    },
    {
      "question": "園遊会",
      "answer": "えんゆうかい",
      "meaning": "garden party"
    },
    {
      "question": "幽か",
      "answer": "かすか",
      "meaning": "faint, dim, weak, slight, vague, indistinct, hazy, poor, wretched, meagre, meager, scanty"
    },
    {
      "question": "集金",
      "answer": "しゅうきん",
      "meaning": "money collection"
    },
    {
      "question": "単品",
      "answer": "たんぴん",
      "meaning": "individual item (i.e. not part of a set), single article, single item out of a set, one item from a"
    },
    {
      "question": "不幸せ",
      "answer": "ふしあわせ",
      "meaning": "unhappiness, misfortune, ill luck"
    },
    {
      "question": "両人",
      "answer": "りょうにん",
      "meaning": "both people"
    },
    {
      "question": "男性的",
      "answer": "だんせいてき",
      "meaning": "manly"
    },
    {
      "question": "疑い深い",
      "answer": "うたがいぶかい",
      "meaning": "doubting, distrustful, incredulous, suspicious"
    },
    {
      "question": "瀑布",
      "answer": "ばくふ",
      "meaning": "waterfall, cataract, cascade"
    },
    {
      "question": "離島",
      "answer": "りとう",
      "meaning": "isolated island, outlying island, leaving an island"
    },
    {
      "question": "誘致",
      "answer": "ゆうち",
      "meaning": "attraction, lure, invitation"
    },
    {
      "question": "作画",
      "answer": "さくが",
      "meaning": "drawing pictures, painting pictures, taking photographs"
    },
    {
      "question": "巨石",
      "answer": "きょせき",
      "meaning": "gigantic stone, megalith"
    },
    {
      "question": "盆踊り",
      "answer": "ぼんおどり",
      "meaning": "Bon Festival dance, Lantern Festival dance"
    },
    {
      "question": "胃腸",
      "answer": "いちょう",
      "meaning": "stomach and intestines, gastrointestinal tract, digestive organs"
    },
    {
      "question": "美醜",
      "answer": "びしゅう",
      "meaning": "beauty or ugliness, personal appearance, looks"
    },
    {
      "question": "晴れ間",
      "answer": "はれま",
      "meaning": "break (in the weather, esp. rain or snow), interval of clear weather, patch of blue sky, period of s"
    },
    {
      "question": "取り込み",
      "answer": "とりこみ",
      "meaning": "taking in, bringing in, capturing (e.g. customers), attracting, winning over, pleasing, confusion, b"
    },
    {
      "question": "写真家",
      "answer": "しゃしんか",
      "meaning": "photographer"
    },
    {
      "question": "骨董",
      "answer": "こっとう",
      "meaning": "antique, curio"
    },
    {
      "question": "無常",
      "answer": "むじょう",
      "meaning": "uncertainty, transiency, impermanence, mutability"
    },
    {
      "question": "赤ら顔",
      "answer": "あからがお",
      "meaning": "red face"
    },
    {
      "question": "内出血",
      "answer": "ないしゅっけつ",
      "meaning": "internal bleeding, internal haemorrhage, internal hemorrhage"
    },
    {
      "question": "宮城",
      "answer": "きゅうじょう,みやぎ",
      "meaning": "Imperial Palace (esp. from 1888 to 1946), Miyagi (prefecture)"
    },
    {
      "question": "悍ましい",
      "answer": "おぞましい",
      "meaning": "disgusting, repulsive"
    },
    {
      "question": "抜剣",
      "answer": "ばっけん",
      "meaning": "drawing one's sword"
    },
    {
      "question": "生ハム",
      "answer": "なまハム",
      "meaning": "dry-cured ham"
    },
    {
      "question": "音読",
      "answer": "おんどく",
      "meaning": "reading aloud, reading a kanji by its Chinese-derived pronunciation"
    },
    {
      "question": "妖狐",
      "answer": "ようこ",
      "meaning": "mythological fox spirit"
    },
    {
      "question": "種付け",
      "answer": "たねつけ",
      "meaning": "mating"
    },
    {
      "question": "考査",
      "answer": "こうさ",
      "meaning": "examination, consideration, test, quiz"
    },
    {
      "question": "頑健",
      "answer": "がんけん",
      "meaning": "robust health, able-bodied"
    },
    {
      "question": "敷設",
      "answer": "ふせつ",
      "meaning": "laying (a railroad, pipes, naval mines, etc.), construction"
    },
    {
      "question": "姦しい",
      "answer": "かしましい",
      "meaning": "noisy, boisterous"
    },
    {
      "question": "散髪",
      "answer": "さんぱつ",
      "meaning": "(having a) haircut, hair-cutting, hair-dressing"
    },
    {
      "question": "草の根",
      "answer": "くさのね",
      "meaning": "roots of grass, places hidden from sight, grassroots (e.g. of a political party), rank and file"
    },
    {
      "question": "臨終",
      "answer": "りんじゅう",
      "meaning": "deathbed, dying hour, one's death"
    },
    {
      "question": "違約金",
      "answer": "いやくきん",
      "meaning": "penalty for contract breach"
    },
    {
      "question": "忌む",
      "answer": "いむ",
      "meaning": "to avoid, to refrain from, to shun, to detest"
    },
    {
      "question": "胃痛",
      "answer": "いつう",
      "meaning": "stomach-ache, stomach pain, gastralgia"
    },
    {
      "question": "長刀",
      "answer": "なぎなた,ちょうとう",
      "meaning": "naginata, polearm with a curved single-edged blade (similar to a glaive), martial art of wielding th"
    },
    {
      "question": "合い言葉",
      "answer": "あいことば",
      "meaning": "password, watchword, motto, slogan"
    },
    {
      "question": "赤紫",
      "answer": "あかむらさき",
      "meaning": "purplish red"
    },
    {
      "question": "辣腕",
      "answer": "らつわん",
      "meaning": "shrewdness, sharpness, astuteness, acumen, tact"
    },
    {
      "question": "教練",
      "answer": "きょうれん",
      "meaning": "drill"
    },
    {
      "question": "禅",
      "answer": "ぜん",
      "meaning": "dhyana (profound meditation), Zen (Buddhism)"
    },
    {
      "question": "下男",
      "answer": "げなん",
      "meaning": "manservant"
    },
    {
      "question": "燃え立つ",
      "answer": "もえたつ",
      "meaning": "to blaze up, to burn up"
    },
    {
      "question": "沿道",
      "answer": "えんどう",
      "meaning": "roadside, wayside, route"
    },
    {
      "question": "陣痛",
      "answer": "じんつう",
      "meaning": "labour pains, labor pains, birth pains, contractions"
    },
    {
      "question": "政治力",
      "answer": "せいじりょく",
      "meaning": "political strength"
    },
    {
      "question": "水増し",
      "answer": "みずまし",
      "meaning": "dilution, watering down, inflation (of budget, claim, etc.), padding"
    },
    {
      "question": "商品化",
      "answer": "しょうひんか",
      "meaning": "commercialization (e.g. product), commodification"
    },
    {
      "question": "美辞麗句",
      "answer": "びじれいく",
      "meaning": "flowery words, rhetorical flourishes"
    },
    {
      "question": "情け容赦",
      "answer": "なさけようしゃ",
      "meaning": "mercy"
    },
    {
      "question": "係留",
      "answer": "けいりゅう",
      "meaning": "mooring, anchorage"
    },
    {
      "question": "希代",
      "answer": "きたい,きだい",
      "meaning": "uncommon, rare, extraordinary, matchless"
    },
    {
      "question": "掌中",
      "answer": "しょうちゅう",
      "meaning": "in the hand, (something) easily manipulated"
    },
    {
      "question": "面立ち",
      "answer": "おもだち",
      "meaning": "features"
    },
    {
      "question": "脱水症状",
      "answer": "だっすいしょうじょう",
      "meaning": "dehydration"
    },
    {
      "question": "陶芸",
      "answer": "とうげい",
      "meaning": "ceramic art, ceramics"
    },
    {
      "question": "世界遺産",
      "answer": "せかいいさん",
      "meaning": "World Heritage (cultural, natural, etc.), World Cultural and Natural Heritage (UNESCO)"
    },
    {
      "question": "発作的",
      "answer": "ほっさてき",
      "meaning": "spasmodic(ally), fitful"
    },
    {
      "question": "風呂屋",
      "answer": "ふろや",
      "meaning": "public bathhouse, bathhouse proprietor"
    },
    {
      "question": "細道",
      "answer": "ほそみち",
      "meaning": "narrow path, narrow lane"
    },
    {
      "question": "菩薩",
      "answer": "ぼさつ,ぼさち",
      "meaning": "bodhisattva, one who has reached enlightenment but vows to save all beings before becoming a buddha,"
    },
    {
      "question": "襤褸",
      "answer": "ぼろ,らんる",
      "meaning": "rag, scrap, tattered clothes, fault (esp. in a pretense, pretence), defect, run-down, shabby, junky"
    },
    {
      "question": "武者修行",
      "answer": "むしゃしゅぎょう",
      "meaning": "traveling about to gain skill in combat (travelling)"
    },
    {
      "question": "銀縁",
      "answer": "ぎんぶち",
      "meaning": "silver-rimmed"
    },
    {
      "question": "固形物",
      "answer": "こけいぶつ",
      "meaning": "solid (body), solid matter, solid food"
    },
    {
      "question": "職業病",
      "answer": "しょくぎょうびょう",
      "meaning": "occupational disease"
    },
    {
      "question": "双六",
      "answer": "すごろく,すぐろく",
      "meaning": "sugoroku, traditional Japanese board game played with dice"
    },
    {
      "question": "子機",
      "answer": "こき",
      "meaning": "(telephone) extension, additional telephone handset, portable handset, cordless telephone"
    },
    {
      "question": "言の葉",
      "answer": "ことのは,ことのえ",
      "meaning": "word, waka (classic Japanese poem, esp. a tanka)"
    },
    {
      "question": "厠",
      "answer": "かわや",
      "meaning": "privy, toilet"
    },
    {
      "question": "大御所",
      "answer": "おおごしょ",
      "meaning": "leading figure, influential figure, mogul"
    },
    {
      "question": "露天商",
      "answer": "ろてんしょう",
      "meaning": "street vendor, stallholder, stallkeeper"
    },
    {
      "question": "潮流",
      "answer": "ちょうりゅう",
      "meaning": "tide, tidal current, tendency, drift, trend"
    },
    {
      "question": "四足",
      "answer": "しそく",
      "meaning": "four legs, four-legged, quadruped"
    },
    {
      "question": "車外",
      "answer": "しゃがい",
      "meaning": "outside a car (train, bus, etc.)"
    },
    {
      "question": "電飾",
      "answer": "でんしょく",
      "meaning": "decorative lights, illumination"
    },
    {
      "question": "背後関係",
      "answer": "はいごかんけい",
      "meaning": "background (of a case, incident, etc.)"
    },
    {
      "question": "獅子奮迅",
      "answer": "ししふんじん",
      "meaning": "being irresistible, being furiously vigorous, being intensely forceful"
    },
    {
      "question": "大目玉",
      "answer": "おおめだま",
      "meaning": "good scolding"
    },
    {
      "question": "公方",
      "answer": "くぼう",
      "meaning": "public affairs, the court, the shogun, the shogunate"
    },
    {
      "question": "絶技",
      "answer": "ぜつぎ",
      "meaning": "special move (e.g. in martial arts)"
    },
    {
      "question": "顔馴染み",
      "answer": "かおなじみ",
      "meaning": "acquaintance, friend, familiar face"
    },
    {
      "question": "道々",
      "answer": "みちみち",
      "meaning": "along the way, along the road"
    },
    {
      "question": "自己弁護",
      "answer": "じこべんご",
      "meaning": "self-justification, excuse"
    },
    {
      "question": "蜜柑",
      "answer": "みかん",
      "meaning": "mandarin (esp. the satsuma mandarin (Citrus unshiu)), mandarin orange, tangerine, clementine, satsum"
    },
    {
      "question": "社会性",
      "answer": "しゃかいせい",
      "meaning": "sociality"
    },
    {
      "question": "神国",
      "answer": "しんこく",
      "meaning": "land of the gods, Japan"
    },
    {
      "question": "電信",
      "answer": "でんしん",
      "meaning": "telegraph"
    },
    {
      "question": "遇する",
      "answer": "ぐうする",
      "meaning": "to entertain, to treat"
    },
    {
      "question": "賢しい",
      "answer": "さかしい",
      "meaning": "intelligent, wise, sagacious, clever, smart-alecky, cheeky"
    },
    {
      "question": "湿気る",
      "answer": "しける,しっける",
      "meaning": "to be damp, to be moist"
    },
    {
      "question": "生え際",
      "answer": "はえぎわ",
      "meaning": "hairline, borders of the hair"
    },
    {
      "question": "心行く",
      "answer": "こころゆく",
      "meaning": "to be completely satisfied, to be completely contented"
    },
    {
      "question": "綻びる",
      "answer": "ほころびる",
      "meaning": "to come apart at the seams, to be ripped, to be torn, to begin to open, to begin to bloom, to smile"
    },
    {
      "question": "目黒",
      "answer": "めぐろ",
      "meaning": "Bonin white-eye (Apalopteron familiare)"
    },
    {
      "question": "狂信",
      "answer": "きょうしん",
      "meaning": "fanaticism, zealotry, blind devotion"
    },
    {
      "question": "指揮棒",
      "answer": "しきぼう",
      "meaning": "conductor's stick, conductor's baton"
    },
    {
      "question": "半死半生",
      "answer": "はんしはんしょう",
      "meaning": "all but dead, half killed"
    },
    {
      "question": "逮捕状",
      "answer": "たいほじょう",
      "meaning": "arrest warrant"
    },
    {
      "question": "明暗",
      "answer": "めいあん",
      "meaning": "light and darkness, light and shade"
    },
    {
      "question": "硯",
      "answer": "すずり",
      "meaning": "inkstone"
    },
    {
      "question": "小姓",
      "answer": "こしょう",
      "meaning": "(noble's) page"
    },
    {
      "question": "獣欲",
      "answer": "じゅうよく",
      "meaning": "animal or carnal desires, lust"
    },
    {
      "question": "毛深い",
      "answer": "けぶかい",
      "meaning": "hairy, thickly haired, shaggy"
    },
    {
      "question": "坩堝",
      "answer": "るつぼ,かんか",
      "meaning": "crucible, melting pot, melting pot (of cultures, ideas, etc.), state of ecstasy, state of fevered ex"
    },
    {
      "question": "漁夫の利",
      "answer": "ぎょふのり,ぎょほのり",
      "meaning": "profiting while others fight"
    },
    {
      "question": "私刑",
      "answer": "しけい",
      "meaning": "punishment without a legal trial, vigilantism"
    },
    {
      "question": "過不足",
      "answer": "かふそく,かぶそく",
      "meaning": "excess or deficiency, too much or too little"
    },
    {
      "question": "象牙",
      "answer": "ぞうげ",
      "meaning": "ivory"
    },
    {
      "question": "凹み",
      "answer": "くぼみ,へこみ",
      "meaning": "hollow, cavity, dent, depression"
    },
    {
      "question": "介錯",
      "answer": "かいしゃく",
      "meaning": "beheading (as the ending to a seppuku), assistance, help"
    },
    {
      "question": "対馬",
      "answer": "たいま,つしま",
      "meaning": "playing on equal terms, having no handicap for either player, being evenly matched, Tsushima (former"
    },
    {
      "question": "穴を穿つ",
      "answer": "あなをうがつ",
      "meaning": "to find somebody's weak spot, to drill a hole"
    },
    {
      "question": "発病",
      "answer": "はつびょう",
      "meaning": "attack (disease)"
    },
    {
      "question": "所行",
      "answer": "しょぎょう",
      "meaning": "deed, act"
    },
    {
      "question": "陽動作戦",
      "answer": "ようどうさくせん",
      "meaning": "diversionary tactics"
    },
    {
      "question": "中流",
      "answer": "ちゅうりゅう,ちゅうる",
      "meaning": "mid-stream, middle course, middle class, banishment (to a somewhat distant province), middle-degree"
    },
    {
      "question": "伸び悩む",
      "answer": "のびなやむ",
      "meaning": "to be sluggish (business), to make little progress, to not grow as much as expected"
    },
    {
      "question": "東海",
      "answer": "とうかい",
      "meaning": "region south of Tokyo on Pacific Ocean side of Japan, eastern sea, East Sea (Korean name for Sea of"
    },
    {
      "question": "元旦",
      "answer": "がんたん",
      "meaning": "New Year's Day, New Year's morning, morning of New Year's Day"
    },
    {
      "question": "下策",
      "answer": "げさく",
      "meaning": "poor plan"
    },
    {
      "question": "一端",
      "answer": "いったん,いっぱし",
      "meaning": "one end, an end, part, fragment, fully fledged, full-fledged, proper, competent, qualified, full-gro"
    },
    {
      "question": "長編",
      "answer": "ちょうへん",
      "meaning": "long (e.g. novel, film)"
    },
    {
      "question": "腹積もり",
      "answer": "はらづもり",
      "meaning": "plan, intention"
    },
    {
      "question": "防空",
      "answer": "ぼうくう",
      "meaning": "air defense, air defence"
    },
    {
      "question": "共通語",
      "answer": "きょうつうご",
      "meaning": "common language, lingua franca, standard language (language variety understood throughout a country)"
    },
    {
      "question": "肉団子",
      "answer": "にくだんご",
      "meaning": "meatball"
    },
    {
      "question": "四つ足",
      "answer": "よつあし",
      "meaning": "four-footed (animal)"
    },
    {
      "question": "洒落込む",
      "answer": "しゃれこむ",
      "meaning": "to get dressed up, to treat oneself"
    },
    {
      "question": "痴情",
      "answer": "ちじょう",
      "meaning": "being struck mad by love, foolish passion, blind love, infatuation, jealousy"
    },
    {
      "question": "経典",
      "answer": "きょうてん,けいてん",
      "meaning": "sacred books, sutras, scriptures, Bible"
    },
    {
      "question": "光彩",
      "answer": "こうさい",
      "meaning": "brilliance, splendour, splendor, lustre, luster"
    },
    {
      "question": "先駆ける",
      "answer": "さきがける",
      "meaning": "to be the first"
    },
    {
      "question": "慎み深い",
      "answer": "つつしみぶかい",
      "meaning": "discreet, modest, cautious"
    },
    {
      "question": "長門",
      "answer": "ながと",
      "meaning": "Nagato (former province located in the west of present-day Yamaguchi Prefecture)"
    },
    {
      "question": "風聞",
      "answer": "ふうぶん",
      "meaning": "rumour, rumor, hearsay, report"
    },
    {
      "question": "耳掃除",
      "answer": "みみそうじ",
      "meaning": "ear cleaning, cleaning one's ears"
    },
    {
      "question": "亡国",
      "answer": "ぼうこく",
      "meaning": "ruined country"
    },
    {
      "question": "薬味",
      "answer": "やくみ",
      "meaning": "condiment (e.g. grated or chopped topping such as daikon, wasabi, ginger, green onion, red pepper),"
    },
    {
      "question": "好事家",
      "answer": "こうずか",
      "meaning": "dilettante, person of fantastic taste"
    },
    {
      "question": "次点",
      "answer": "じてん",
      "meaning": "runner-up"
    },
    {
      "question": "公算",
      "answer": "こうさん",
      "meaning": "probability, likelihood"
    },
    {
      "question": "食い潰す",
      "answer": "くいつぶす",
      "meaning": "to eat oneself out of house and home, to eat up completely"
    },
    {
      "question": "贅沢品",
      "answer": "ぜいたくひん",
      "meaning": "luxury item"
    },
    {
      "question": "片が付く",
      "answer": "かたがつく",
      "meaning": "to settle (a problem), to put an end to (a dispute), to be disposed of, to be settled, to come to an"
    },
    {
      "question": "開拓者",
      "answer": "かいたくしゃ",
      "meaning": "pioneer, settler, colonist"
    },
    {
      "question": "参じる",
      "answer": "さんじる",
      "meaning": "to come, to go, to participate, to perform Zen meditation"
    },
    {
      "question": "手汗",
      "answer": "てあせ",
      "meaning": "palm sweat"
    },
    {
      "question": "出っ張り",
      "answer": "でっぱり",
      "meaning": "projection, protrusion, lump, bulge"
    },
    {
      "question": "用法",
      "answer": "ようほう",
      "meaning": "directions, rules of use"
    },
    {
      "question": "計算違い",
      "answer": "けいさんちがい",
      "meaning": "miscalculation"
    },
    {
      "question": "乳頭",
      "answer": "にゅうとう",
      "meaning": "(mammary) nipple, teat"
    },
    {
      "question": "純金",
      "answer": "じゅんきん",
      "meaning": "pure gold, solid gold, fine gold"
    },
    {
      "question": "半ズボン",
      "answer": "はんズボン",
      "meaning": "short pants, shorts, breeches, knickerbockers"
    },
    {
      "question": "水商売",
      "answer": "みずしょうばい",
      "meaning": "chancy trade or business with uncertain profitability, night entertainment business (e.g. hostess ba"
    },
    {
      "question": "憲法",
      "answer": "けんぽう,けんぼう",
      "meaning": "constitution, rules, regulation"
    },
    {
      "question": "請け合う",
      "answer": "うけあう",
      "meaning": "to undertake, to take on (task), to assure, to guarantee, to vouch (for), to promise"
    },
    {
      "question": "始末書",
      "answer": "しまつしょ",
      "meaning": "written explanation, written apology"
    },
    {
      "question": "無理ゲー",
      "answer": "むりゲー",
      "meaning": "impossibly hard video game"
    },
    {
      "question": "諏訪",
      "answer": "",
      "meaning": ""
    },
    {
      "question": "信管",
      "answer": "しんかん",
      "meaning": "fuse"
    },
    {
      "question": "眠り薬",
      "answer": "ねむりぐすり",
      "meaning": "sleeping powder, sleeping drug, narcotic, anaesthetic, anesthetic"
    },
    {
      "question": "指数",
      "answer": "しすう",
      "meaning": "index, index number, exponent (e.g. in floating-point representation), characteristic"
    },
    {
      "question": "理詰め",
      "answer": "りづめ",
      "meaning": "reasoning, logic, persuasion"
    },
    {
      "question": "消化不良",
      "answer": "しょうかふりょう",
      "meaning": "indigestion, dyspepsia, incomprehensibility, inability to understand"
    },
    {
      "question": "押し合う",
      "answer": "おしあう",
      "meaning": "to jostle, to crowd, to haggle"
    },
    {
      "question": "兵長",
      "answer": "へいちょう",
      "meaning": "leading private, leading seaman, former rank in the Japanese army and navy"
    },
    {
      "question": "揺すぶる",
      "answer": "ゆすぶる",
      "meaning": "to shake, to jolt, to rock, to swing"
    },
    {
      "question": "落石",
      "answer": "らくせき",
      "meaning": "falling rocks, fallen rocks"
    },
    {
      "question": "右折",
      "answer": "うせつ",
      "meaning": "turning to the right, right turn"
    },
    {
      "question": "恒久的",
      "answer": "こうきゅうてき",
      "meaning": "permanent, perpetual, lasting"
    },
    {
      "question": "風下",
      "answer": "かざしも",
      "meaning": "leeward, lee, downwind"
    },
    {
      "question": "積層",
      "answer": "せきそう",
      "meaning": "laminating, lamination layer"
    },
    {
      "question": "転載",
      "answer": "てんさい",
      "meaning": "reprinting, reproduction"
    },
    {
      "question": "昇級",
      "answer": "しょうきゅう",
      "meaning": "promotion, advancement"
    },
    {
      "question": "公式戦",
      "answer": "こうしきせん",
      "meaning": "regular game, regular-season game"
    },
    {
      "question": "角材",
      "answer": "かくざい",
      "meaning": "squared timber, rectangular lumber"
    },
    {
      "question": "自傷",
      "answer": "じしょう",
      "meaning": "self-mutilation, self-injury"
    },
    {
      "question": "上顎",
      "answer": "うわあご,じょうがく",
      "meaning": "upper jaw, palate"
    },
    {
      "question": "筆談",
      "answer": "ひつだん",
      "meaning": "communicating in writing"
    },
    {
      "question": "捨て鉢",
      "answer": "すてばち",
      "meaning": "desperation"
    },
    {
      "question": "科す",
      "answer": "かす",
      "meaning": "to inflict, to impose (a fine, etc.)"
    },
    {
      "question": "前時代的",
      "answer": "ぜんじだいてき",
      "meaning": "premodern, old-fashioned, outmoded, antiquated"
    },
    {
      "question": "霊界",
      "answer": "れいかい",
      "meaning": "the spiritual world"
    },
    {
      "question": "占",
      "answer": "うら",
      "meaning": "fortune-telling, divination"
    },
    {
      "question": "魔改造",
      "answer": "まかいぞう",
      "meaning": "extreme modification (esp. of cars or toy figurines)"
    },
    {
      "question": "白皙",
      "answer": "はくせき",
      "meaning": "white"
    },
    {
      "question": "無頼",
      "answer": "ごろつき,ぶらい,むらい",
      "meaning": "rogue, thug, hoodlum, punk, racketeer, villainous, rascally, knavish, independent, self-reliant"
    },
    {
      "question": "唯我独尊",
      "answer": "ゆいがどくそん",
      "meaning": "self-conceit, self-centeredness, vainglory"
    },
    {
      "question": "幕を引く",
      "answer": "まくをひく",
      "meaning": "to draw closed the curtain (of a theatre, etc.), to come to an end"
    },
    {
      "question": "廃る",
      "answer": "すたる",
      "meaning": "to go out of use, to become obsolete, to die out, to go out of fashion, to become lost (e.g. of dign"
    },
    {
      "question": "下落",
      "answer": "げらく",
      "meaning": "depreciation, decline, fall, slump"
    },
    {
      "question": "霧雨",
      "answer": "きりさめ",
      "meaning": "drizzle, light rain"
    },
    {
      "question": "待合",
      "answer": "まちあい",
      "meaning": "rendezvous, meeting, assignation, area where guests gather before the start of a tea ceremony, waiti"
    },
    {
      "question": "痩身",
      "answer": "そうしん",
      "meaning": "slim figure, lean figure, weight reduction"
    },
    {
      "question": "判子",
      "answer": "はんこ",
      "meaning": "seal (used in lieu of a signature), stamp, chop"
    },
    {
      "question": "門外漢",
      "answer": "もんがいかん",
      "meaning": "outsider, layman, amateur"
    },
    {
      "question": "低姿勢",
      "answer": "ていしせい",
      "meaning": "(keeping a) low profile"
    },
    {
      "question": "洗い直す",
      "answer": "あらいなおす",
      "meaning": "to wash again, to reconsider"
    },
    {
      "question": "心眼",
      "answer": "しんがん",
      "meaning": "the mind's eye"
    },
    {
      "question": "色分け",
      "answer": "いろわけ",
      "meaning": "classification, color coding, colour coding, color keying, colour keying, differentiation using diff"
    },
    {
      "question": "合気道",
      "answer": "あいきどう",
      "meaning": "aikido"
    },
    {
      "question": "改正",
      "answer": "かいせい",
      "meaning": "revision, amendment, alteration"
    },
    {
      "question": "転び",
      "answer": "ころび",
      "meaning": "falling (down), tumbling (down), falling to the ground, failure, failing, renouncing Christianity an"
    },
    {
      "question": "我が方",
      "answer": "わがほう",
      "meaning": "our side, we"
    },
    {
      "question": "高波",
      "answer": "たかなみ",
      "meaning": "high waves, heavy seas"
    },
    {
      "question": "識",
      "answer": "しき",
      "meaning": "acquaintanceship, vijnana, consciousness, written by..."
    },
    {
      "question": "神格化",
      "answer": "しんかくか",
      "meaning": "deification"
    },
    {
      "question": "耳が遠い",
      "answer": "みみがとおい",
      "meaning": "poor hearing"
    },
    {
      "question": "肢",
      "answer": "あし",
      "meaning": "foot, paw, arm (of an octopus, squid, etc.), leg, gait, pace, bottom structural component (i.e. radi"
    },
    {
      "question": "療法",
      "answer": "りょうほう",
      "meaning": "therapy, treatment, remedy, cure"
    },
    {
      "question": "細面",
      "answer": "ほそおもて",
      "meaning": "slender face"
    },
    {
      "question": "資金力",
      "answer": "しきんりょく",
      "meaning": "financial muscle, economic clout"
    },
    {
      "question": "才気",
      "answer": "さいき",
      "meaning": "wisdom"
    },
    {
      "question": "光芒",
      "answer": "こうぼう",
      "meaning": "beam of light"
    },
    {
      "question": "四阿",
      "answer": "あずまや",
      "meaning": "arbor, arbour, bower, summer house, square gazebo"
    },
    {
      "question": "黙示録",
      "answer": "もくしろく",
      "meaning": "Revelation (book of the Bible), the Apocalypse"
    },
    {
      "question": "品薄",
      "answer": "しなうす",
      "meaning": "shortage of stock, scarcity of goods"
    },
    {
      "question": "愛の巣",
      "answer": "あいのす",
      "meaning": "love nest"
    },
    {
      "question": "場慣れ",
      "answer": "ばなれ",
      "meaning": "experience, being accustomed (to something), poise in a critical situation"
    },
    {
      "question": "若頭",
      "answer": "わかがしら",
      "meaning": "leader of a crime syndicate's henchmen, young leading subordinate in yakuza group"
    },
    {
      "question": "天神",
      "answer": "てんじん",
      "meaning": "heavenly god, heavenly gods, spirit of Sugawara no Michizane, Tenmangu shrine (dedicated to Michizan"
    },
    {
      "question": "合い鍵",
      "answer": "あいかぎ",
      "meaning": "duplicate key, pass key, master key, skeleton key"
    },
    {
      "question": "情報誌",
      "answer": "じょうほうし",
      "meaning": "listings magazine, information magazine"
    },
    {
      "question": "任ずる",
      "answer": "にんずる",
      "meaning": "to appoint, to nominate, to assume (responsibility), to pose as"
    },
    {
      "question": "花道",
      "answer": "はなみち,かどう",
      "meaning": "elevated walkway through the audience to the stage (kabuki), honourable end to a career, flower arra"
    },
    {
      "question": "毎食",
      "answer": "まいしょく",
      "meaning": "every meal"
    },
    {
      "question": "能書き",
      "answer": "のうがき",
      "meaning": "advertising the excellence of one's wares, boasting, self-advertisement, statement of the virtues of"
    },
    {
      "question": "呪わしい",
      "answer": "のろわしい",
      "meaning": "hateful, accursed"
    },
    {
      "question": "脱税",
      "answer": "だつぜい",
      "meaning": "tax evasion"
    },
    {
      "question": "沈殿",
      "answer": "ちんでん",
      "meaning": "precipitation, deposition, settlement (e.g. of sediment)"
    },
    {
      "question": "腹立ち",
      "answer": "はらだち",
      "meaning": "anger"
    },
    {
      "question": "薫",
      "answer": "かおり,くん",
      "meaning": "aroma, fragrance, scent, smell, pleasant smell, pleasant-smelling vegetation"
    },
    {
      "question": "雨戸",
      "answer": "あまど",
      "meaning": "sliding storm shutter"
    },
    {
      "question": "揉み手",
      "answer": "もみで",
      "meaning": "rubbing one's hands together"
    },
    {
      "question": "空前",
      "answer": "くうぜん",
      "meaning": "unprecedented, record-breaking"
    },
    {
      "question": "特異性",
      "answer": "とくいせい",
      "meaning": "singularity, peculiarity, idiosyncrasy, specificity"
    },
    {
      "question": "霊廟",
      "answer": "れいびょう",
      "meaning": "mausoleum"
    },
    {
      "question": "連絡網",
      "answer": "れんらくもう",
      "meaning": "contact network, phone tree, contact information for relevant people (in a given organization)"
    },
    {
      "question": "着服",
      "answer": "ちゃくふく,ちゃくぶく,ちゃくぼく",
      "meaning": "dressing oneself, putting on clothes, embezzlement"
    },
    {
      "question": "旅籠",
      "answer": "はたご",
      "meaning": "inn, tavern, hatago, Edo period lodging for travellers, basket used by travellers to carry food and"
    },
    {
      "question": "勾玉",
      "answer": "まがたま",
      "meaning": "comma-shaped jewels"
    },
    {
      "question": "打者",
      "answer": "だしゃ",
      "meaning": "batter"
    },
    {
      "question": "影法師",
      "answer": "かげぼうし",
      "meaning": "shadow figure, silhouette"
    },
    {
      "question": "金利",
      "answer": "きんり",
      "meaning": "interest rate, interest"
    },
    {
      "question": "初速",
      "answer": "しょそく",
      "meaning": "initial velocity"
    },
    {
      "question": "袈裟懸け",
      "answer": "けさがけ",
      "meaning": "wearing a kasaya, wearing an article of clothing in the same manner as a kasaya (i.e. draped over on"
    },
    {
      "question": "時刻表",
      "answer": "じこくひょう",
      "meaning": "timetable, schedule"
    },
    {
      "question": "飽くなき",
      "answer": "あくなき",
      "meaning": "insatiable, untiring, persistent"
    },
    {
      "question": "脈々",
      "answer": "みゃくみゃく",
      "meaning": "continuous, unbroken, ceaseless"
    },
    {
      "question": "煙管",
      "answer": "えんかん,キセル",
      "meaning": "kiseru, Japanese smoking pipe, fire tube (of a fire-tube boiler), chimney, (tobacco) pipe with metal"
    },
    {
      "question": "品数",
      "answer": "しなかず",
      "meaning": "variety of goods, number of articles"
    },
    {
      "question": "足軽",
      "answer": "あしがる",
      "meaning": "common foot soldier (feudal Japan), samurai of the lowest rank"
    },
    {
      "question": "商館",
      "answer": "しょうかん",
      "meaning": "firm, trading company"
    },
    {
      "question": "祖父さん",
      "answer": "じいさん",
      "meaning": "grandfather (may be used after name as honorific), male senior-citizen (may be used after name as ho"
    },
    {
      "question": "念力",
      "answer": "ねんりき",
      "meaning": "willpower, faith, telekinesis, psychokinesis"
    },
    {
      "question": "編制",
      "answer": "へんせい",
      "meaning": "organization, organisation, forming"
    },
    {
      "question": "閑話休題",
      "answer": "かんわきゅうだい",
      "meaning": "Now let's return to the main subject, To return from the digression,.. (in a conversation, speech, o"
    },
    {
      "question": "出窓",
      "answer": "でまど",
      "meaning": "bay window"
    },
    {
      "question": "吸着",
      "answer": "きゅうちゃく",
      "meaning": "adsorption, adhesion (by suction), attachment, sticking to"
    },
    {
      "question": "中心的",
      "answer": "ちゅうしんてき",
      "meaning": "central, mainline"
    },
    {
      "question": "計らう",
      "answer": "はからう",
      "meaning": "to manage, to arrange, to talk over, to dispose of"
    },
    {
      "question": "組み付く",
      "answer": "くみつく",
      "meaning": "to grapple, to wrestle"
    },
    {
      "question": "歩哨",
      "answer": "ほしょう",
      "meaning": "sentry, sentinel"
    },
    {
      "question": "大火",
      "answer": "たいか",
      "meaning": "large fire"
    },
    {
      "question": "香気",
      "answer": "こうき",
      "meaning": "fragrance"
    },
    {
      "question": "立ち退く",
      "answer": "たちのく",
      "meaning": "to leave, to evacuate, to withdraw (from), to clear out, to move out (of a house, etc.), to vacate"
    },
    {
      "question": "論議",
      "answer": "ろんぎ",
      "meaning": "discussion, argument, debate"
    },
    {
      "question": "裏目",
      "answer": "うらめ",
      "meaning": "reverse side, opposite (of the expected), purl stitch (knitting)"
    },
    {
      "question": "呂",
      "answer": "りょ",
      "meaning": "bass range (in Japanese music), six even-numbered notes of the ancient chromatic scale, Japanese sev"
    },
    {
      "question": "書房",
      "answer": "しょぼう",
      "meaning": "study, library, bookstore, bookshop, publishing company"
    },
    {
      "question": "宇宙開発",
      "answer": "うちゅうかいはつ",
      "meaning": "space development, space exploration"
    },
    {
      "question": "砥石",
      "answer": "といし",
      "meaning": "whetstone, grindstone"
    },
    {
      "question": "八百万",
      "answer": "やおよろず,はっぴゃくまん",
      "meaning": "myriad, countless things, 8,000,000, eight million"
    },
    {
      "question": "受難",
      "answer": "じゅなん",
      "meaning": "sufferings, ordeals, agony, Passion (of Christ), crucifixion"
    },
    {
      "question": "低木",
      "answer": "ていぼく",
      "meaning": "shrub, shrubbery"
    },
    {
      "question": "迷宮入り",
      "answer": "めいきゅういり",
      "meaning": "going unsolved, remaining unanswered"
    },
    {
      "question": "雁",
      "answer": "がん,かり,かりがね",
      "meaning": "wild goose, glans, head of a penis, call of a wild goose, wild goose (esp. a lesser white-fronted go"
    },
    {
      "question": "枯れ草",
      "answer": "かれくさ",
      "meaning": "dry grass, dead grass, hay, withered grass"
    },
    {
      "question": "職務質問",
      "answer": "しょくむしつもん",
      "meaning": "police questioning"
    },
    {
      "question": "酵母",
      "answer": "こうぼ",
      "meaning": "yeast, leaven"
    },
    {
      "question": "計算機",
      "answer": "けいさんき",
      "meaning": "calculator, computer"
    },
    {
      "question": "波濤",
      "answer": "はとう",
      "meaning": "surging sea, rough sea, large waves"
    },
    {
      "question": "係わる",
      "answer": "かかわる",
      "meaning": "to be affected, to be influenced, to be concerned with, to have to do with, to stick to (opinions)"
    },
    {
      "question": "受精",
      "answer": "じゅせい",
      "meaning": "fertilization, fertilisation, impregnation, pollination, insemination"
    },
    {
      "question": "福引き",
      "answer": "ふくびき",
      "meaning": "lottery, tombola, drawing"
    },
    {
      "question": "新鋭",
      "answer": "しんえい",
      "meaning": "young and energetic, up-and-coming, new and excellent, newly produced, up-and-comer"
    },
    {
      "question": "三角巾",
      "answer": "さんかくきん",
      "meaning": "triangular bandage, sling, triangular kerchief, bandana, bandanna"
    },
    {
      "question": "芽を摘む",
      "answer": "めをつむ",
      "meaning": "to nip (something) in the bud"
    },
    {
      "question": "全う",
      "answer": "まっとう",
      "meaning": "proper, respectable, decent, honest, entirely, completely, wholly, perfectly"
    },
    {
      "question": "訳無い",
      "answer": "わけない",
      "meaning": "easy, simple, there's no way that ..."
    },
    {
      "question": "黄土色",
      "answer": "おうどいろ,こうどいろ",
      "meaning": "ocher (colour), ochre"
    },
    {
      "question": "絞殺",
      "answer": "こうさつ",
      "meaning": "strangulation, strangling"
    },
    {
      "question": "潤滑",
      "answer": "じゅんかつ",
      "meaning": "lubrication, smoothness"
    },
    {
      "question": "上旬",
      "answer": "じょうじゅん",
      "meaning": "first 10 days of month"
    },
    {
      "question": "薄緑",
      "answer": "うすみどり",
      "meaning": "light green"
    },
    {
      "question": "白昼",
      "answer": "はくちゅう",
      "meaning": "daytime, midday"
    },
    {
      "question": "家捜し",
      "answer": "やさがし,いえさがし",
      "meaning": "searching an entire house, house-hunting"
    },
    {
      "question": "拭い取る",
      "answer": "ぬぐいとる",
      "meaning": "to wipe off, to wipe out, to expunge"
    },
    {
      "question": "抜かる",
      "answer": "ぬかる",
      "meaning": "to make a mistake"
    },
    {
      "question": "水草",
      "answer": "みずくさ,すいそう",
      "meaning": "water plant, aquatic plant, waterweed, hydrophyte"
    },
    {
      "question": "節制",
      "answer": "せっせい",
      "meaning": "moderation, self-restraint, temperance"
    },
    {
      "question": "貰い手",
      "answer": "もらいて",
      "meaning": "receiver, recipient"
    },
    {
      "question": "潮吹き",
      "answer": "しおふき",
      "meaning": "spouting (e.g. of a whale, blowhole, etc.), blowing water, Mactra veneriformis (species of trough sh"
    },
    {
      "question": "疎開",
      "answer": "そかい",
      "meaning": "dispersal, evacuation, removal, spreading out (troops), deployment"
    },
    {
      "question": "持ち帰り",
      "answer": "もちかえり",
      "meaning": "takeout (i.e. food), take-out, takeaway, take-away"
    },
    {
      "question": "草食動物",
      "answer": "そうしょくどうぶつ",
      "meaning": "herbivore"
    },
    {
      "question": "欲をかく",
      "answer": "よくをかく",
      "meaning": "to be greedy, to covet"
    },
    {
      "question": "恋は盲目",
      "answer": "こいはもうもく",
      "meaning": "love is blind"
    },
    {
      "question": "自伝",
      "answer": "じでん",
      "meaning": "autobiography"
    },
    {
      "question": "近代化",
      "answer": "きんだいか",
      "meaning": "modernization, modernisation"
    },
    {
      "question": "寂",
      "answer": "さび,じゃく,せき",
      "meaning": "patina, antique look, elegant simplicity, well-trained voice, (entering into) nirvana, died, silent,"
    },
    {
      "question": "市中",
      "answer": "しちゅう,いちなか",
      "meaning": "in the city"
    },
    {
      "question": "上唇",
      "answer": "うわくちびる,じょうしん",
      "meaning": "upper lip, labrum"
    },
    {
      "question": "雑食",
      "answer": "ざっしょく",
      "meaning": "omnivorous"
    },
    {
      "question": "若作り",
      "answer": "わかづくり",
      "meaning": "dressing oneself up to look young, altering one's appearance to look young, dressing younger than on"
    },
    {
      "question": "天恵",
      "answer": "てんけい",
      "meaning": "Heaven's blessing, gift of nature, natural resources"
    },
    {
      "question": "吉祥",
      "answer": "きっしょう,きちじょう",
      "meaning": "lucky omen, happy, auspicious"
    },
    {
      "question": "香炉",
      "answer": "こうろ",
      "meaning": "censer, incense burner"
    },
    {
      "question": "放尿",
      "answer": "ほうにょう",
      "meaning": "urination"
    },
    {
      "question": "反攻",
      "answer": "はんこう",
      "meaning": "counteroffensive"
    },
    {
      "question": "虚脱",
      "answer": "きょだつ",
      "meaning": "lethargy, despondency, mental numbness, (physical) collapse, prostration"
    },
    {
      "question": "心霊",
      "answer": "しんれい",
      "meaning": "spirit (e.g. human spirit), soul, spirit, ghost, ethereal being"
    },
    {
      "question": "合わせ目",
      "answer": "あわせめ",
      "meaning": "joint, seam"
    },
    {
      "question": "買い漁る",
      "answer": "かいあさる",
      "meaning": "to buy all (of something) one can get one's hands on, to buy up, to scoop up"
    },
    {
      "question": "飾り物",
      "answer": "かざりもの",
      "meaning": "ornament, decoration, figurehead, leader without real power"
    },
    {
      "question": "蜜蜂",
      "answer": "みつばち,みちばち",
      "meaning": "honeybee (Apis sp.), honey bee"
    },
    {
      "question": "無明",
      "answer": "むみょう",
      "meaning": "avidya (ignorance)"
    },
    {
      "question": "板前",
      "answer": "いたまえ",
      "meaning": "chef (esp. of high-end Japanese cuisine), cook, area of a kitchen that contains the chopping board"
    },
    {
      "question": "魚釣り",
      "answer": "さかなつり,うおつり,いおつり",
      "meaning": "fishing"
    },
    {
      "question": "雑学",
      "answer": "ざつがく",
      "meaning": "miscellaneous knowledge"
    },
    {
      "question": "立て札",
      "answer": "たてふだ",
      "meaning": "bulletin board, notice board, billboard, roadside sign, sign on a post, usu. wooden, esp. containing"
    },
    {
      "question": "広告塔",
      "answer": "こうこくとう",
      "meaning": "billboard, advertising sign"
    },
    {
      "question": "縦書き",
      "answer": "たてがき",
      "meaning": "writing vertically, vertical writing"
    },
    {
      "question": "供与",
      "answer": "きょうよ",
      "meaning": "giving, provision, furnishing"
    },
    {
      "question": "扮装",
      "answer": "ふんそう",
      "meaning": "make-up, get-up, disguise, costume"
    },
    {
      "question": "其れ",
      "answer": "それ",
      "meaning": "that, it, then, that point (in time), that time, there, you"
    },
    {
      "question": "徴発",
      "answer": "ちょうはつ",
      "meaning": "requisition, commandeering, conscription"
    },
    {
      "question": "旗頭",
      "answer": "はたがしら",
      "meaning": "leader, boss, upper part of a flag, (Okinawa) bamboo poles with an attached vertical flag and an ela"
    },
    {
      "question": "縁結び",
      "answer": "えんむすび",
      "meaning": "marriage, marriage tie, love knot"
    },
    {
      "question": "弦楽器",
      "answer": "げんがっき",
      "meaning": "string instrument, stringed instrument"
    },
    {
      "question": "織り",
      "answer": "おり",
      "meaning": "weave, weaving, woven item"
    },
    {
      "question": "仕分ける",
      "answer": "しわける",
      "meaning": "to assort, to classify, to journalize (in accounting), to journalise"
    },
    {
      "question": "行き帰り",
      "answer": "ゆきかえり,いきかえり",
      "meaning": "going and returning (e.g. work, school), both ways"
    },
    {
      "question": "分室",
      "answer": "ぶんしつ",
      "meaning": "detached office, annex"
    },
    {
      "question": "練兵場",
      "answer": "れんぺいじょう",
      "meaning": "parade ground"
    },
    {
      "question": "通信網",
      "answer": "つうしんもう",
      "meaning": "communications network"
    },
    {
      "question": "羊羹",
      "answer": "ようかん",
      "meaning": "yōkan, jellied dessert made from red bean paste, agar, and sugar"
    },
    {
      "question": "中天",
      "answer": "ちゅうてん",
      "meaning": "mid-air, mid-heaven, zenith"
    },
    {
      "question": "映画化",
      "answer": "えいがか",
      "meaning": "making (book, etc.) into film, making a screen version, adapting for the screen"
    },
    {
      "question": "圧する",
      "answer": "あっする",
      "meaning": "to press, to oppress, to dominate, to overwhelm"
    },
    {
      "question": "客用",
      "answer": "きゃくよう",
      "meaning": "for use of customers or guests"
    },
    {
      "question": "原典",
      "answer": "げんてん",
      "meaning": "original (text)"
    },
    {
      "question": "獣性",
      "answer": "じゅうせい",
      "meaning": "brutality, animal nature"
    },
    {
      "question": "前掛け",
      "answer": "まえかけ",
      "meaning": "apron"
    },
    {
      "question": "輸入品",
      "answer": "ゆにゅうひん",
      "meaning": "imported goods"
    },
    {
      "question": "勤まる",
      "answer": "つとまる",
      "meaning": "to be fit for, to be equal to, to function properly"
    },
    {
      "question": "右利き",
      "answer": "みぎきき",
      "meaning": "right-handedness, right-handed person, right-hander"
    },
    {
      "question": "長柄",
      "answer": "ながえ",
      "meaning": "long handle, long-handled spear, long shaft"
    },
    {
      "question": "独りでに",
      "answer": "ひとりでに",
      "meaning": "by itself, automatically, naturally"
    },
    {
      "question": "換気扇",
      "answer": "かんきせん",
      "meaning": "ventilation fan, extractor fan"
    },
    {
      "question": "紛れ",
      "answer": "まぐれ,まぎれ",
      "meaning": "fluke, chance, pure luck, confusion, complications, being gripped by strong feelings, fit (e.g. of a"
    },
    {
      "question": "使い分け",
      "answer": "つかいわけ",
      "meaning": "proper use, using (different things) for different purposes"
    },
    {
      "question": "軍靴",
      "answer": "ぐんか",
      "meaning": "military shoes, combat boots"
    },
    {
      "question": "溶鉱炉",
      "answer": "ようこうろ",
      "meaning": "smelting furnace, blast furnace"
    },
    {
      "question": "新芽",
      "answer": "しんめ",
      "meaning": "sprout, bud, shoot"
    },
    {
      "question": "得手",
      "answer": "えて",
      "meaning": "forte, strong point"
    },
    {
      "question": "道徳的",
      "answer": "どうとくてき",
      "meaning": "ethical, moral"
    },
    {
      "question": "適温",
      "answer": "てきおん",
      "meaning": "suitable or moderate temperature"
    },
    {
      "question": "髪質",
      "answer": "かみしつ",
      "meaning": "hair type, hair quality"
    },
    {
      "question": "討滅",
      "answer": "とうめつ",
      "meaning": "destroying, annihilating, eradicating"
    },
    {
      "question": "水飴",
      "answer": "みずあめ",
      "meaning": "mizuame, glucose syrup, starch syrup, corn syrup"
    },
    {
      "question": "鋲",
      "answer": "びょう",
      "meaning": "rivet, tack, thumbtack, drawing-pin, hobnail"
    },
    {
      "question": "常世",
      "answer": "とこよ",
      "meaning": "eternalness, forever unchanging, distant land over the sea, world of the dead"
    },
    {
      "question": "平板",
      "answer": "へいばん",
      "meaning": "flat board, slab, slat, plane table, monotonous, dull, flat, boring"
    },
    {
      "question": "雑種",
      "answer": "ざっしゅ",
      "meaning": "hybrid, crossbreed, mongrel"
    },
    {
      "question": "天頂",
      "answer": "てんちょう",
      "meaning": "zenith, vertex"
    },
    {
      "question": "国家権力",
      "answer": "こっかけんりょく",
      "meaning": "power of the state, government authority"
    },
    {
      "question": "慰み者",
      "answer": "なぐさみもの",
      "meaning": "(person treated as a) plaything"
    },
    {
      "question": "茹だる",
      "answer": "ゆだる,うだる",
      "meaning": "to boil, to seethe, to be oppressed by heat"
    },
    {
      "question": "殺菌",
      "answer": "さっきん",
      "meaning": "sterilization, sterilisation, disinfection"
    },
    {
      "question": "忌み",
      "answer": "いみ",
      "meaning": "mourning, abstinence, taboo, religious purification, pure, holy"
    },
    {
      "question": "評定",
      "answer": "ひょうてい,ひょうじょう",
      "meaning": "assessment, rating, grade, evaluation, council, conference, consultation"
    },
    {
      "question": "商う",
      "answer": "あきなう",
      "meaning": "to trade in (commercial goods), to deal in, to sell"
    },
    {
      "question": "捨て子",
      "answer": "すてご",
      "meaning": "abandoned child, foundling"
    },
    {
      "question": "本妻",
      "answer": "ほんさい",
      "meaning": "one's legal wife"
    },
    {
      "question": "横文字",
      "answer": "よこもじ",
      "meaning": "horizontal script (esp. of a European language), European writing, Roman letters, European language,"
    },
    {
      "question": "淡雪",
      "answer": "あわゆき",
      "meaning": "light snowfall"
    },
    {
      "question": "織姫",
      "answer": "おりひめ",
      "meaning": "woman textile worker, Vega (star in the constellation Lyra), Alpha Lyrae"
    },
    {
      "question": "鐙",
      "answer": "あぶみ",
      "meaning": "stirrup"
    },
    {
      "question": "自省",
      "answer": "じせい",
      "meaning": "self-examination, reflection"
    },
    {
      "question": "全力投球",
      "answer": "ぜんりょくとうきゅう",
      "meaning": "using all of one's strength (to), giving (it) everything one has got, going full-out, throwing a bal"
    },
    {
      "question": "終章",
      "answer": "しゅうしょう",
      "meaning": "final chapter, last chapter, last section (of a book, essay, song etc.), epilogue"
    },
    {
      "question": "尼",
      "answer": "あま,に",
      "meaning": "nun, bitch, Amagasaki, Hyogo, Amazon (online retailer), bhikkhuni (fully ordained Buddhist nun), Ind"
    },
    {
      "question": "遅滞",
      "answer": "ちたい",
      "meaning": "delay, procrastination"
    },
    {
      "question": "千倍",
      "answer": "せんばい",
      "meaning": "thousand-fold"
    },
    {
      "question": "植わる",
      "answer": "うわる",
      "meaning": "to be planted"
    },
    {
      "question": "四角形",
      "answer": "しかくけい,しかっけい",
      "meaning": "quadrilateral, quadrangle, tetragon"
    },
    {
      "question": "一生涯",
      "answer": "いっしょうがい",
      "meaning": "lifetime, one's whole life, all through life"
    },
    {
      "question": "馴れ合い",
      "answer": "なれあい",
      "meaning": "collusion, conspiracy, common-law marriage, illicit intercourse, liaison"
    },
    {
      "question": "最盛期",
      "answer": "さいせいき",
      "meaning": "golden age, prime, heyday, height of prosperity, season (for fruit, vegetables, etc.), best time"
    },
    {
      "question": "転ばす",
      "answer": "ころばす",
      "meaning": "to knock down, to topple"
    },
    {
      "question": "釣",
      "answer": "つり",
      "meaning": "fishing, angling, change (for a purchase), trolling, writing deliberately inflammatory posts online"
    },
    {
      "question": "此奴",
      "answer": "こいつ,こやつ",
      "meaning": "he, she, this fellow, this guy, this person, this, this one, this thing, Hey, you!, You bastard!, Da"
    },
    {
      "question": "紙芝居",
      "answer": "かみしばい",
      "meaning": "kamishibai, storytelling with pictures, form of Japanese street theater and storytelling (popular fr"
    },
    {
      "question": "神の言葉",
      "answer": "かみのことば",
      "meaning": "Word of God, God's Word, sword of the Spirit, Logos (i.e. the Trinity incarnate in Jesus Christ)"
    },
    {
      "question": "呼ばわる",
      "answer": "よばわる",
      "meaning": "to call out, to shout"
    },
    {
      "question": "日和見",
      "answer": "ひよりみ",
      "meaning": "opportunism, waiting and seeing (how the wind blows), sitting on the fence, straddling"
    },
    {
      "question": "赤身",
      "answer": "あかみ",
      "meaning": "red flesh (of a fish), red-fleshed fish (e.g. tuna), lean meat, heartwood"
    },
    {
      "question": "上目使い",
      "answer": "うわめづかい",
      "meaning": "upturned eyes"
    },
    {
      "question": "名画",
      "answer": "めいが",
      "meaning": "famous picture, masterpiece (painting), film classic"
    },
    {
      "question": "胎動",
      "answer": "たいどう",
      "meaning": "quickening, foetal (fetal) movement, fomenting (trouble)"
    },
    {
      "question": "兼用",
      "answer": "けんよう",
      "meaning": "multi-use, combined use, combination, serving two purposes"
    },
    {
      "question": "達磨",
      "answer": "だるま",
      "meaning": "daruma, tumbling doll, round, red-painted good-luck doll in the shape of Bodhidharma, with a blank e"
    },
    {
      "question": "憤激",
      "answer": "ふんげき",
      "meaning": "fury"
    },
    {
      "question": "菜園",
      "answer": "さいえん",
      "meaning": "vegetable garden"
    },
    {
      "question": "穏当",
      "answer": "おんとう",
      "meaning": "proper, reasonable, right, appropriate"
    },
    {
      "question": "管理職",
      "answer": "かんりしょく",
      "meaning": "management, managerial position, administrative post, person in a managerial position"
    },
    {
      "question": "極地",
      "answer": "きょくち",
      "meaning": "polar regions, the pole, farthest land, ends of the earth"
    },
    {
      "question": "末娘",
      "answer": "すえむすめ",
      "meaning": "youngest daughter"
    },
    {
      "question": "蜜月",
      "answer": "みつげつ",
      "meaning": "honeymoon, in an intimate relationship"
    },
    {
      "question": "侍医",
      "answer": "じい",
      "meaning": "court physician"
    },
    {
      "question": "高空",
      "answer": "こうくう,たかぞら",
      "meaning": "high altitude"
    },
    {
      "question": "進攻",
      "answer": "しんこう",
      "meaning": "attack, drive, advance, invasion"
    },
    {
      "question": "平安時代",
      "answer": "へいあんじだい",
      "meaning": "Heian period (794-1185)"
    },
    {
      "question": "高次元",
      "answer": "こうじげん",
      "meaning": "high dimension, higher dimensions"
    },
    {
      "question": "上塗り",
      "answer": "うわぬり",
      "meaning": "final coat (of paint, plaster, varnish, etc.), finish, glazing, adding more of the same (of somethin"
    },
    {
      "question": "口を拭う",
      "answer": "くちをぬぐう",
      "meaning": "to feign innocence, to feign ignorance, to wipe one's mouth"
    },
    {
      "question": "鉄橋",
      "answer": "てっきょう",
      "meaning": "railway bridge, iron bridge"
    },
    {
      "question": "高周波",
      "answer": "こうしゅうは",
      "meaning": "high frequency, HF"
    },
    {
      "question": "上衣",
      "answer": "うわぎ,じょうい",
      "meaning": "coat, tunic, jacket, outer garment"
    },
    {
      "question": "水棲",
      "answer": "すいせい",
      "meaning": "aquatic (life), living in the water"
    },
    {
      "question": "絵文字",
      "answer": "えもじ",
      "meaning": "emoji, pictorial symbol, pictograph, pictogram, ASCII art"
    },
    {
      "question": "青森",
      "answer": "あおもり",
      "meaning": "Aomori (city, prefecture)"
    },
    {
      "question": "老骨",
      "answer": "ろうこつ",
      "meaning": "one's old bones, old man"
    },
    {
      "question": "日光浴",
      "answer": "にっこうよく",
      "meaning": "sunbathing"
    },
    {
      "question": "食べ盛り",
      "answer": "たべざかり",
      "meaning": "growing child's hearty appetite"
    },
    {
      "question": "授受",
      "answer": "じゅじゅ",
      "meaning": "giving and receiving, transferring, transfer, changing hands"
    },
    {
      "question": "一党",
      "answer": "いっとう",
      "meaning": "one party, one faction, one clique"
    },
    {
      "question": "辻馬車",
      "answer": "つじばしゃ",
      "meaning": "(horse-drawn) cab, gharry, fiacre"
    },
    {
      "question": "空爆",
      "answer": "くうばく",
      "meaning": "aerial bombing"
    },
    {
      "question": "物産",
      "answer": "ぶっさん",
      "meaning": "product"
    },
    {
      "question": "股下",
      "answer": "またした",
      "meaning": "inseam, inside leg"
    },
    {
      "question": "酷評",
      "answer": "こくひょう",
      "meaning": "severe criticism, damnation"
    },
    {
      "question": "重なり",
      "answer": "かさなり",
      "meaning": "overlapping, piling, stacking"
    },
    {
      "question": "日輪",
      "answer": "にちりん",
      "meaning": "the sun"
    },
    {
      "question": "目を遣る",
      "answer": "めをやる",
      "meaning": "to look towards"
    },
    {
      "question": "主宰",
      "answer": "しゅさい",
      "meaning": "supervision, superintendence, chairmanship, chairman"
    },
    {
      "question": "黎明",
      "answer": "れいめい",
      "meaning": "daybreak, dawn, gray of the morning (grey), dawn (of a new age)"
    },
    {
      "question": "神仏",
      "answer": "しんぶつ,かみほとけ",
      "meaning": "gods and Buddha, Shinto and Buddhism"
    },
    {
      "question": "切り抜き",
      "answer": "きりぬき",
      "meaning": "clipping (of newspaper article, etc.), cutting, scrap (for a scrapbook), cut-out (picture, coloured"
    },
    {
      "question": "永続",
      "answer": "えいぞく",
      "meaning": "permanence, continuation"
    },
    {
      "question": "霊峰",
      "answer": "れいほう",
      "meaning": "sacred mountain"
    },
    {
      "question": "複眼",
      "answer": "ふくがん",
      "meaning": "compound eyes"
    },
    {
      "question": "鉛色",
      "answer": "なまりいろ",
      "meaning": "lead colour, lead color"
    },
    {
      "question": "符号",
      "answer": "ふごう",
      "meaning": "sign, mark, symbol, code, sign (e.g. positive, negative)"
    },
    {
      "question": "虚実",
      "answer": "きょじつ",
      "meaning": "falsehood and truth, fiction and fact"
    },
    {
      "question": "概算",
      "answer": "がいさん",
      "meaning": "approximation, rough estimate, ballpark figure"
    },
    {
      "question": "滑らす",
      "answer": "ずらす,すべらす",
      "meaning": "to shift, to slide (e.g. something away from something else), to move (e.g. something out of the way"
    },
    {
      "question": "下がり",
      "answer": "さがり",
      "meaning": "fall, decline, lowering, hanging down, drooping, slanting (downward), string apron, ornamental cords"
    },
    {
      "question": "朕",
      "answer": "ちん",
      "meaning": "We"
    },
    {
      "question": "本官",
      "answer": "ほんかん",
      "meaning": "official post, regular post, permanent office, principal post (as opposed to secondary post), I (of"
    },
    {
      "question": "和尚",
      "answer": "おしょう,かしょう,わじょう",
      "meaning": "preceptor or high priest (esp. in Zen or Pure Land Buddhism), second highest priestly rank in Buddhi"
    },
    {
      "question": "木槌",
      "answer": "きづち",
      "meaning": "wooden hammer, wooden mallet"
    },
    {
      "question": "捨て猫",
      "answer": "すてねこ",
      "meaning": "abandoned cat, stray cat"
    },
    {
      "question": "肥え太る",
      "answer": "こえふとる",
      "meaning": "to grow fat"
    },
    {
      "question": "打ち首",
      "answer": "うちくび",
      "meaning": "decapitation, beheading"
    },
    {
      "question": "箇条書き",
      "answer": "かじょうがき",
      "meaning": "itemized form, itemised form, itemization, itemisation"
    },
    {
      "question": "面食い",
      "answer": "めんくい",
      "meaning": "being attracted by physical looks only, person who puts much store by good looks"
    },
    {
      "question": "小花",
      "answer": "しょうか,こばな",
      "meaning": "small flower, floret, pseudanthium, small hanafuda deck"
    },
    {
      "question": "売春",
      "answer": "ばいしゅん",
      "meaning": "prostitution"
    },
    {
      "question": "無意識的",
      "answer": "むいしきてき",
      "meaning": "unconscious"
    },
    {
      "question": "関節技",
      "answer": "かんせつわざ",
      "meaning": "locking technique in judo"
    },
    {
      "question": "詮無い",
      "answer": "せんない",
      "meaning": "unavoidable, no help for"
    },
    {
      "question": "刺し傷",
      "answer": "さしきず",
      "meaning": "stab wound, puncture wound, bite (e.g. from a insect), sting, prick"
    },
    {
      "question": "使用料",
      "answer": "しようりょう",
      "meaning": "use fee, rent"
    },
    {
      "question": "余暇",
      "answer": "よか",
      "meaning": "leisure, leisure time, spare time"
    },
    {
      "question": "絶え絶え",
      "answer": "たえだえ",
      "meaning": "feeble, faint"
    },
    {
      "question": "出来合い",
      "answer": "できあい",
      "meaning": "ready-made, common-law (wife)"
    },
    {
      "question": "削げる",
      "answer": "そげる",
      "meaning": "to split, to be split, to splinter"
    },
    {
      "question": "化け猫",
      "answer": "ばけねこ",
      "meaning": "monster cat, cat with magical powers"
    },
    {
      "question": "針葉樹",
      "answer": "しんようじゅ",
      "meaning": "conifer, needle-leaved tree"
    },
    {
      "question": "内実",
      "answer": "ないじつ",
      "meaning": "the facts, the truth, the true state of affairs, in truth, in fact, in reality, actually"
    },
    {
      "question": "寒々",
      "answer": "さむざむ",
      "meaning": "wintry, very cold-looking (e.g. landscape), bleak (e.g. room, street), desolate, empty (of furnishin"
    },
    {
      "question": "生成り",
      "answer": "きなり,なまなり",
      "meaning": "unbleached cloth, unbleached colour (color), unbleached, undyed, unfinished, unripe, incomplete, unf"
    },
    {
      "question": "恥丘",
      "answer": "ちきゅう",
      "meaning": "mons pubis, mons veneris"
    },
    {
      "question": "質疑応答",
      "answer": "しつぎおうとう",
      "meaning": "question and answer session"
    },
    {
      "question": "水兵",
      "answer": "すいへい",
      "meaning": "(naval) sailor"
    },
    {
      "question": "速力",
      "answer": "そくりょく",
      "meaning": "speed"
    },
    {
      "question": "入用",
      "answer": "いりよう,にゅうよう",
      "meaning": "need, want, necessity, costs, expenses, requirement, cost"
    },
    {
      "question": "殺し文句",
      "answer": "ころしもんく",
      "meaning": "clincher, pick-up line, honeyed phrase, telling phrase, phrase that brings someone around, esp. in p"
    },
    {
      "question": "鎮静",
      "answer": "ちんせい",
      "meaning": "calm, quiet, tranquility, tranquillity, appeasement, pacification"
    },
    {
      "question": "乱れ飛ぶ",
      "answer": "みだれとぶ",
      "meaning": "to fly wildly about"
    },
    {
      "question": "名誉挽回",
      "answer": "めいよばんかい",
      "meaning": "restoring one's impaired reputation, regaining one's honor, redeeming oneself"
    },
    {
      "question": "綿棒",
      "answer": "めんぼう",
      "meaning": "cotton swab"
    },
    {
      "question": "身請け",
      "answer": "みうけ",
      "meaning": "paying to get someone (esp. a geisha, prostitute, etc.) out of bondage"
    },
    {
      "question": "光輪",
      "answer": "こうりん",
      "meaning": "halo (esp. in Christian art), nimbus"
    },
    {
      "question": "底無し",
      "answer": "そこなし",
      "meaning": "bottomless, endlessly deep, infinite"
    },
    {
      "question": "三味線",
      "answer": "しゃみせん,さみせん",
      "meaning": "shamisen, samisen, three-stringed Japanese lute"
    },
    {
      "question": "上記",
      "answer": "じょうき",
      "meaning": "above-mentioned, above-named, above"
    },
    {
      "question": "頭頂",
      "answer": "とうちょう",
      "meaning": "top of the head, vertex, parietal"
    },
    {
      "question": "同じる",
      "answer": "どうじる",
      "meaning": "to agree"
    },
    {
      "question": "凡そ",
      "answer": "おおよそ,およそ",
      "meaning": "about, roughly, approximately, generally, on the whole, as a rule, completely, quite, entirely, alto"
    },
    {
      "question": "復縁",
      "answer": "ふくえん",
      "meaning": "reconciliation (with one's spouse, adopted child, etc.)"
    },
    {
      "question": "果たし状",
      "answer": "はたしじょう",
      "meaning": "letter of challenge (to a duel, etc.)"
    },
    {
      "question": "着色",
      "answer": "ちゃくしょく",
      "meaning": "colouring, coloring, colorant"
    },
    {
      "question": "樹齢",
      "answer": "じゅれい",
      "meaning": "age of a tree"
    },
    {
      "question": "鍛造",
      "answer": "たんぞう",
      "meaning": "forging"
    },
    {
      "question": "蒸気機関",
      "answer": "じょうききかん",
      "meaning": "steam engine"
    },
    {
      "question": "網目",
      "answer": "あみめ",
      "meaning": "stitch, mesh (of a net), half-tone (printing)"
    },
    {
      "question": "毛足",
      "answer": "けあし",
      "meaning": "length of hair (fur), pile length, growth of hair, hairy legs"
    },
    {
      "question": "滑舌",
      "answer": "かつぜつ",
      "meaning": "articulation, speaking one's lines smoothly, reciting one's lines well"
    },
    {
      "question": "果報者",
      "answer": "かほうもの",
      "meaning": "lucky fellow"
    },
    {
      "question": "聖歌",
      "answer": "せいか",
      "meaning": "hymn, chant, sacred song"
    },
    {
      "question": "陸戦",
      "answer": "りくせん",
      "meaning": "land war"
    },
    {
      "question": "睫",
      "answer": "まつげ",
      "meaning": "eyelashes"
    },
    {
      "question": "旧来",
      "answer": "きゅうらい",
      "meaning": "traditional, from ancient times, formerly"
    },
    {
      "question": "狭き門",
      "answer": "せまきもん",
      "meaning": "the strait gate (in the Bible), the narrow gate, high barrier (to enter a highly competitive school,"
    },
    {
      "question": "誤報",
      "answer": "ごほう",
      "meaning": "false report, incorrect report, misinformation, false alarm"
    },
    {
      "question": "海図",
      "answer": "かいず",
      "meaning": "sea chart"
    },
    {
      "question": "個展",
      "answer": "こてん",
      "meaning": "solo exhibition, one-man exhibition, one-woman exhibition"
    },
    {
      "question": "塹壕",
      "answer": "ざんごう",
      "meaning": "trench, dugout"
    },
    {
      "question": "二級",
      "answer": "にきゅう",
      "meaning": "second grade, second class, secondary"
    },
    {
      "question": "鋳造",
      "answer": "ちゅうぞう",
      "meaning": "casting, founding, minting"
    },
    {
      "question": "罷免",
      "answer": "ひめん",
      "meaning": "dismissal (from a position), discharge"
    },
    {
      "question": "見た所",
      "answer": "みたところ",
      "meaning": "in appearance, to look at, judging from appearances"
    },
    {
      "question": "絵筆",
      "answer": "えふで",
      "meaning": "paintbrush"
    },
    {
      "question": "学外",
      "answer": "がくがい",
      "meaning": "outside the school, outside the university, unaffiliated with the university, off-campus, extramural"
    },
    {
      "question": "腹話術",
      "answer": "ふくわじゅつ",
      "meaning": "ventriloquism"
    },
    {
      "question": "結婚詐欺",
      "answer": "けっこんさぎ",
      "meaning": "marriage fraud, fake marriage"
    },
    {
      "question": "顕微鏡",
      "answer": "けんびきょう",
      "meaning": "microscope"
    },
    {
      "question": "産後",
      "answer": "さんご",
      "meaning": "postpartum, after childbirth"
    },
    {
      "question": "乱発",
      "answer": "らんぱつ",
      "meaning": "random firing, reckless firing, excessive issue"
    },
    {
      "question": "肘鉄",
      "answer": "ひじてつ",
      "meaning": "elbowing (someone), rejection, rebuff"
    },
    {
      "question": "損害賠償",
      "answer": "そんがいばいしょう",
      "meaning": "restitution, damages, indemnity, compensation"
    },
    {
      "question": "走者",
      "answer": "そうしゃ",
      "meaning": "runner, base runner"
    },
    {
      "question": "絵姿",
      "answer": "えすがた",
      "meaning": "portrait"
    },
    {
      "question": "劣等生",
      "answer": "れっとうせい",
      "meaning": "poor student"
    },
    {
      "question": "卑小",
      "answer": "ひしょう",
      "meaning": "petty, trifling"
    },
    {
      "question": "膨れっ面",
      "answer": "ふくれっつら",
      "meaning": "sulky look, sullen look"
    },
    {
      "question": "穴蔵",
      "answer": "あなぐら",
      "meaning": "cellar, cave, hole in the ground"
    },
    {
      "question": "敢然",
      "answer": "かんぜん",
      "meaning": "boldly, bravely, resolutely, determinedly"
    },
    {
      "question": "薫陶",
      "answer": "くんとう",
      "meaning": "education, training, discipline"
    },
    {
      "question": "肩慣らし",
      "answer": "かたならし",
      "meaning": "warming up, limbering up"
    },
    {
      "question": "居留守",
      "answer": "いるす",
      "meaning": "pretending to be out"
    },
    {
      "question": "濡れ濡れ",
      "answer": "ぬれぬれ",
      "meaning": "wetly, moistly"
    },
    {
      "question": "焼死",
      "answer": "しょうし",
      "meaning": "death by fire"
    },
    {
      "question": "騎馬戦",
      "answer": "きばせん",
      "meaning": "mock cavalry battle, piggyback fight"
    },
    {
      "question": "藁人形",
      "answer": "わらにんぎょう",
      "meaning": "straw doll, straw figure, straw effigy"
    },
    {
      "question": "鉄塔",
      "answer": "てっとう",
      "meaning": "steel tower, electricity pylon, transmission tower"
    },
    {
      "question": "戦記",
      "answer": "せんき",
      "meaning": "record of war, war chronicle, commentaries of war, military history"
    },
    {
      "question": "乳製品",
      "answer": "にゅうせいひん",
      "meaning": "dairy products"
    },
    {
      "question": "専",
      "answer": "せん",
      "meaning": "having a fetish for ..., specializing in ..., majoring in ..., first, foremost, number one priority,"
    },
    {
      "question": "吹雪く",
      "answer": "ふぶく",
      "meaning": "to blow snow violently"
    },
    {
      "question": "博愛",
      "answer": "はくあい",
      "meaning": "charity, benevolence, philanthropy, (love for) humanity, fraternity, brotherhood, brotherly love, lo"
    },
    {
      "question": "陶磁器",
      "answer": "とうじき",
      "meaning": "porcelain, china, chinaware, ceramics, pottery"
    },
    {
      "question": "郷土料理",
      "answer": "きょうどりょうり",
      "meaning": "regional cuisine, local cuisine"
    },
    {
      "question": "冷え",
      "answer": "ひえ",
      "meaning": "chilliness, coldness"
    },
    {
      "question": "物取り",
      "answer": "ものとり",
      "meaning": "thief, robber"
    },
    {
      "question": "班員",
      "answer": "はんいん",
      "meaning": "member of a group"
    },
    {
      "question": "揺",
      "answer": "ゆり",
      "meaning": "vibration, flickering, jolting, tremor"
    },
    {
      "question": "冷凍食品",
      "answer": "れいとうしょくひん",
      "meaning": "frozen food"
    },
    {
      "question": "潜在意識",
      "answer": "せんざいいしき",
      "meaning": "subconsciousness, subconscious (awareness)"
    },
    {
      "question": "加速度",
      "answer": "かそくど",
      "meaning": "acceleration"
    },
    {
      "question": "不一致",
      "answer": "ふいっち",
      "meaning": "discrepancy, discord, disagreement, mismatch, dissonance"
    },
    {
      "question": "平身低頭",
      "answer": "へいしんていとう",
      "meaning": "prostrating oneself, kowtowing, going down on one's knees"
    },
    {
      "question": "手癖",
      "answer": "てくせ,てぐせ",
      "meaning": "having sticky fingers, compulsive thievery, habitual movement of one's hands, marks from being handl"
    },
    {
      "question": "棒術",
      "answer": "ぼうじゅつ",
      "meaning": "bōjutsu (art of using a stick as a weapon)"
    },
    {
      "question": "逆探知",
      "answer": "ぎゃくたんち",
      "meaning": "phone trace, detecting the source of a telephone call"
    },
    {
      "question": "磨り潰す",
      "answer": "すりつぶす",
      "meaning": "to mash, to grind, to pulverize, to pulverise, to deface, to dissipate (a fortune), to run through,"
    },
    {
      "question": "夫婦喧嘩",
      "answer": "ふうふげんか",
      "meaning": "marital quarrel, argument between husband and wife"
    },
    {
      "question": "風邪気味",
      "answer": "かぜぎみ",
      "meaning": "slight cold, bit of a cold, touch of a cold, lingering cold"
    },
    {
      "question": "頭首",
      "answer": "とうしゅ",
      "meaning": "boss, chief, manager"
    },
    {
      "question": "聖痕",
      "answer": "せいこん",
      "meaning": "stigmata"
    },
    {
      "question": "家庭菜園",
      "answer": "かていさいえん",
      "meaning": "kitchen garden"
    },
    {
      "question": "忠言",
      "answer": "ちゅうげん",
      "meaning": "(good) advice"
    },
    {
      "question": "睦言",
      "answer": "むつごと",
      "meaning": "lovers' talk, whispered intimacies"
    },
    {
      "question": "湯冷め",
      "answer": "ゆざめ",
      "meaning": "feeling chilly after taking a bath"
    },
    {
      "question": "稀に見る",
      "answer": "まれにみる",
      "meaning": "rare, extraordinary, singular"
    },
    {
      "question": "素子",
      "answer": "そし",
      "meaning": "element (esp. component in electronics), elemental device, device, data, datum"
    },
    {
      "question": "謀殺",
      "answer": "ぼうさつ",
      "meaning": "premeditated murder, deliberate murder, willful murder, wilful murder"
    },
    {
      "question": "特命",
      "answer": "とくめい",
      "meaning": "special directive, special order, special mission, special appointment"
    },
    {
      "question": "教職",
      "answer": "きょうしょく",
      "meaning": "the teaching profession, education of laity (in Christianity)"
    },
    {
      "question": "婚",
      "answer": "よばい,くながい",
      "meaning": "creeping at night into a woman's bedroom, stealing into a girl's bedroom at night to make love, snea"
    },
    {
      "question": "退社",
      "answer": "たいしゃ",
      "meaning": "resignation, leaving office, leaving work (e.g. at the end of the day)"
    },
    {
      "question": "未然",
      "answer": "みぜん",
      "meaning": "before it happens, previously"
    },
    {
      "question": "御三家",
      "answer": "ごさんけ",
      "meaning": "three branch Tokugawa families (Owari, Kii, and Mito), big three, top three"
    },
    {
      "question": "銜える",
      "answer": "くわえる",
      "meaning": "to hold in one's mouth"
    },
    {
      "question": "奏上",
      "answer": "そうじょう",
      "meaning": "report to the Emperor"
    },
    {
      "question": "自社",
      "answer": "じしゃ",
      "meaning": "one's company, company one works for, in-house, belonging to the company"
    },
    {
      "question": "型破り",
      "answer": "かたやぶり",
      "meaning": "unusual, unconventional, mold-breaking, outside the box"
    },
    {
      "question": "助け合い",
      "answer": "たすけあい",
      "meaning": "cooperation, mutual aid (help)"
    },
    {
      "question": "膝が笑う",
      "answer": "ひざがわらう",
      "meaning": "to have one's knees be about to give way"
    },
    {
      "question": "黒豹",
      "answer": "くろひょう",
      "meaning": "black panther"
    },
    {
      "question": "株主",
      "answer": "かぶぬし",
      "meaning": "shareholder, stockholder"
    },
    {
      "question": "先発",
      "answer": "せんぱつ",
      "meaning": "starting in advance, starting first, going first, going ahead, starting (in team sports)"
    },
    {
      "question": "敷",
      "answer": "しき,じき",
      "meaning": "spreading, laying out, covering, security deposit, Japanese mattress, suffix indicating room size (f"
    },
    {
      "question": "代表作",
      "answer": "だいひょうさく",
      "meaning": "most important work (of a writer, artist, etc.), representative work, masterpiece"
    },
    {
      "question": "大言壮語",
      "answer": "たいげんそうご",
      "meaning": "big talk, boasting, bragging"
    },
    {
      "question": "永住",
      "answer": "えいじゅう",
      "meaning": "permanent residence"
    },
    {
      "question": "卯",
      "answer": "う,ぼう",
      "meaning": "the Rabbit (fourth sign of the Chinese zodiac), the Hare, hour of the Rabbit (around 6am, 5-7am, or"
    },
    {
      "question": "姿絵",
      "answer": "すがたえ",
      "meaning": "portrait"
    },
    {
      "question": "カレー粉",
      "answer": "カレーこ",
      "meaning": "curry powder"
    },
    {
      "question": "八百長",
      "answer": "やおちょう",
      "meaning": "match fixing, put-up job, fixed game"
    },
    {
      "question": "落とし所",
      "answer": "おとしどころ",
      "meaning": "point of compromise, common ground"
    },
    {
      "question": "火消し",
      "answer": "ひけし",
      "meaning": "extinguishing a fire, (Edo-period) fireman"
    },
    {
      "question": "銃刀法",
      "answer": "じゅうとうほう",
      "meaning": "Swords and Firearms Control Law (1958)"
    },
    {
      "question": "合いの手",
      "answer": "あいのて",
      "meaning": "interlude (in traditional Japanese music), chanting or clapping along (during a song or dance), inte"
    },
    {
      "question": "事後承諾",
      "answer": "じごしょうだく",
      "meaning": "ex-post-facto approval"
    },
    {
      "question": "旨とする",
      "answer": "むねとする",
      "meaning": "to make it a principle to ..., to aim at doing"
    },
    {
      "question": "前衛的",
      "answer": "ぜんえいてき",
      "meaning": "avant-garde"
    },
    {
      "question": "電子戦",
      "answer": "でんしせん",
      "meaning": "electronic warfare"
    },
    {
      "question": "韋駄天",
      "answer": "いだてん",
      "meaning": "Skanda (swift-footed guardian deity), great runner"
    },
    {
      "question": "先任",
      "answer": "せんにん",
      "meaning": "seniority, predecessor"
    },
    {
      "question": "十字軍",
      "answer": "じゅうじぐん",
      "meaning": "Crusades, Crusaders"
    },
    {
      "question": "ロン毛",
      "answer": "ロンげ",
      "meaning": "long hair (usu. of a man)"
    },
    {
      "question": "狂騒",
      "answer": "きょうそう",
      "meaning": "mania, wild excitement"
    },
    {
      "question": "知見",
      "answer": "ちけん",
      "meaning": "expertise, experience, knowledge"
    },
    {
      "question": "実行力",
      "answer": "じっこうりょく",
      "meaning": "ability to get things done"
    },
    {
      "question": "捻り潰す",
      "answer": "ひねりつぶす",
      "meaning": "to pinch and crush, to pinch out"
    },
    {
      "question": "塩加減",
      "answer": "しおかげん",
      "meaning": "seasoning with salt, amount of salt"
    },
    {
      "question": "遠雷",
      "answer": "えんらい",
      "meaning": "distant thunder"
    },
    {
      "question": "所感",
      "answer": "しょかん",
      "meaning": "impressions, thoughts, feelings, opinions"
    },
    {
      "question": "著作権",
      "answer": "ちょさくけん",
      "meaning": "copyright"
    },
    {
      "question": "聞き上手",
      "answer": "ききじょうず",
      "meaning": "being a good listener, good listener"
    },
    {
      "question": "放任",
      "answer": "ほうにん",
      "meaning": "noninterference, leaving something to take its own course, giving someone a free hand with something"
    },
    {
      "question": "お早う",
      "answer": "おはよう",
      "meaning": "good morning"
    },
    {
      "question": "石灰",
      "answer": "せっかい,いしばい",
      "meaning": "lime, quicklime, caustic lime"
    },
    {
      "question": "花吹雪",
      "answer": "はなふぶき",
      "meaning": "falling cherry blossoms, storm of falling cherry blossoms"
    },
    {
      "question": "給水",
      "answer": "きゅうすい",
      "meaning": "water supply"
    },
    {
      "question": "饗宴",
      "answer": "きょうえん",
      "meaning": "feast, banquet"
    },
    {
      "question": "月一",
      "answer": "つきいち",
      "meaning": "(at a rate of) once a month, 10 percent monthly interest"
    },
    {
      "question": "地毛",
      "answer": "じげ",
      "meaning": "real hair, one's own hair"
    },
    {
      "question": "戦く",
      "answer": "おののく,わななく",
      "meaning": "to shake (from fear, cold, excitement, etc.), to shudder, to tremble, to shiver, to shake"
    },
    {
      "question": "突き通す",
      "answer": "つきとおす",
      "meaning": "to pierce, to penetrate"
    },
    {
      "question": "余罪",
      "answer": "よざい",
      "meaning": "other crimes, further offenses, further offences"
    },
    {
      "question": "監",
      "answer": "げん",
      "meaning": "special Nara-period administrative division for areas containing a detached palace (Yoshino and Izum"
    },
    {
      "question": "灯籠",
      "answer": "とうろう",
      "meaning": "garden lantern, hanging lantern"
    },
    {
      "question": "装弾",
      "answer": "そうだん",
      "meaning": "loading (a firearm)"
    },
    {
      "question": "低位",
      "answer": "ていい",
      "meaning": "lower position"
    },
    {
      "question": "水瓶",
      "answer": "みずがめ,すいびょう,すいびん",
      "meaning": "water jug, portable water vessel (for drinking or washing up)"
    },
    {
      "question": "機影",
      "answer": "きえい",
      "meaning": "sight (signs) of an aeroplane (airplane)"
    },
    {
      "question": "小鉢",
      "answer": "こばち",
      "meaning": "small bowl"
    },
    {
      "question": "詰め物",
      "answer": "つめもの",
      "meaning": "filling, packing material, stuffing, padding"
    },
    {
      "question": "言付け",
      "answer": "ことづけ,いいつけ",
      "meaning": "(verbal) message, excuse, pretext, order, command, directions, instructions"
    },
    {
      "question": "教示",
      "answer": "きょうじ,きょうし",
      "meaning": "instruction, teaching"
    },
    {
      "question": "気前",
      "answer": "きまえ",
      "meaning": "generosity"
    },
    {
      "question": "爪弾く",
      "answer": "つまびく",
      "meaning": "to strum, to pluck the strings (of a guitar)"
    },
    {
      "question": "受肉",
      "answer": "じゅにく",
      "meaning": "(Christ's) incarnation"
    },
    {
      "question": "泥濘",
      "answer": "ぬかるみ,でいねい",
      "meaning": "quagmire, sludge, mud, slush, mire"
    },
    {
      "question": "炭素",
      "answer": "たんそ",
      "meaning": "carbon (C)"
    },
    {
      "question": "教育的",
      "answer": "きょういくてき",
      "meaning": "educational, instructive"
    },
    {
      "question": "義肢",
      "answer": "ぎし",
      "meaning": "artificial limb"
    },
    {
      "question": "諸刃",
      "answer": "もろは",
      "meaning": "double-edged, double-edged blade"
    },
    {
      "question": "闇市",
      "answer": "やみいち",
      "meaning": "black market"
    },
    {
      "question": "鉤",
      "answer": "はり,ち,かぎ",
      "meaning": "needle, pin, hook, stinger, thorn, hand (e.g. clock, etc.), pointer, staple (for a stapler), needlew"
    },
    {
      "question": "震度",
      "answer": "しんど",
      "meaning": "seismic intensity"
    },
    {
      "question": "設問",
      "answer": "せつもん",
      "meaning": "posing a question, question"
    },
    {
      "question": "排気",
      "answer": "はいき",
      "meaning": "exhaust, emission (of gas from an engine), expulsion (of air), ventilation"
    },
    {
      "question": "平素",
      "answer": "へいそ",
      "meaning": "ordinary, in the past, usual, regular"
    },
    {
      "question": "光合成",
      "answer": "こうごうせい",
      "meaning": "photosynthesis"
    },
    {
      "question": "図柄",
      "answer": "ずがら",
      "meaning": "design, pattern"
    },
    {
      "question": "がぶ飲み",
      "answer": "がぶのみ",
      "meaning": "swig, gulp"
    },
    {
      "question": "会わす",
      "answer": "あわす",
      "meaning": "to make (someone) to meet, to let (someone) meet, to expose to, to subject to"
    },
    {
      "question": "東海道",
      "answer": "とうかいどう",
      "meaning": "Tokaido (Edo-period Edo-Kyoto highway)"
    },
    {
      "question": "自己流",
      "answer": "じこりゅう",
      "meaning": "one's own style, self-taught manner"
    },
    {
      "question": "嬉し涙",
      "answer": "うれしなみだ",
      "meaning": "happy tears, tears of joy"
    },
    {
      "question": "か黒い",
      "answer": "かぐろい",
      "meaning": "deep black"
    },
    {
      "question": "炬燵",
      "answer": "こたつ",
      "meaning": "kotatsu, table over an electric heater (orig. a charcoal brazier in a floor well) with a hanging qui"
    },
    {
      "question": "二軍",
      "answer": "にぐん",
      "meaning": "second string players"
    },
    {
      "question": "幌馬車",
      "answer": "ほろばしゃ",
      "meaning": "covered wagon, prairie schooner"
    },
    {
      "question": "廃棄物",
      "answer": "はいきぶつ",
      "meaning": "waste matter, waste, garbage, trash"
    },
    {
      "question": "後列",
      "answer": "こうれつ",
      "meaning": "rear, back row"
    },
    {
      "question": "立ち退き",
      "answer": "たちのき",
      "meaning": "eviction"
    },
    {
      "question": "前傾",
      "answer": "ぜんけい",
      "meaning": "forward inclination (of the body), bending forward, anteversion"
    },
    {
      "question": "隆々",
      "answer": "りゅうりゅう",
      "meaning": "prosperous, flourishing, thriving, muscular, brawny"
    },
    {
      "question": "器用貧乏",
      "answer": "きようびんぼう",
      "meaning": "Jack of all trades and master of none"
    },
    {
      "question": "婉曲",
      "answer": "えんきょく",
      "meaning": "euphemistic, circumlocutory, roundabout, indirect"
    },
    {
      "question": "紛糾",
      "answer": "ふんきゅう",
      "meaning": "complication, confusion, disorder"
    },
    {
      "question": "下車",
      "answer": "げしゃ",
      "meaning": "alighting (from a train, bus, etc.), getting off, getting out (of a car)"
    },
    {
      "question": "原始人",
      "answer": "げんしじん",
      "meaning": "primitive man"
    },
    {
      "question": "舌戦",
      "answer": "ぜっせん",
      "meaning": "war of words"
    },
    {
      "question": "小粋",
      "answer": "こいき",
      "meaning": "stylish, smart, chic, tasteful, snappy, dapper, conceited, cheeky"
    },
    {
      "question": "実業家",
      "answer": "じつぎょうか",
      "meaning": "businessman, industrialist"
    },
    {
      "question": "銃剣",
      "answer": "じゅうけん",
      "meaning": "bayonet, guns and swords"
    },
    {
      "question": "天守閣",
      "answer": "てんしゅかく",
      "meaning": "castle tower, keep, donjon"
    },
    {
      "question": "賄い",
      "answer": "まかない",
      "meaning": "boarding, board, meals, catering, cook"
    },
    {
      "question": "一昼夜",
      "answer": "いっちゅうや",
      "meaning": "whole day and night, 24 hours"
    },
    {
      "question": "頭越し",
      "answer": "あたまごし",
      "meaning": "ignoring, bypassing, doing something without consultation, going over someone's head"
    },
    {
      "question": "爪楊枝",
      "answer": "つまようじ",
      "meaning": "toothpick"
    },
    {
      "question": "錨",
      "answer": "いかり",
      "meaning": "anchor"
    },
    {
      "question": "馬の背",
      "answer": "うまのせ",
      "meaning": "horseback"
    },
    {
      "question": "輪ゴム",
      "answer": "わゴム",
      "meaning": "rubber band, elastic band"
    },
    {
      "question": "真人間",
      "answer": "まにんげん",
      "meaning": "an honest man, a good citizen"
    },
    {
      "question": "観音開き",
      "answer": "かんのんびらき",
      "meaning": "double doors opening from the centre, double-opening from the centre (e.g. doors, casement windows,"
    },
    {
      "question": "読み耽る",
      "answer": "よみふける",
      "meaning": "to be absorbed in reading"
    },
    {
      "question": "敵役",
      "answer": "かたきやく,てきやく",
      "meaning": "role of the villain, the bad guy"
    },
    {
      "question": "千鳥足",
      "answer": "ちどりあし",
      "meaning": "tottering steps, drunken staggering"
    },
    {
      "question": "歩き",
      "answer": "あるき,ありき",
      "meaning": "walk, walking, foot messenger (of a town, village, etc.)"
    },
    {
      "question": "鉄血",
      "answer": "てっけつ",
      "meaning": "blood and iron, military might"
    },
    {
      "question": "燦",
      "answer": "さん",
      "meaning": "brilliant, resplendent"
    },
    {
      "question": "官軍",
      "answer": "かんぐん",
      "meaning": "government forces, loyalist army"
    },
    {
      "question": "深海魚",
      "answer": "しんかいぎょ",
      "meaning": "deep-sea fish"
    },
    {
      "question": "欠乏",
      "answer": "けつぼう",
      "meaning": "want, shortage, famine"
    },
    {
      "question": "労り",
      "answer": "いたわり",
      "meaning": "sympathy, consideration, carefulness, attention, service, labor, labour, trouble, meritorious deed,"
    },
    {
      "question": "一読",
      "answer": "いちどく",
      "meaning": "perusal, one reading"
    },
    {
      "question": "猫撫で声",
      "answer": "ねこなでごえ",
      "meaning": "soft, coaxing voice, wheedling voice, ingratiating voice"
    },
    {
      "question": "採血",
      "answer": "さいけつ",
      "meaning": "drawing blood, collecting blood"
    },
    {
      "question": "中心街",
      "answer": "ちゅうしんがい",
      "meaning": "high street, town centre (center)"
    },
    {
      "question": "転進",
      "answer": "てんしん",
      "meaning": "changing course or direction, shifting position"
    },
    {
      "question": "磨り減る",
      "answer": "すりへる",
      "meaning": "to be worn down, to be reduced"
    },
    {
      "question": "叫喚",
      "answer": "きょうかん",
      "meaning": "shout, scream"
    },
    {
      "question": "隻腕",
      "answer": "せきわん",
      "meaning": "one-armed person, one-handed person"
    },
    {
      "question": "葬",
      "answer": "そう",
      "meaning": "funeral"
    },
    {
      "question": "煽動",
      "answer": "せんどう",
      "meaning": "incitement, sedition, agitation, abetting"
    },
    {
      "question": "基幹",
      "answer": "きかん",
      "meaning": "mainstay, nucleus, key"
    },
    {
      "question": "正対",
      "answer": "せいたい",
      "meaning": "confronting directly, meeting face-to-face"
    },
    {
      "question": "休講",
      "answer": "きゅうこう",
      "meaning": "cancellation (of a lecture, class, etc.)"
    },
    {
      "question": "覿面",
      "answer": "てきめん",
      "meaning": "immediacy, instantaneousness, promptness"
    },
    {
      "question": "着信履歴",
      "answer": "ちゃくしんりれき",
      "meaning": "call register, incoming call history, list of received calls"
    },
    {
      "question": "伸びやか",
      "answer": "のびやか",
      "meaning": "comfortable, carefree"
    },
    {
      "question": "蛇足",
      "answer": "だそく",
      "meaning": "redundancy, superfluity, useless addition"
    },
    {
      "question": "両極端",
      "answer": "りょうきょくたん",
      "meaning": "both extremes"
    },
    {
      "question": "神宮",
      "answer": "じんぐう",
      "meaning": "high-status Shinto shrine with connection to imperial family, imperial Shinto shrine"
    },
    {
      "question": "竪琴",
      "answer": "たてごと",
      "meaning": "harp, lyre"
    },
    {
      "question": "官邸",
      "answer": "かんてい",
      "meaning": "official residence (e.g. of the prime minister)"
    },
    {
      "question": "政党",
      "answer": "せいとう",
      "meaning": "political party"
    },
    {
      "question": "武門",
      "answer": "ぶもん",
      "meaning": "military family, warrior class"
    },
    {
      "question": "手提げ",
      "answer": "てさげ",
      "meaning": "handbag, purse"
    },
    {
      "question": "足技",
      "answer": "あしわざ",
      "meaning": "(judo) foot technique, footwork"
    },
    {
      "question": "秒殺",
      "answer": "びょうさつ",
      "meaning": "winning in a flash, instant defeat"
    },
    {
      "question": "出戻り",
      "answer": "でもどり",
      "meaning": "(of a woman) divorcing and moving back in with her parents, (of an employee) leaving a position only"
    },
    {
      "question": "熊本",
      "answer": "くまもと",
      "meaning": "Kumamoto (city, prefecture)"
    },
    {
      "question": "種別",
      "answer": "しゅべつ",
      "meaning": "classification, assortment"
    },
    {
      "question": "受け手",
      "answer": "うけて",
      "meaning": "(referring to a person) receiver, receiving side, viewer, listener"
    },
    {
      "question": "耽美",
      "answer": "たんび",
      "meaning": "aestheticism, pursuit of beauty, obsession with beautiful things"
    },
    {
      "question": "酒豪",
      "answer": "しゅごう",
      "meaning": "heavy drinker"
    },
    {
      "question": "直訳",
      "answer": "ちょくやく",
      "meaning": "literal translation, direct translation"
    },
    {
      "question": "悪童",
      "answer": "あくどう",
      "meaning": "bad boy, naughty child, brat"
    },
    {
      "question": "痒み",
      "answer": "かゆみ",
      "meaning": "itch"
    },
    {
      "question": "初版",
      "answer": "しょはん",
      "meaning": "first edition"
    },
    {
      "question": "魔窟",
      "answer": "まくつ",
      "meaning": "den of vice, rogue's den, brothel, red-light district, cluttered room"
    },
    {
      "question": "一文無し",
      "answer": "いちもんなし",
      "meaning": "penniless, broke"
    },
    {
      "question": "自己分析",
      "answer": "じこぶんせき",
      "meaning": "self-analysis, autoanalysis"
    },
    {
      "question": "満室",
      "answer": "まんしつ",
      "meaning": "no vacancy, full occupancy"
    },
    {
      "question": "細め",
      "answer": "ほそめ",
      "meaning": "thinnish, somewhat narrow"
    },
    {
      "question": "海月",
      "answer": "くらげ",
      "meaning": "jellyfish, medusa"
    },
    {
      "question": "海兵",
      "answer": "かいへい",
      "meaning": "sailor, marine"
    },
    {
      "question": "合奏",
      "answer": "がっそう",
      "meaning": "ensemble (e.g. orchestra, chamber group, etc.), concert"
    },
    {
      "question": "異教",
      "answer": "いきょう",
      "meaning": "paganism, heathenism"
    },
    {
      "question": "歌唱",
      "answer": "かしょう",
      "meaning": "song, singing"
    },
    {
      "question": "試飲",
      "answer": "しいん",
      "meaning": "sampling a drink, tasting"
    },
    {
      "question": "鰹節",
      "answer": "かつおぶし,かつぶし",
      "meaning": "katsuobushi, small pieces of sliced dried bonito"
    },
    {
      "question": "人家",
      "answer": "じんか",
      "meaning": "house, dwelling, human habitation"
    },
    {
      "question": "初雪",
      "answer": "はつゆき",
      "meaning": "first snow (of the season), first snowfall"
    },
    {
      "question": "厚顔無恥",
      "answer": "こうがんむち",
      "meaning": "shameless, brazen and unscrupulous"
    },
    {
      "question": "出走",
      "answer": "しゅっそう",
      "meaning": "entry in a race"
    },
    {
      "question": "落葉",
      "answer": "おちば,らくよう",
      "meaning": "fallen leaves, leaf litter, falling leaves, leaf fall, dropping leaves, defoliation, deciduous"
    },
    {
      "question": "奇術師",
      "answer": "きじゅつし",
      "meaning": "conjurer, magician, illusionist"
    },
    {
      "question": "金棒",
      "answer": "かなぼう",
      "meaning": "metal rod, metal bar, iron rod, crowbar, iron club, iron staff with rings on top (traditionally used"
    },
    {
      "question": "三角帽子",
      "answer": "さんかくぼうし",
      "meaning": "three-cornered hat, tricorne"
    },
    {
      "question": "一重",
      "answer": "ひとえ",
      "meaning": "one layer, single layer, monopetalous, unlined kimono, single-edged eyelid, eyelid with an epicanthi"
    },
    {
      "question": "縁戚",
      "answer": "えんせき",
      "meaning": "relative"
    },
    {
      "question": "床の間",
      "answer": "とこのま",
      "meaning": "tokonoma (alcove where art or flowers are displayed)"
    },
    {
      "question": "縺れる",
      "answer": "もつれる",
      "meaning": "to get entangled, to get tangled, to tangle, to have poor control over (one's tongue, feet, etc.), t"
    },
    {
      "question": "積載",
      "answer": "せきさい",
      "meaning": "lading, loading, carrying"
    },
    {
      "question": "賛美歌",
      "answer": "さんびか",
      "meaning": "hymn, hymnal"
    },
    {
      "question": "冷蔵",
      "answer": "れいぞう",
      "meaning": "cold storage, refrigeration"
    },
    {
      "question": "上目",
      "answer": "うわめ,じょうもく",
      "meaning": "upward glance, upturned eyes, superorder"
    },
    {
      "question": "疎外",
      "answer": "そがい",
      "meaning": "estrangement, neglect, alienation, casting out, ostracism, giving the cold shoulder"
    },
    {
      "question": "左折",
      "answer": "させつ",
      "meaning": "turning to the left, left turn"
    },
    {
      "question": "余熱",
      "answer": "よねつ",
      "meaning": "waste heat, remaining heat"
    },
    {
      "question": "裏工作",
      "answer": "うらこうさく",
      "meaning": "dodgy dealings, monkey business"
    },
    {
      "question": "引き算",
      "answer": "ひきざん",
      "meaning": "subtraction"
    },
    {
      "question": "艦船",
      "answer": "かんせん",
      "meaning": "(ocean) vessels, warship"
    },
    {
      "question": "帯刀",
      "answer": "たいとう",
      "meaning": "wearing a sword"
    },
    {
      "question": "空挺",
      "answer": "くうてい",
      "meaning": "airborne"
    },
    {
      "question": "漁村",
      "answer": "ぎょそん",
      "meaning": "fishing village"
    },
    {
      "question": "軍規",
      "answer": "ぐんき",
      "meaning": "military discipline, military regulations, military rules"
    },
    {
      "question": "全高",
      "answer": "ぜんこう",
      "meaning": "overall height, distance from the ground to the highest point of an object"
    },
    {
      "question": "叛意",
      "answer": "はんい",
      "meaning": "spirit of rebellion"
    },
    {
      "question": "人肉",
      "answer": "じんにく",
      "meaning": "human flesh"
    },
    {
      "question": "日本海",
      "answer": "にほんかい",
      "meaning": "Sea of Japan"
    },
    {
      "question": "顕",
      "answer": "あらわ,けん",
      "meaning": "exposed, scanty, bare, unconcealed, naked, public, open, exposure, clarity, exoteric Buddhism, publi"
    },
    {
      "question": "月々",
      "answer": "つきづき",
      "meaning": "every month, monthly, month by month"
    },
    {
      "question": "教皇庁",
      "answer": "きょうこうちょう",
      "meaning": "Curia"
    },
    {
      "question": "魔法瓶",
      "answer": "まほうびん",
      "meaning": "thermos bottle, vacuum flask"
    },
    {
      "question": "風評被害",
      "answer": "ふうひょうひがい",
      "meaning": "damage (esp. financial) caused by harmful rumours or misinformation (rumors)"
    },
    {
      "question": "実験的",
      "answer": "じっけんてき",
      "meaning": "experimental"
    },
    {
      "question": "晒し者",
      "answer": "さらしもの",
      "meaning": "pilloried criminal exposed to public view, public scorn or humiliation, person shamed in front of ot"
    },
    {
      "question": "思い合う",
      "answer": "おもいあう",
      "meaning": "to love one another"
    },
    {
      "question": "窪",
      "answer": "くぼ",
      "meaning": "hollow, cavity, sunken place, vagina, female genitalia"
    },
    {
      "question": "画廊",
      "answer": "がろう",
      "meaning": "art gallery (esp. artworks for sale), picture gallery"
    },
    {
      "question": "堕する",
      "answer": "だする",
      "meaning": "to degenerate, to lapse into"
    },
    {
      "question": "番台",
      "answer": "ばんだい",
      "meaning": "watch stand, watcher's seat, attendant's booth (e.g. at an onsen)"
    },
    {
      "question": "長物",
      "answer": "ちょうぶつ,ながもの",
      "meaning": "something long, useless things, white elephant, boondoggle"
    },
    {
      "question": "馬鹿笑い",
      "answer": "ばかわらい",
      "meaning": "horse laugh, guffaw, wild laughter"
    },
    {
      "question": "一期一会",
      "answer": "いちごいちえ",
      "meaning": "once-in-a-lifetime encounter (hence should be cherished as such)"
    },
    {
      "question": "照り返し",
      "answer": "てりかえし",
      "meaning": "reflection, reflected light, reflected heat, glare"
    },
    {
      "question": "生体反応",
      "answer": "せいたいはんのう",
      "meaning": "reaction of a living body"
    },
    {
      "question": "交遊",
      "answer": "こうゆう",
      "meaning": "friendship, companionship, fraternity, comradeship"
    },
    {
      "question": "飲み放題",
      "answer": "のみほうだい",
      "meaning": "all you can drink, bottomless cup"
    },
    {
      "question": "中座",
      "answer": "ちゅうざ",
      "meaning": "leaving one's seat (before an event is over), excusing oneself (from a meeting, conversation, etc.)"
    },
    {
      "question": "忌憚",
      "answer": "きたん",
      "meaning": "reserve, modesty"
    },
    {
      "question": "革命家",
      "answer": "かくめいか",
      "meaning": "revolutionary"
    },
    {
      "question": "波止場",
      "answer": "はとば",
      "meaning": "wharf, quay, landing-stage, jetty"
    },
    {
      "question": "旅芸人",
      "answer": "たびげいにん",
      "meaning": "itinerant entertainer"
    },
    {
      "question": "早漏",
      "answer": "そうろう",
      "meaning": "premature ejaculation"
    },
    {
      "question": "膿む",
      "answer": "うむ",
      "meaning": "to fester, to form pus"
    },
    {
      "question": "運賃",
      "answer": "うんちん",
      "meaning": "(passenger) fare, freight rates, shipping expenses"
    },
    {
      "question": "頭脳労働",
      "answer": "ずのうろうどう",
      "meaning": "brain work, mental work, nonmanual labor"
    },
    {
      "question": "鎌鼬",
      "answer": "かまいたち",
      "meaning": "cut in the skin caused by a vacuum formed by a whirlwind, mythical weasel-like creatures riding on w"
    },
    {
      "question": "惑い",
      "answer": "まどい",
      "meaning": "delusion, illusion, infatuation, bewilderment, perplexity"
    },
    {
      "question": "移譲",
      "answer": "いじょう",
      "meaning": "transfer, assignment"
    },
    {
      "question": "握手会",
      "answer": "あくしゅかい",
      "meaning": "handshake event, handshake session, event where it is possible to shake hands with a celebrity, spor"
    },
    {
      "question": "多目的",
      "answer": "たもくてき",
      "meaning": "multipurpose"
    },
    {
      "question": "計上",
      "answer": "けいじょう",
      "meaning": "including a sum of money in one's calculations, appropriation (a sum of money)"
    },
    {
      "question": "新車",
      "answer": "しんしゃ",
      "meaning": "new car"
    },
    {
      "question": "早食い",
      "answer": "はやぐい",
      "meaning": "eating quickly, speed-eating"
    },
    {
      "question": "猛暑",
      "answer": "もうしょ",
      "meaning": "heat wave, fierce heat"
    },
    {
      "question": "得意満面",
      "answer": "とくいまんめん",
      "meaning": "triumphant air, smugness"
    },
    {
      "question": "小洒落る",
      "answer": "こじゃれる",
      "meaning": "to be somewhat stylish, to be somewhat chic"
    },
    {
      "question": "星型",
      "answer": "ほしがた",
      "meaning": "star shape, pentagram"
    },
    {
      "question": "縁故",
      "answer": "えんこ",
      "meaning": "relation, connection, affinity"
    },
    {
      "question": "符丁",
      "answer": "ふちょう",
      "meaning": "symbol, sign, mark, (secret) price mark, secret language, code, cipher, argot, password"
    },
    {
      "question": "雁字搦め",
      "answer": "がんじがらめ",
      "meaning": "bound hand and foot, hedged in (e.g. by restrictions), immobile"
    },
    {
      "question": "優越",
      "answer": "ゆうえつ",
      "meaning": "supremacy, predominance, being superior to"
    },
    {
      "question": "父子",
      "answer": "ふし",
      "meaning": "father and child, father and son, father and daughter"
    },
    {
      "question": "食べ残し",
      "answer": "たべのこし",
      "meaning": "leftovers, half-eaten food, leftover food"
    },
    {
      "question": "造詣",
      "answer": "ぞうけい",
      "meaning": "deep knowledge, attainments, scholarship"
    },
    {
      "question": "山上",
      "answer": "さんじょう",
      "meaning": "mountain top"
    },
    {
      "question": "富山",
      "answer": "とやま",
      "meaning": "Toyama (city, prefecture)"
    },
    {
      "question": "大仏",
      "answer": "だいぶつ",
      "meaning": "large statue of Buddha (trad. at least 4.8m high)"
    },
    {
      "question": "歴史家",
      "answer": "れきしか",
      "meaning": "historian"
    },
    {
      "question": "加虐",
      "answer": "かぎゃく",
      "meaning": "causing pain, sadism"
    },
    {
      "question": "電信柱",
      "answer": "でんしんばしら",
      "meaning": "telephone pole"
    },
    {
      "question": "保守",
      "answer": "ほしゅ",
      "meaning": "maintenance, conservatism, conservativeness, conservation"
    },
    {
      "question": "裏取引",
      "answer": "うらとりひき",
      "meaning": "backroom deal"
    },
    {
      "question": "頭が高い",
      "answer": "ずがたかい",
      "meaning": "haughty, holding one's head high"
    },
    {
      "question": "針の穴",
      "answer": "はりのあな",
      "meaning": "eye of a needle"
    },
    {
      "question": "無味無臭",
      "answer": "むみむしゅう",
      "meaning": "tasteless and odorless, bland"
    },
    {
      "question": "鶴の一声",
      "answer": "つるのひとこえ",
      "meaning": "final word, voice of authority, authoritative pronouncement"
    },
    {
      "question": "女王蜂",
      "answer": "じょおうばち",
      "meaning": "queen bee"
    },
    {
      "question": "華族",
      "answer": "かぞく",
      "meaning": "peerage (in Japan, 1868-1946), nobility, aristocracy"
    },
    {
      "question": "判じる",
      "answer": "はんじる",
      "meaning": "to judge, to decide, to solve, to decipher, to puzzle out, to interpret, to divine, to guess, to mak"
    },
    {
      "question": "浦島太郎",
      "answer": "うらしまたろう",
      "meaning": "Urashima Tarō, (a) Rip van Winkle, fairy-tale fisherman who, after visiting the underwater Palace of"
    },
    {
      "question": "漂白",
      "answer": "ひょうはく",
      "meaning": "blanching, bleaching"
    },
    {
      "question": "面目躍如",
      "answer": "めんもくやくじょ,めんぼくやくじょ",
      "meaning": "demonstrative of one's worth, worthy of one's reputation, living up to one's name, characteristicall"
    },
    {
      "question": "鼻の先",
      "answer": "はなのさき",
      "meaning": "in front of your nose, right next to you, tip of one's nose"
    },
    {
      "question": "浮島",
      "answer": "うきしま,うきじま",
      "meaning": "floating mass (of waterweeds, ice, etc.), floating island (mirage)"
    },
    {
      "question": "非人間的",
      "answer": "ひにんげんてき",
      "meaning": "inhuman, inhumane"
    },
    {
      "question": "投棄",
      "answer": "とうき",
      "meaning": "abandonment, giving up, throwing away, disposal, dumping"
    },
    {
      "question": "派兵",
      "answer": "はへい",
      "meaning": "dispatch of troops, despatch of troops"
    },
    {
      "question": "放水",
      "answer": "ほうすい",
      "meaning": "hosing down, drainage, discharge of water, spraying with water"
    },
    {
      "question": "男臭い",
      "answer": "おとこくさい",
      "meaning": "smelling of men, reeking of male body odor, manly, macho"
    },
    {
      "question": "厄日",
      "answer": "やくび",
      "meaning": "unlucky day, evil day"
    },
    {
      "question": "情に厚い",
      "answer": "じょうにあつい",
      "meaning": "compassionate, sympathetic"
    },
    {
      "question": "血涙",
      "answer": "けつるい",
      "meaning": "bitter tears, tears of blood"
    },
    {
      "question": "寂寥",
      "answer": "せきりょう",
      "meaning": "loneliness, desolateness"
    },
    {
      "question": "声なき声",
      "answer": "こえなきこえ",
      "meaning": "unvoiced opinion, (opinion of the) silent majority, views which are not expressed"
    },
    {
      "question": "増水",
      "answer": "ぞうすい",
      "meaning": "rising water (of river, lake, etc.), swelling water, increased water, high water"
    },
    {
      "question": "遅効",
      "answer": "ちこう",
      "meaning": "delayed effect"
    },
    {
      "question": "横長",
      "answer": "よこなが",
      "meaning": "oblong, landscape orientation"
    },
    {
      "question": "後ろ指",
      "answer": "うしろゆび",
      "meaning": "talking about (behind one's back), backbiting"
    },
    {
      "question": "三次",
      "answer": "さんじ",
      "meaning": "third, tertiary, cubic (function, equation, etc.), third-order"
    },
    {
      "question": "郷里",
      "answer": "きょうり",
      "meaning": "birth-place, home town"
    },
    {
      "question": "先見",
      "answer": "せんけん",
      "meaning": "foresight, anticipation"
    },
    {
      "question": "送金",
      "answer": "そうきん",
      "meaning": "remittance, sending money"
    },
    {
      "question": "売値",
      "answer": "うりね",
      "meaning": "selling price"
    },
    {
      "question": "拘泥",
      "answer": "こうでい",
      "meaning": "adhering to, being a stickler for, being particular about, worrying too much about"
    },
    {
      "question": "待避",
      "answer": "たいひ",
      "meaning": "(take) shelter, shunt"
    },
    {
      "question": "感付く",
      "answer": "かんづく",
      "meaning": "to sense, to suspect, to get an inkling (of something), to get wind of, to smell (e.g. danger), to b"
    },
    {
      "question": "悪乗り",
      "answer": "わるのり",
      "meaning": "getting carried away, going too far, overdoing"
    },
    {
      "question": "単独犯",
      "answer": "たんどくはん",
      "meaning": "lone criminal, sole perpetrator, crime carried out by one person"
    },
    {
      "question": "朧げ",
      "answer": "おぼろげ",
      "meaning": "vague, faint, dim, indistinct, hazy, blurry"
    },
    {
      "question": "黄昏時",
      "answer": "たそがれどき",
      "meaning": "dusk, twilight"
    },
    {
      "question": "病欠",
      "answer": "びょうけつ",
      "meaning": "absence due to illness, sick leave"
    },
    {
      "question": "小春",
      "answer": "こはる",
      "meaning": "10th month of the lunisolar calendar (traditional first month of winter, approx. November), late aut"
    },
    {
      "question": "四輪",
      "answer": "よんりん",
      "meaning": "four-wheeled"
    },
    {
      "question": "現場監督",
      "answer": "げんばかんとく",
      "meaning": "field overseer, site foreman"
    },
    {
      "question": "島流し",
      "answer": "しまながし",
      "meaning": "exile, banishment"
    },
    {
      "question": "宿直",
      "answer": "しゅくちょく,とのい",
      "meaning": "night watch, night guard, night shift"
    },
    {
      "question": "中頃",
      "answer": "なかごろ",
      "meaning": "about the middle"
    },
    {
      "question": "辰巳",
      "answer": "たつみ",
      "meaning": "southeast"
    },
    {
      "question": "生殖器",
      "answer": "せいしょくき",
      "meaning": "genital organ, genitalia, sexual organ, reproductive organ"
    },
    {
      "question": "帝王学",
      "answer": "ていおうがく",
      "meaning": "education for governing as a monarch, kingcraft"
    },
    {
      "question": "筵",
      "answer": "むしろ,えん",
      "meaning": "woven mat (esp. one made of straw), seat"
    },
    {
      "question": "不戦勝",
      "answer": "ふせんしょう",
      "meaning": "win by default"
    },
    {
      "question": "肩肘張る",
      "answer": "かたひじはる",
      "meaning": "to put on a bold front, to act big, to be unyielding, to act formally, to act stiffly"
    },
    {
      "question": "衛生的",
      "answer": "えいせいてき",
      "meaning": "hygienic, sanitary"
    },
    {
      "question": "手が早い",
      "answer": "てがはやい",
      "meaning": "to be a quick worker, to be fast in forming relationships with women, to be quick to resort to viole"
    },
    {
      "question": "閻魔",
      "answer": "えんま",
      "meaning": "Yama (king of the world of the dead, who judges the dead), Emma, Yan, Yomna"
    },
    {
      "question": "猛進",
      "answer": "もうしん",
      "meaning": "rushing madly ahead"
    },
    {
      "question": "包",
      "answer": "パオ",
      "meaning": "yurt"
    },
    {
      "question": "名うて",
      "answer": "なうて",
      "meaning": "notorious, famous"
    },
    {
      "question": "切開",
      "answer": "せっかい",
      "meaning": "incision, operation, section"
    },
    {
      "question": "抉り出す",
      "answer": "えぐりだす",
      "meaning": "to gouge out, to cut out, to scoop out, to bring to light, to reveal"
    },
    {
      "question": "水鳥",
      "answer": "すいちょう,みずとり,みずどり",
      "meaning": "waterfowl, water bird, shorebird"
    },
    {
      "question": "二者択一",
      "answer": "にしゃたくいつ",
      "meaning": "choosing between two things, two choices"
    },
    {
      "question": "目が無い",
      "answer": "めがない",
      "meaning": "being extremely fond of, having a weakness for, being a sucker for, having no eye for, being a poor"
    },
    {
      "question": "未完",
      "answer": "みかん",
      "meaning": "incomplete, unfinished"
    },
    {
      "question": "危急",
      "answer": "ききゅう",
      "meaning": "emergency, crisis, imminent danger, Vulnerable (conservation status), VU"
    },
    {
      "question": "子会社",
      "answer": "こがいしゃ",
      "meaning": "subsidiary (company)"
    },
    {
      "question": "爆竹",
      "answer": "ばくちく",
      "meaning": "firecracker"
    },
    {
      "question": "修了",
      "answer": "しゅうりょう",
      "meaning": "completion (of a course)"
    },
    {
      "question": "疎んじる",
      "answer": "うとんじる",
      "meaning": "to shun, to avoid, to ostracize, to neglect, to distance oneself from, to give the hard shoulder"
    },
    {
      "question": "山荘",
      "answer": "さんそう",
      "meaning": "mountain villa, mountain retreat, mountain cottage"
    },
    {
      "question": "迅雷",
      "answer": "じんらい",
      "meaning": "thunderclap"
    },
    {
      "question": "卵子",
      "answer": "らんし",
      "meaning": "ovum, ovule, egg cell"
    },
    {
      "question": "譜面",
      "answer": "ふめん",
      "meaning": "sheet music, score"
    },
    {
      "question": "映え",
      "answer": "はえ",
      "meaning": "glory, splendour, honour"
    },
    {
      "question": "彩色",
      "answer": "さいしき,さいしょく",
      "meaning": "colouring, coloring, colouration, coloration, painting"
    },
    {
      "question": "塗り薬",
      "answer": "ぬりぐすり",
      "meaning": "medical cream, ointment, salve, liniment"
    },
    {
      "question": "食物連鎖",
      "answer": "しょくもつれんさ",
      "meaning": "food chain"
    },
    {
      "question": "別つ",
      "answer": "わかつ",
      "meaning": "to divide, to separate, to share, to distribute, to distinguish"
    },
    {
      "question": "極悪非道",
      "answer": "ごくあくひどう",
      "meaning": "inhuman, heinous, atrocious"
    },
    {
      "question": "終止符",
      "answer": "しゅうしふ",
      "meaning": "full stop, period, end"
    },
    {
      "question": "次長",
      "answer": "じちょう",
      "meaning": "vice-chief, vice-director, assistant director, deputy manager"
    },
    {
      "question": "竜宮城",
      "answer": "りゅうぐうじょう",
      "meaning": "Palace of the Dragon King, palace from the story of Urashima Taro (said to be located at the bottom"
    },
    {
      "question": "一頻り",
      "answer": "ひとしきり",
      "meaning": "for a while, for some time, for a period"
    },
    {
      "question": "群集",
      "answer": "ぐんしゅう",
      "meaning": "crowd, community, group, herd, gathering, assembly"
    },
    {
      "question": "夢遊病",
      "answer": "むゆうびょう",
      "meaning": "sleepwalking, somnambulism"
    },
    {
      "question": "立ち戻る",
      "answer": "たちもどる",
      "meaning": "to return, to come back"
    },
    {
      "question": "異種",
      "answer": "いしゅ",
      "meaning": "different kind (species, variety), heterologous, heterogenous"
    },
    {
      "question": "同道",
      "answer": "どうどう",
      "meaning": "going with, accompanying"
    },
    {
      "question": "授乳",
      "answer": "じゅにゅう",
      "meaning": "breast-feeding, suckling, nursing"
    },
    {
      "question": "毟り取る",
      "answer": "むしりとる",
      "meaning": "to tear off, to pluck off, to take forcibly"
    },
    {
      "question": "首都圏",
      "answer": "しゅとけん",
      "meaning": "the capital city (often Tokyo) area (typically within 50 km of city's centre) (center)"
    },
    {
      "question": "全巻",
      "answer": "ぜんかん",
      "meaning": "the whole reel, the whole volume, the complete set"
    },
    {
      "question": "膝元",
      "answer": "ひざもと",
      "meaning": "near one's knee, (by) one's side, (at) one's hand, place under the protection (of one's parents, etc"
    },
    {
      "question": "鋭意",
      "answer": "えいい",
      "meaning": "eagerly, earnestly, assiduously, diligently, wholeheartedly"
    },
    {
      "question": "底本",
      "answer": "ていほん,そこほん,そこぼん",
      "meaning": "original text, source book, draft"
    },
    {
      "question": "男優",
      "answer": "だんゆう",
      "meaning": "actor (male)"
    },
    {
      "question": "高次",
      "answer": "こうじ",
      "meaning": "higher-order-, meta-"
    },
    {
      "question": "永久機関",
      "answer": "えいきゅうきかん",
      "meaning": "perpetual motion machine, perpetual motion engine, perpetuum mobile"
    },
    {
      "question": "一笑",
      "answer": "いっしょう",
      "meaning": "laugh, smile"
    },
    {
      "question": "襟足",
      "answer": "えりあし",
      "meaning": "hairline at nape of neck, nape of neck"
    },
    {
      "question": "二束三文",
      "answer": "にそくさんもん",
      "meaning": "dirt cheap, very cheap"
    },
    {
      "question": "届け出る",
      "answer": "とどけでる",
      "meaning": "to report, to notify"
    },
    {
      "question": "彼岸花",
      "answer": "ひがんばな",
      "meaning": "red spider lily (Lycoris radiata), cluster amaryllis"
    },
    {
      "question": "山形",
      "answer": "やまがた,やまなり",
      "meaning": "Yamagata (city, prefecture), mountain shape, chevron, cone, curved, forming the shape of an arch"
    },
    {
      "question": "区役所",
      "answer": "くやくしょ",
      "meaning": "ward office, council (regional)"
    },
    {
      "question": "健勝",
      "answer": "けんしょう",
      "meaning": "good health"
    },
    {
      "question": "鼻っ柱",
      "answer": "はなっぱしら",
      "meaning": "aggressiveness, competitive spirit, fighting spirit"
    },
    {
      "question": "密封",
      "answer": "みっぷう",
      "meaning": "hermetically seal, sealing (e.g. envelope)"
    },
    {
      "question": "拵える",
      "answer": "こしらえる,こさえる",
      "meaning": "to make, to manufacture"
    },
    {
      "question": "革新",
      "answer": "かくしん",
      "meaning": "reform, innovation"
    },
    {
      "question": "西部劇",
      "answer": "せいぶげき",
      "meaning": "western (film genre)"
    },
    {
      "question": "口パク",
      "answer": "くちパク",
      "meaning": "lip-syncing, lip-synching"
    },
    {
      "question": "掛け算",
      "answer": "かけざん",
      "meaning": "multiplication"
    },
    {
      "question": "目盛り",
      "answer": "めもり",
      "meaning": "gradations (on a ruler, thermometer, etc.), division, scale"
    },
    {
      "question": "顔を潰す",
      "answer": "かおをつぶす",
      "meaning": "to make somebody lose face, to embarrass someone, to make someone look foolish"
    },
    {
      "question": "生き恥",
      "answer": "いきはじ",
      "meaning": "dishonor during one's life, shame experienced during one's life"
    },
    {
      "question": "暗む",
      "answer": "くらむ",
      "meaning": "to be dazzled by, to be dizzied by, to be disoriented by, to be lost in (greed, lust, etc.), to beco"
    },
    {
      "question": "挙措",
      "answer": "きょそ",
      "meaning": "behavior, behaviour, manner"
    },
    {
      "question": "鎖国",
      "answer": "さこく",
      "meaning": "national isolation, closing the country (to foreigners), sakoku, policy of national isolation enacte"
    },
    {
      "question": "温室育ち",
      "answer": "おんしつそだち",
      "meaning": "sheltered upbringing, person who has had a sheltered upbringing, hothouse upbringing"
    },
    {
      "question": "才媛",
      "answer": "さいえん",
      "meaning": "literary woman, talented woman"
    },
    {
      "question": "戟",
      "answer": "ほこ,げき",
      "meaning": "long-handled Chinese spear, lance, pike, weapon, arms, grip of a bow, parade float decorated with lo"
    },
    {
      "question": "紀元前",
      "answer": "きげんぜん",
      "meaning": "pre-era, BC, BCE"
    },
    {
      "question": "便座",
      "answer": "べんざ",
      "meaning": "toilet seat"
    },
    {
      "question": "累計",
      "answer": "るいけい",
      "meaning": "cumulative total, accumulated total, total up to now"
    },
    {
      "question": "延髄",
      "answer": "えんずい",
      "meaning": "medulla oblongata"
    },
    {
      "question": "後追い",
      "answer": "あとおい",
      "meaning": "trailing, chasing after, imitation, copy"
    },
    {
      "question": "世捨て人",
      "answer": "よすてびと",
      "meaning": "hermit, recluse"
    },
    {
      "question": "形骸化",
      "answer": "けいがいか",
      "meaning": "becoming a mere shell, becoming a dead letter, losing (one's) substance, being reduced to a formalit"
    },
    {
      "question": "取り直す",
      "answer": "とりなおす",
      "meaning": "to re-grip, to re-wrestle, to regroup (after some adverse event)"
    },
    {
      "question": "育て",
      "answer": "そだて",
      "meaning": "bringing up, raising"
    },
    {
      "question": "足が向く",
      "answer": "あしがむく",
      "meaning": "to head towards, to be inclined to go towards, to head for a place naturally"
    },
    {
      "question": "天文台",
      "answer": "てんもんだい",
      "meaning": "astronomical observatory"
    },
    {
      "question": "年貢",
      "answer": "ねんぐ",
      "meaning": "annual tribute, land tax"
    },
    {
      "question": "合否",
      "answer": "ごうひ",
      "meaning": "success or failure, result"
    },
    {
      "question": "名分",
      "answer": "めいぶん",
      "meaning": "moral duty, moral obligations, justification, pretext, just cause"
    },
    {
      "question": "骨身",
      "answer": "ほねみ",
      "meaning": "flesh and bones"
    },
    {
      "question": "乱用",
      "answer": "らんよう",
      "meaning": "abuse, misuse, misappropriation, using to excess"
    },
    {
      "question": "皇宮",
      "answer": "こうぐう",
      "meaning": "the Imperial Palace"
    },
    {
      "question": "節分",
      "answer": "せつぶん,せちぶん,せちぶ",
      "meaning": "last day of winter in the traditional Japanese calendar (usually February 3 or 4), holiday for end o"
    },
    {
      "question": "製菓",
      "answer": "せいか",
      "meaning": "confectionery production, baking (e.g. pastries, sweets), confectionery"
    },
    {
      "question": "夜伽",
      "answer": "よとぎ",
      "meaning": "attending someone through the night (guard, nurse), act of a woman sleeping with a man (at his biddi"
    },
    {
      "question": "神経系",
      "answer": "しんけいけい",
      "meaning": "nervous system"
    },
    {
      "question": "日照り",
      "answer": "ひでり",
      "meaning": "dry weather, drought"
    },
    {
      "question": "減刑",
      "answer": "げんけい",
      "meaning": "reduction of penalty, commutation of a sentence"
    },
    {
      "question": "越境",
      "answer": "えっきょう",
      "meaning": "border transgression"
    },
    {
      "question": "桜吹雪",
      "answer": "さくらふぶき",
      "meaning": "blizzard of falling cherry blossoms, flurry of falling cherry blossoms"
    },
    {
      "question": "速射",
      "answer": "そくしゃ",
      "meaning": "quick firing, rapid firing"
    },
    {
      "question": "色調",
      "answer": "しきちょう",
      "meaning": "color tone, colour tone"
    },
    {
      "question": "圧死",
      "answer": "あっし",
      "meaning": "crushing to death"
    },
    {
      "question": "我を通す",
      "answer": "がをとおす",
      "meaning": "to insist on one's own ideas, to have one's own way"
    },
    {
      "question": "危篤",
      "answer": "きとく",
      "meaning": "critical condition, being on the verge of death"
    },
    {
      "question": "着艦",
      "answer": "ちゃっかん",
      "meaning": "landing on an aircraft carrier, deck-landing, reaching a warship, arrival of a warship (at a port)"
    },
    {
      "question": "増税",
      "answer": "ぞうぜい",
      "meaning": "tax increase"
    },
    {
      "question": "区内",
      "answer": "くない",
      "meaning": "in the ward or borough"
    },
    {
      "question": "静脈",
      "answer": "じょうみゃく",
      "meaning": "vein"
    },
    {
      "question": "外車",
      "answer": "がいしゃ",
      "meaning": "foreign-made car, imported car, paddle wheel"
    },
    {
      "question": "宗教家",
      "answer": "しゅうきょうか",
      "meaning": "religious leader, person of religion, religious figure, religionist"
    },
    {
      "question": "伽",
      "answer": "とぎ",
      "meaning": "nursing, nurse, attending, attendant, entertainer"
    },
    {
      "question": "制空権",
      "answer": "せいくうけん",
      "meaning": "control of the air, air supremacy"
    },
    {
      "question": "告訴",
      "answer": "こくそ",
      "meaning": "accusation, complaint, charge, legal action"
    },
    {
      "question": "全景",
      "answer": "ぜんけい",
      "meaning": "panoramic view, bird's-eye view"
    },
    {
      "question": "滑り出し",
      "answer": "すべりだし",
      "meaning": "start, beginning"
    },
    {
      "question": "雲雀",
      "answer": "ひばり",
      "meaning": "skylark (Alauda arvensis)"
    },
    {
      "question": "灌木",
      "answer": "かんぼく",
      "meaning": "bush, shrub"
    },
    {
      "question": "奇数",
      "answer": "きすう",
      "meaning": "odd number"
    },
    {
      "question": "狸寝入り",
      "answer": "たぬきねいり",
      "meaning": "feigning sleep"
    },
    {
      "question": "猛将",
      "answer": "もうしょう",
      "meaning": "brave general, brave warrior, courageous general"
    },
    {
      "question": "緒戦",
      "answer": "しょせん,ちょせん",
      "meaning": "beginning of hostilities, beginning of competition"
    },
    {
      "question": "点差",
      "answer": "てんさ",
      "meaning": "point spread, point difference"
    },
    {
      "question": "演出家",
      "answer": "えんしゅつか",
      "meaning": "producer, director"
    },
    {
      "question": "こそ泥",
      "answer": "こそどろ",
      "meaning": "sneak thief, petty thief, cat burglar"
    },
    {
      "question": "粗",
      "answer": "ほぼ,あら,そ",
      "meaning": "almost, roughly, approximately, remaining bony parts (of a fish after filleting), flaw (esp. of a pe"
    },
    {
      "question": "精密機械",
      "answer": "せいみつきかい",
      "meaning": "precision instrument or machine"
    },
    {
      "question": "無味乾燥",
      "answer": "むみかんそう",
      "meaning": "dull, uninteresting, dry, insipid, boring, prosaic"
    },
    {
      "question": "御簾",
      "answer": "みす,ぎょれん",
      "meaning": "bamboo blind"
    },
    {
      "question": "八王子",
      "answer": "はちおうじ",
      "meaning": "Hachiōji (city)"
    },
    {
      "question": "極細",
      "answer": "ごくぼそ",
      "meaning": "superfine, extra-fine, extremely thin, extra-fine woollen yarn"
    },
    {
      "question": "百科事典",
      "answer": "ひゃっかじてん",
      "meaning": "encyclopedia, encyclopaedia"
    },
    {
      "question": "産婦人科",
      "answer": "さんふじんか",
      "meaning": "maternity and gynaecology department (gynecology), department of obstetrics and gynaecology (gynecol"
    },
    {
      "question": "消毒薬",
      "answer": "しょうどくやく",
      "meaning": "disinfectant"
    },
    {
      "question": "病理",
      "answer": "びょうり",
      "meaning": "pathology"
    },
    {
      "question": "彦星",
      "answer": "ひこぼし",
      "meaning": "Altair (star in the constellation Aquila), Alpha Aquilae"
    },
    {
      "question": "古本",
      "answer": "ふるほん,ふるぼん,こほん",
      "meaning": "secondhand book, ancient book, antiquarian books"
    },
    {
      "question": "面会謝絶",
      "answer": "めんかいしゃぜつ",
      "meaning": "No Visitors"
    },
    {
      "question": "美的感覚",
      "answer": "びてきかんかく",
      "meaning": "aesthetic feeling, aesthetic sense, sense of beauty"
    },
    {
      "question": "美的",
      "answer": "びてき",
      "meaning": "esthetic, aesthetic"
    },
    {
      "question": "独立戦争",
      "answer": "どくりつせんそう",
      "meaning": "American Revolutionary War, War of Independence"
    },
    {
      "question": "睡い",
      "answer": "ねむい",
      "meaning": "sleepy, drowsy, somnolent"
    },
    {
      "question": "警視総監",
      "answer": "けいしそうかん",
      "meaning": "Superintendent General of the Metropolitan Police"
    },
    {
      "question": "追い縋る",
      "answer": "おいすがる",
      "meaning": "to be hot on a person's heels"
    },
    {
      "question": "キメ顔",
      "answer": "キメがお",
      "meaning": "posed look (chic, sexy, sultry, etc.), facial expression and orientation presented when being photog"
    },
    {
      "question": "脱臼",
      "answer": "だっきゅう",
      "meaning": "dislocation"
    },
    {
      "question": "浮き沈み",
      "answer": "うきしずみ",
      "meaning": "ups and downs, bobbing up and down, rising and falling, ebbing and flowing"
    },
    {
      "question": "竜車",
      "answer": "りゅうしゃ",
      "meaning": "imperial carriage, ryūsha, spherical part of a pagoda finial between the hōju and suien"
    },
    {
      "question": "民兵",
      "answer": "みんぺい",
      "meaning": "militia, militiaman"
    },
    {
      "question": "五行",
      "answer": "ごぎょう",
      "meaning": "the five elements (in Chinese philosophy: wood, fire, earth, metal and water), the five phases, wu x"
    },
    {
      "question": "商工",
      "answer": "しょうこう",
      "meaning": "commerce and industry"
    },
    {
      "question": "邪心",
      "answer": "じゃしん",
      "meaning": "wicked heart, evil design"
    },
    {
      "question": "開口部",
      "answer": "かいこうぶ",
      "meaning": "aperture"
    },
    {
      "question": "計量",
      "answer": "けいりょう",
      "meaning": "measuring, weighing, metric, distance function"
    },
    {
      "question": "財源",
      "answer": "ざいげん",
      "meaning": "source of funds, resources, finances"
    },
    {
      "question": "会頭",
      "answer": "かいとう",
      "meaning": "society president"
    },
    {
      "question": "黄昏れる",
      "answer": "たそがれる",
      "meaning": "to fade into dusk, to fade into twilight, to decline, to wane, to abate, to look melancholic (of a p"
    },
    {
      "question": "力抜け",
      "answer": "ちからぬけ",
      "meaning": "discouragement, disappointment"
    },
    {
      "question": "何処でも",
      "answer": "どこでも",
      "meaning": "anywhere"
    },
    {
      "question": "委任",
      "answer": "いにん",
      "meaning": "entrusting, charge, delegation, authorization"
    },
    {
      "question": "唐",
      "answer": "とう,もろこし,から",
      "meaning": "Tang dynasty (China, 618-907), T'ang dynasty, China, foreign country, Chinese, China (sometimes also"
    },
    {
      "question": "退行",
      "answer": "たいこう",
      "meaning": "retrogression, regression"
    },
    {
      "question": "干し草",
      "answer": "ほしくさ,ほしぐさ",
      "meaning": "hay, dry grass"
    },
    {
      "question": "羊肉",
      "answer": "ようにく",
      "meaning": "mutton, lamb (meat)"
    },
    {
      "question": "茫漠",
      "answer": "ぼうばく",
      "meaning": "vast, boundless, vague, obscure"
    },
    {
      "question": "賞状",
      "answer": "しょうじょう",
      "meaning": "honorable certificate, honourable certificate"
    },
    {
      "question": "積雪",
      "answer": "せきせつ",
      "meaning": "fallen snow, snow cover"
    },
    {
      "question": "晩秋",
      "answer": "ばんしゅう",
      "meaning": "late autumn (fall), ninth month of the lunar calendar"
    },
    {
      "question": "賃貸",
      "answer": "ちんたい",
      "meaning": "lease, rent, hire"
    },
    {
      "question": "駄目出し",
      "answer": "だめだし",
      "meaning": "criticizing, lambasting, pointing out faults, finding fault, calling for a retake, ordering (somebod"
    },
    {
      "question": "無人機",
      "answer": "むじんき",
      "meaning": "drone, unmanned aircraft"
    },
    {
      "question": "錐揉み",
      "answer": "きりもみ",
      "meaning": "tailspin, spin, drilling, boring"
    },
    {
      "question": "娘っ子",
      "answer": "むすめっこ",
      "meaning": "girl, lass, young thing, chick"
    },
    {
      "question": "暖色",
      "answer": "だんしょく",
      "meaning": "warm colour, warm color"
    },
    {
      "question": "霊視",
      "answer": "れいし",
      "meaning": "clairvoyance"
    },
    {
      "question": "遡行",
      "answer": "そこう",
      "meaning": "going upstream, sailing against the current"
    },
    {
      "question": "神性",
      "answer": "しんせい",
      "meaning": "divinity"
    },
    {
      "question": "草案",
      "answer": "そうあん",
      "meaning": "draft (for a speech, bill, etc.)"
    },
    {
      "question": "板書",
      "answer": "ばんしょ",
      "meaning": "(act of) writing on a blackboard"
    },
    {
      "question": "虫の音",
      "answer": "むしのね",
      "meaning": "calls and sounds made by insects"
    },
    {
      "question": "眼鏡越し",
      "answer": "めがねごし",
      "meaning": "(looking) over the top of one's glasses, (looking) through a pair of glasses"
    },
    {
      "question": "紛う",
      "answer": "まがう",
      "meaning": "to be mistaken for, to be confused with"
    },
    {
      "question": "定価",
      "answer": "ていか",
      "meaning": "list price, regular price, established price"
    },
    {
      "question": "時の人",
      "answer": "ときのひと",
      "meaning": "man of the hour, woman of the hour"
    },
    {
      "question": "買い出す",
      "answer": "かいだす",
      "meaning": "to begin purchasing, to purchase"
    },
    {
      "question": "棟梁",
      "answer": "とうりょう",
      "meaning": "central figure, pillar (e.g. of the nation), mainstay, chief support, leader, chief, boss, head, mas"
    },
    {
      "question": "群馬",
      "answer": "ぐんま",
      "meaning": "Gunma (prefecture)"
    },
    {
      "question": "薫る",
      "answer": "かおる",
      "meaning": "to smell sweet, to be fragrant"
    },
    {
      "question": "落着",
      "answer": "らくちゃく",
      "meaning": "being settled, coming to a conclusion"
    },
    {
      "question": "年号",
      "answer": "ねんごう",
      "meaning": "name of an imperial era (e.g. Heisei, Shōwa), Japanese era name"
    },
    {
      "question": "頭打ち",
      "answer": "あたまうち,ずうち",
      "meaning": "reaching a peak, reaching the limit, plateauing, maxing out"
    },
    {
      "question": "船出",
      "answer": "ふなで",
      "meaning": "setting sail, putting out to sea, starting anew, embarking on something new"
    },
    {
      "question": "ぶん回す",
      "answer": "ぶんまわす",
      "meaning": "to spin vigorously, to wave around (e.g. sword, bat)"
    },
    {
      "question": "絶対数",
      "answer": "ぜったいすう",
      "meaning": "number (on its own, without considering its proportion to the whole), overall number"
    },
    {
      "question": "匣",
      "answer": "はこ,くしげ",
      "meaning": "box, case, chest, package, pack, crate, car (of a train, etc.), shamisen case, shamisen, public buil"
    },
    {
      "question": "廃坑",
      "answer": "はいこう",
      "meaning": "abandoned mine, disused mine"
    },
    {
      "question": "連装",
      "answer": "れんそう",
      "meaning": "coaxial mounting, multiple mounting"
    },
    {
      "question": "絶対者",
      "answer": "ぜったいしゃ",
      "meaning": "the Absolute"
    },
    {
      "question": "パン粉",
      "answer": "パンこ",
      "meaning": "breadcrumbs, panko, bread flour"
    },
    {
      "question": "牧草",
      "answer": "ぼくそう",
      "meaning": "pasture, grass"
    },
    {
      "question": "勤労",
      "answer": "きんろう",
      "meaning": "labor, labour, exertion, diligent service"
    },
    {
      "question": "黒点",
      "answer": "こくてん",
      "meaning": "black spot, dark spot, sunspot"
    },
    {
      "question": "島内",
      "answer": "とうない",
      "meaning": "on an island, on-island"
    },
    {
      "question": "大凶",
      "answer": "だいきょう",
      "meaning": "terrible luck, very bad luck"
    },
    {
      "question": "自失",
      "answer": "じしつ",
      "meaning": "stupefaction"
    },
    {
      "question": "著書",
      "answer": "ちょしょ",
      "meaning": "(written) work, book, writings"
    },
    {
      "question": "数的",
      "answer": "すうてき,かずてき",
      "meaning": "numerical, quantitative"
    },
    {
      "question": "膝頭",
      "answer": "ひざがしら",
      "meaning": "kneecap"
    },
    {
      "question": "執行猶予",
      "answer": "しっこうゆうよ",
      "meaning": "stay of execution, suspended sentence"
    },
    {
      "question": "白を切る",
      "answer": "しらをきる",
      "meaning": "to feign ignorance, to pretend to be ignorant of, to play innocent, to brazen it out"
    },
    {
      "question": "往生",
      "answer": "おうじょう",
      "meaning": "passing on to the next life, death, giving up a struggle, submission, being at one's wits' end, bein"
    },
    {
      "question": "四面楚歌",
      "answer": "しめんそか",
      "meaning": "being surrounded by enemies on all sides, being betrayed (forsaken) by everybody"
    },
    {
      "question": "御門",
      "answer": "みかど,ごもん",
      "meaning": "emperor (of Japan), mikado, (the gates of an) imperial residence"
    },
    {
      "question": "戦闘艦",
      "answer": "せんとうかん",
      "meaning": "combat ship, combat vessel"
    },
    {
      "question": "晴れ着",
      "answer": "はれぎ",
      "meaning": "(one's) Sunday best, (one's) best clothes, glad rags"
    },
    {
      "question": "靴屋",
      "answer": "くつや",
      "meaning": "shoe store, shoe shop, shoemaker"
    },
    {
      "question": "開帳",
      "answer": "かいちょう",
      "meaning": "unveiling a Buddhist image, public exhibition (of a Buddhist image), revealing something that is sup"
    },
    {
      "question": "免許皆伝",
      "answer": "めんきょかいでん",
      "meaning": "possessing full mastery of an art (e.g. Judo), initiation into the secrets (e.g. of an art), full ma"
    },
    {
      "question": "捨て石",
      "answer": "すていし",
      "meaning": "ornamental garden stone (seemingly placed randomly to give the garden a more natural appearance), ga"
    },
    {
      "question": "世帯",
      "answer": "せたい,しょたい",
      "meaning": "household, home, family, housekeeping"
    },
    {
      "question": "瓶詰め",
      "answer": "びんづめ",
      "meaning": "bottling, bottled"
    },
    {
      "question": "離れ業",
      "answer": "はなれわざ",
      "meaning": "stunt, feat"
    },
    {
      "question": "馬鹿話",
      "answer": "ばかばなし",
      "meaning": "foolish talk"
    },
    {
      "question": "公社",
      "answer": "こうしゃ",
      "meaning": "public corporation"
    },
    {
      "question": "閣僚",
      "answer": "かくりょう",
      "meaning": "cabinet ministers"
    },
    {
      "question": "募金",
      "answer": "ぼきん",
      "meaning": "fund-raising, collection of funds"
    },
    {
      "question": "珍",
      "answer": "ちん",
      "meaning": "rare, strange, odd, peculiar, curious"
    },
    {
      "question": "木枯らし",
      "answer": "こがらし",
      "meaning": "cold wintry wind"
    },
    {
      "question": "奇想天外",
      "answer": "きそうてんがい",
      "meaning": "fantastic, bizarre, incredible, unbelievable"
    },
    {
      "question": "振り分け",
      "answer": "ふりわけ",
      "meaning": "divide, parting, separating, distribution, carrying two bundles tied together over one's shoulder, h"
    },
    {
      "question": "近江",
      "answer": "おうみ",
      "meaning": "Ōmi (former province located in present-day Shiga Prefecture)"
    },
    {
      "question": "敵手",
      "answer": "てきしゅ",
      "meaning": "rival, enemy"
    },
    {
      "question": "議場",
      "answer": "ぎじょう",
      "meaning": "assembly hall, the House"
    },
    {
      "question": "三等",
      "answer": "さんとう",
      "meaning": "third class"
    },
    {
      "question": "国会議員",
      "answer": "こっかいぎいん",
      "meaning": "member of the Diet, Diet member, member of parliament, MP"
    },
    {
      "question": "咽せる",
      "answer": "むせる",
      "meaning": "to choke, to be choked by, to be stifled by"
    },
    {
      "question": "瀬戸",
      "answer": "せと",
      "meaning": "strait, channel"
    },
    {
      "question": "星雲",
      "answer": "せいうん",
      "meaning": "nebula, galaxy"
    },
    {
      "question": "成層圏",
      "answer": "せいそうけん",
      "meaning": "stratosphere"
    },
    {
      "question": "選曲",
      "answer": "せんきょく",
      "meaning": "selection of music, song selection"
    },
    {
      "question": "魘される",
      "answer": "うなされる",
      "meaning": "to have a nightmare, to make a noise during a nightmare"
    },
    {
      "question": "憂い顔",
      "answer": "うれいがお",
      "meaning": "sad face, sorrowful face, anxious look, sad countenance"
    },
    {
      "question": "実像",
      "answer": "じつぞう",
      "meaning": "real image, real form, real-life image, true picture, actual conditions, actual circumstances"
    },
    {
      "question": "昴",
      "answer": "すばる,すまる,ぼう",
      "meaning": "Chinese 'Hairy Head' constellation (one of the 28 mansions), Pleiades, Seven Sisters"
    },
    {
      "question": "徳利",
      "answer": "とっくり,とくり",
      "meaning": "sake bottle, tall and slender bottle with a narrow mouth made from ceramic, metal or glass that can"
    },
    {
      "question": "警察手帳",
      "answer": "けいさつてちょう",
      "meaning": "police identification card"
    },
    {
      "question": "駄弁る",
      "answer": "だべる",
      "meaning": "to jabber, to chatter, to chat with"
    },
    {
      "question": "擦過",
      "answer": "さっか",
      "meaning": "abrasion, scrape, graze, paratripsis"
    },
    {
      "question": "渓流",
      "answer": "けいりゅう",
      "meaning": "mountain stream, mountain torrent"
    },
    {
      "question": "腐葉土",
      "answer": "ふようど",
      "meaning": "humus, leaf mold, leaf mould, mulch"
    },
    {
      "question": "付録",
      "answer": "ふろく",
      "meaning": "appendix, supplement, annex, extra (of a newspaper or magazine)"
    },
    {
      "question": "愁い",
      "answer": "うれい",
      "meaning": "sorrow, grief, anguish, distress, trouble, affliction, anxiety, fear, misgivings"
    },
    {
      "question": "不確実",
      "answer": "ふかくじつ",
      "meaning": "uncertain, unreliable, inauthentic, insecure"
    },
    {
      "question": "追悼",
      "answer": "ついとう",
      "meaning": "mourning (dead persons), memorial"
    },
    {
      "question": "長細い",
      "answer": "ながほそい",
      "meaning": "long and thin"
    },
    {
      "question": "高慢ちき",
      "answer": "こうまんちき",
      "meaning": "arrogant, haughty, stuck-up, arrogant bastard, snob"
    },
    {
      "question": "門を叩く",
      "answer": "もんをたたく",
      "meaning": "to knock at the gate, to request an apprenticeship, to ask to be made a pupil"
    },
    {
      "question": "鉄拳制裁",
      "answer": "てっけんせいさい",
      "meaning": "(punishment by) striking with fists"
    },
    {
      "question": "高を括る",
      "answer": "たかをくくる",
      "meaning": "to underrate, to make light of"
    },
    {
      "question": "国連軍",
      "answer": "こくれんぐん",
      "meaning": "UN forces, UN troops"
    },
    {
      "question": "真言",
      "answer": "しんごん",
      "meaning": "mantra, Shingon sect (of Buddhism)"
    },
    {
      "question": "拘置所",
      "answer": "こうちしょ",
      "meaning": "prison, detention house, detention center, jail"
    },
    {
      "question": "保育士",
      "answer": "ほいくし",
      "meaning": "nursery school teacher, childcare worker"
    },
    {
      "question": "夕空",
      "answer": "ゆうぞら",
      "meaning": "evening sky, twilight sky"
    },
    {
      "question": "更正",
      "answer": "こうせい",
      "meaning": "correction, revision, rectification"
    },
    {
      "question": "鉄砲玉",
      "answer": "てっぽうだま",
      "meaning": "gunshot, bullet, lost messenger, truant messenger, non-returner, bull's-eye (candy)"
    },
    {
      "question": "格下げ",
      "answer": "かくさげ",
      "meaning": "demotion, downgrading"
    },
    {
      "question": "気骨",
      "answer": "きこつ,きぼね",
      "meaning": "(moral) backbone, spirit, soul, grit, worry, care, anxiety"
    },
    {
      "question": "法規",
      "answer": "ほうき",
      "meaning": "laws and regulations, legislation"
    },
    {
      "question": "現実化",
      "answer": "げんじつか",
      "meaning": "realization, realisation"
    },
    {
      "question": "十三日",
      "answer": "じゅうさんにち",
      "meaning": "thirteenth day of the month, thirteen days"
    },
    {
      "question": "紫水晶",
      "answer": "むらさきずいしょう,むらさきすいしょう",
      "meaning": "amethyst"
    },
    {
      "question": "履修",
      "answer": "りしゅう",
      "meaning": "taking a class, studying a subject, completing a course"
    },
    {
      "question": "防災",
      "answer": "ぼうさい",
      "meaning": "disaster preparedness, prevention of damage resulting from a natural disaster, protection against di"
    },
    {
      "question": "後日談",
      "answer": "ごじつだん",
      "meaning": "sequel, later development"
    },
    {
      "question": "刑期",
      "answer": "けいき",
      "meaning": "prison term"
    },
    {
      "question": "差し障り",
      "answer": "さしさわり",
      "meaning": "offence, offense, hindrance"
    },
    {
      "question": "研修医",
      "answer": "けんしゅうい",
      "meaning": "medical intern, resident"
    },
    {
      "question": "軍旗",
      "answer": "ぐんき",
      "meaning": "battle flag, standard, (regimental) colours, colors, ensign"
    },
    {
      "question": "平仮名",
      "answer": "ひらがな",
      "meaning": "hiragana, cursive Japanese syllabary used primarily for native Japanese words (esp. function words,"
    },
    {
      "question": "出火",
      "answer": "しゅっか",
      "meaning": "outbreak of fire"
    },
    {
      "question": "掃き掃除",
      "answer": "はきそうじ",
      "meaning": "sweeping and cleaning"
    },
    {
      "question": "残金",
      "answer": "ざんきん",
      "meaning": "remaining money"
    },
    {
      "question": "百点満点",
      "answer": "ひゃくてんまんてん",
      "meaning": "(getting a) perfect score, scoring 100, grading students on a scale of one hundred, doing perfectly"
    },
    {
      "question": "前祝い",
      "answer": "まえいわい",
      "meaning": "advance celebration"
    },
    {
      "question": "荒れ放題",
      "answer": "あれほうだい",
      "meaning": "left in a state of neglect, left to go to ruin, left to run wild (e.g. of a garden)"
    },
    {
      "question": "足袋",
      "answer": "たび",
      "meaning": "tabi, Japanese socks (with split toe)"
    },
    {
      "question": "冬季",
      "answer": "とうき",
      "meaning": "(season of) winter"
    },
    {
      "question": "省エネ",
      "answer": "しょうエネ",
      "meaning": "energy conservation, economical use of energy"
    },
    {
      "question": "自席",
      "answer": "じせき",
      "meaning": "one's seat, one's desk"
    },
    {
      "question": "流行り病",
      "answer": "はやりやまい",
      "meaning": "epidemic"
    },
    {
      "question": "音階",
      "answer": "おんかい",
      "meaning": "scale"
    },
    {
      "question": "手向ける",
      "answer": "たむける",
      "meaning": "to offer something to a deity or somebody's spirit, to pay a tribute to a person who is about to dep"
    },
    {
      "question": "意欲的",
      "answer": "いよくてき",
      "meaning": "ambitious, motivated, willful"
    },
    {
      "question": "巡査部長",
      "answer": "じゅんさぶちょう",
      "meaning": "police sergeant"
    },
    {
      "question": "望遠",
      "answer": "ぼうえん",
      "meaning": "seeing at a distance"
    },
    {
      "question": "退かす",
      "answer": "どかす",
      "meaning": "to remove, to move out of the way"
    },
    {
      "question": "七面鳥",
      "answer": "しちめんちょう",
      "meaning": "turkey (Meleagris gallopavo)"
    },
    {
      "question": "子守り",
      "answer": "こもり",
      "meaning": "nursemaid, nanny, babysitter, child-minding, babysitting"
    },
    {
      "question": "所蔵",
      "answer": "しょぞう",
      "meaning": "(in one's) possession"
    },
    {
      "question": "内向的",
      "answer": "ないこうてき",
      "meaning": "introverted, withdrawn"
    },
    {
      "question": "廊",
      "answer": "ろう",
      "meaning": "corridor, passage, hall"
    },
    {
      "question": "跳ね橋",
      "answer": "はねばし",
      "meaning": "drawbridge"
    },
    {
      "question": "船倉",
      "answer": "せんそう,ふなぐら",
      "meaning": "ship's hold, hatch, boathouse"
    },
    {
      "question": "仕立屋",
      "answer": "したてや",
      "meaning": "tailor, dressmaker"
    },
    {
      "question": "朝靄",
      "answer": "あさもや",
      "meaning": "morning mist"
    },
    {
      "question": "星霜",
      "answer": "せいそう,せいぞう",
      "meaning": "years, time"
    },
    {
      "question": "穀潰し",
      "answer": "ごくつぶし",
      "meaning": "good-for-nothing, parasite, deadbeat, loafer, drone, idler"
    },
    {
      "question": "対角線",
      "answer": "たいかくせん",
      "meaning": "diagonal (line)"
    },
    {
      "question": "分かれ目",
      "answer": "わかれめ",
      "meaning": "fork, junction, parting of the ways, turning point"
    },
    {
      "question": "釣り堀",
      "answer": "つりぼり",
      "meaning": "fish pond (artificially stocked), fishing pond"
    },
    {
      "question": "麦酒",
      "answer": "ばくしゅ",
      "meaning": "beer"
    },
    {
      "question": "交換日記",
      "answer": "こうかんにっき",
      "meaning": "exchanging diary between friends (usually at school)"
    },
    {
      "question": "尾根",
      "answer": "おね",
      "meaning": "(mountain) ridge"
    },
    {
      "question": "探究",
      "answer": "たんきゅう",
      "meaning": "research, investigation, enquiry, inquiry, study"
    },
    {
      "question": "生産力",
      "answer": "せいさんりょく",
      "meaning": "productivity"
    },
    {
      "question": "老害",
      "answer": "ろうがい",
      "meaning": "problems caused by the elderly (esp. gerontocracy, and elderly people's control over the young)"
    },
    {
      "question": "流線型",
      "answer": "りゅうせんけい",
      "meaning": "streamline shape, aerodynamic shape"
    },
    {
      "question": "某国",
      "answer": "ぼうこく",
      "meaning": "certain country"
    },
    {
      "question": "副次的",
      "answer": "ふくじてき",
      "meaning": "secondary"
    },
    {
      "question": "子煩悩",
      "answer": "こぼんのう",
      "meaning": "cherishing one's children, doting, adoring parent"
    },
    {
      "question": "記念祭",
      "answer": "きねんさい",
      "meaning": "anniversary, commemoration"
    },
    {
      "question": "僕等",
      "answer": "ぼくら",
      "meaning": "we"
    },
    {
      "question": "夏季",
      "answer": "かき,なつき",
      "meaning": "summer season"
    },
    {
      "question": "尽かす",
      "answer": "つかす",
      "meaning": "to use completely, to use up, to exhaust, to exhaust somebody's civility, to give up (on someone)"
    },
    {
      "question": "序",
      "answer": "ついで,じょ",
      "meaning": "opportunity, occasion, chance, order, sequence, successor, ordering, beginning, start, foreword, pre"
    },
    {
      "question": "快速",
      "answer": "かいそく",
      "meaning": "high speed, rapidity, rapid-service train (not as fast as express), rapid train"
    },
    {
      "question": "往路",
      "answer": "おうろ",
      "meaning": "outward journey"
    },
    {
      "question": "目端",
      "answer": "めはし",
      "meaning": "quick-wittedness, having tact, being sensible"
    },
    {
      "question": "涼風",
      "answer": "りょうふう,すずかぜ",
      "meaning": "cool breeze, refreshing breeze"
    },
    {
      "question": "場当たり",
      "answer": "ばあたり",
      "meaning": "playing to the gallery, grandstanding, gag, claptrap, ad hoc, haphazard, dress rehearsal"
    },
    {
      "question": "流動的",
      "answer": "りゅうどうてき",
      "meaning": "fluid, unsettled"
    },
    {
      "question": "既婚",
      "answer": "きこん",
      "meaning": "married"
    },
    {
      "question": "北欧神話",
      "answer": "ほくおうしんわ",
      "meaning": "Norse mythology"
    },
    {
      "question": "走狗",
      "answer": "そうく",
      "meaning": "hound, hunting dog, running dog, dupe, tool of another person, cat's-paw"
    },
    {
      "question": "斟酌",
      "answer": "しんしゃく",
      "meaning": "consideration (for others), (making) allowance"
    },
    {
      "question": "連名",
      "answer": "れんめい",
      "meaning": "joint signature"
    },
    {
      "question": "黙秘権",
      "answer": "もくひけん",
      "meaning": "right to keep silent, right to silence, right to remain silent"
    },
    {
      "question": "差し引き",
      "answer": "さしひき",
      "meaning": "deduction, subtraction, balance, ebb and flow, rise and fall"
    },
    {
      "question": "画質",
      "answer": "がしつ",
      "meaning": "image quality (film, video, etc.)"
    },
    {
      "question": "油を注ぐ",
      "answer": "あぶらをそそぐ",
      "meaning": "to pour oil on (something), to anoint with oil, to turn up, to add fuel (e.g. to a dispute), to rev"
    },
    {
      "question": "全損",
      "answer": "ぜんそん",
      "meaning": "total loss"
    },
    {
      "question": "アル中",
      "answer": "アルちゅう",
      "meaning": "alcoholism"
    },
    {
      "question": "勢力圏",
      "answer": "せいりょくけん",
      "meaning": "sphere of influence"
    },
    {
      "question": "支度金",
      "answer": "したくきん",
      "meaning": "money to cover the cost of preparations or arrangements"
    },
    {
      "question": "質す",
      "answer": "ただす",
      "meaning": "to enquire of someone about something (inquire), to question"
    },
    {
      "question": "横座り",
      "answer": "よこずわり",
      "meaning": "sitting with one's legs out to one side"
    },
    {
      "question": "落ち窪む",
      "answer": "おちくぼむ",
      "meaning": "to sink in, to cave in"
    },
    {
      "question": "著作",
      "answer": "ちょさく",
      "meaning": "writing, book"
    },
    {
      "question": "長じる",
      "answer": "ちょうじる",
      "meaning": "to grow, to grow up, to be good at, to excel in"
    },
    {
      "question": "目白押し",
      "answer": "めじろおし",
      "meaning": "jostling, milling about, crush, being jammed together, packed with (activities, products, etc.), tee"
    },
    {
      "question": "牛車",
      "answer": "ぎゅうしゃ,ぎっしゃ,うしぐるま",
      "meaning": "ox carriage (for Heian era nobles), oxcart"
    },
    {
      "question": "心電図",
      "answer": "しんでんず",
      "meaning": "electrocardiogram, ECG, EKG"
    },
    {
      "question": "ラテン語",
      "answer": "ラテンご",
      "meaning": "Latin (language)"
    },
    {
      "question": "住民票",
      "answer": "じゅうみんひょう",
      "meaning": "certificate of residence"
    },
    {
      "question": "治外法権",
      "answer": "ちがいほうけん",
      "meaning": "extraterritoriality"
    },
    {
      "question": "煩雑",
      "answer": "はんざつ",
      "meaning": "complex, intricate, complicated, confused, troublesome, vexatious, cumbersome"
    },
    {
      "question": "身持ち",
      "answer": "みもち",
      "meaning": "conduct, behavior, behaviour, being pregnant"
    },
    {
      "question": "継ぎ足す",
      "answer": "つぎたす",
      "meaning": "to extend (e.g. a house), to add to (e.g. coals to a fire)"
    },
    {
      "question": "自由都市",
      "answer": "じゆうとし",
      "meaning": "free city (of Germany), commune (of medieval Europe)"
    },
    {
      "question": "方舟",
      "answer": "はこぶね",
      "meaning": "ark (i.e. Noah's)"
    },
    {
      "question": "青竜",
      "answer": "せいりょう,しょうりょう,せいりゅう",
      "meaning": "blue dragon (an auspicious creature in Chinese mythology), Azure Dragon (god said to rule over the e"
    },
    {
      "question": "島民",
      "answer": "とうみん",
      "meaning": "islander"
    },
    {
      "question": "印税",
      "answer": "いんぜい",
      "meaning": "royalty (on book)"
    },
    {
      "question": "本年度",
      "answer": "ほんねんど",
      "meaning": "current year (fiscal, academic, etc.)"
    },
    {
      "question": "飲食物",
      "answer": "いんしょくぶつ",
      "meaning": "food and drink"
    },
    {
      "question": "見栄張る",
      "answer": "みえばる",
      "meaning": "to be pretentious, to put on airs"
    },
    {
      "question": "芸者",
      "answer": "げいしゃ",
      "meaning": "geisha, professional female entertainer, usu. at traditional banquets"
    },
    {
      "question": "軍法会議",
      "answer": "ぐんぽうかいぎ",
      "meaning": "court-martial"
    },
    {
      "question": "手に手に",
      "answer": "てにてに",
      "meaning": "each (carrying)"
    },
    {
      "question": "空前絶後",
      "answer": "くうぜんぜつご",
      "meaning": "(so marvelous or horrible that it may be) the first and probably the last"
    },
    {
      "question": "小心",
      "answer": "しょうしん",
      "meaning": "timidity, cowardice, prudence, pedantry"
    },
    {
      "question": "生活力",
      "answer": "せいかつりょく",
      "meaning": "vitality, ability to earn a living"
    },
    {
      "question": "杏子",
      "answer": "あんず",
      "meaning": "apricot (Prunus armeniaca)"
    },
    {
      "question": "金賞",
      "answer": "きんしょう",
      "meaning": "gold (first-place) prize"
    },
    {
      "question": "珍奇",
      "answer": "ちんき",
      "meaning": "strange, rare, novel, curious"
    },
    {
      "question": "禁欲",
      "answer": "きんよく",
      "meaning": "abstinence, self-control, celibacy, abnegation, asceticism"
    },
    {
      "question": "縄跳び",
      "answer": "なわとび",
      "meaning": "skipping rope, jump rope, skipping, rope-jumping"
    },
    {
      "question": "偽証",
      "answer": "ぎしょう",
      "meaning": "false evidence, perjury, false testimony"
    },
    {
      "question": "土着",
      "answer": "どちゃく",
      "meaning": "indigenousness, being native (to a region), settling (of people), native, indigenous, aboriginal"
    },
    {
      "question": "逐次",
      "answer": "ちくじ",
      "meaning": "successively, one after another, sequentially, one by one"
    },
    {
      "question": "腰骨",
      "answer": "こしぼね",
      "meaning": "hipbone, innominate bone, fortitude, perseverance, endurance, persistence"
    },
    {
      "question": "愛読",
      "answer": "あいどく",
      "meaning": "reading with pleasure"
    },
    {
      "question": "下向き",
      "answer": "したむき",
      "meaning": "pointing down, pointing downward, (market) decline, downturn, downward trend"
    },
    {
      "question": "単眼",
      "answer": "たんがん",
      "meaning": "one eye"
    },
    {
      "question": "柏",
      "answer": "かしわ",
      "meaning": "oak, daimyo oak, Japanese emperor oak, Quercus dentata"
    },
    {
      "question": "造船",
      "answer": "ぞうせん",
      "meaning": "shipbuilding"
    },
    {
      "question": "秘法",
      "answer": "ひほう",
      "meaning": "secret formula, secret process"
    },
    {
      "question": "百姓",
      "answer": "ひゃくしょう,ひゃくせい,おおみたから",
      "meaning": "farmer, peasant, country bumpkin, farming, the common people, imperial subjects, the people"
    },
    {
      "question": "委譲",
      "answer": "いじょう",
      "meaning": "transfer, assignment"
    },
    {
      "question": "湧き立つ",
      "answer": "わきたつ",
      "meaning": "to appear suddenly"
    },
    {
      "question": "桂馬",
      "answer": "けいま",
      "meaning": "knight, keima (in go), knight's move, stone placed at a knight's jump from another stone of the same"
    },
    {
      "question": "成虫",
      "answer": "せいちゅう",
      "meaning": "imago, adult (insect)"
    },
    {
      "question": "係数",
      "answer": "けいすう",
      "meaning": "coefficient, factor, proportional constant"
    },
    {
      "question": "招来",
      "answer": "しょうらい",
      "meaning": "invitation, bringing over, bringing about, giving rise to, causing, incurring"
    },
    {
      "question": "断ち割る",
      "answer": "たちわる",
      "meaning": "to cut open, to cut apart, to divide, to split"
    },
    {
      "question": "祝言",
      "answer": "しゅうげん,いわいごと",
      "meaning": "festivities, celebration, wedding, marriage ceremony, congratulatory words, prayer for happiness"
    },
    {
      "question": "一語",
      "answer": "いちご",
      "meaning": "one word"
    },
    {
      "question": "門柱",
      "answer": "もんちゅう",
      "meaning": "gatepost, pier"
    },
    {
      "question": "耳年増",
      "answer": "みみどしま",
      "meaning": "young woman with a lot of superficial knowledge about sex, etc."
    },
    {
      "question": "天文学",
      "answer": "てんもんがく",
      "meaning": "astronomy"
    },
    {
      "question": "過密",
      "answer": "かみつ",
      "meaning": "overcrowding, crowded, congestion"
    },
    {
      "question": "頭取",
      "answer": "とうどり",
      "meaning": "(bank) president, greenroom manager (in a theater)"
    },
    {
      "question": "老爺",
      "answer": "おやじ,ろうや",
      "meaning": "one's father, old man, one's boss"
    },
    {
      "question": "仕合",
      "answer": "しあい",
      "meaning": "match, game, bout, contest"
    },
    {
      "question": "手許",
      "answer": "てもと",
      "meaning": "at hand, on hand, nearby, close at hand, way of moving one's arms, skill, money at hand, pocket mone"
    },
    {
      "question": "神学",
      "answer": "しんがく",
      "meaning": "theology"
    },
    {
      "question": "湖水",
      "answer": "こすい",
      "meaning": "lake"
    },
    {
      "question": "戴冠",
      "answer": "たいかん",
      "meaning": "coronation, crowning"
    },
    {
      "question": "甲虫",
      "answer": "かぶとむし,こうちゅう",
      "meaning": "rhinoceros beetle (esp. the Japanese rhinoceros beetle, Trypoxylus dichotomus), beetle"
    },
    {
      "question": "公募",
      "answer": "こうぼ",
      "meaning": "public appeal (e.g. for contributions), public offering (of securities), public advertisement (of a"
    },
    {
      "question": "塗布",
      "answer": "とふ",
      "meaning": "application (of ointment), coating"
    },
    {
      "question": "販路",
      "answer": "はんろ",
      "meaning": "market (for goods, services, etc.), outlet (for selling), opening"
    },
    {
      "question": "供給源",
      "answer": "きょうきゅうげん",
      "meaning": "source of supply"
    },
    {
      "question": "腕組",
      "answer": "うでぐみ",
      "meaning": "folding one's arms"
    },
    {
      "question": "寮監",
      "answer": "りょうかん",
      "meaning": "housemaster, resident advisor, houseparent, housefather, housemother, dorm parent"
    },
    {
      "question": "鹵獲",
      "answer": "ろかく",
      "meaning": "capture (of enemy weapons, supplies, etc.), seizure, plunder"
    },
    {
      "question": "服役",
      "answer": "ふくえき",
      "meaning": "penal servitude, serving time in prison, military service, forced labor, compulsory service"
    },
    {
      "question": "究める",
      "answer": "きわめる",
      "meaning": "to carry to extremes, to go to the end of something, to investigate thoroughly, to master"
    },
    {
      "question": "具体性",
      "answer": "ぐたいせい",
      "meaning": "concreteness, feasibility"
    },
    {
      "question": "総裁",
      "answer": "そうさい",
      "meaning": "president (of an organization), director general, governor (of a central bank), party leader (esp. L"
    },
    {
      "question": "官職",
      "answer": "かんしょく",
      "meaning": "government service, official position, civil service"
    },
    {
      "question": "異国人",
      "answer": "いこくじん",
      "meaning": "foreigner, stranger, outsider, alien"
    },
    {
      "question": "毎秒",
      "answer": "まいびょう",
      "meaning": "every second"
    },
    {
      "question": "小熊",
      "answer": "こぐま",
      "meaning": "small bear, bear cub"
    },
    {
      "question": "小松",
      "answer": "こまつ",
      "meaning": "small pine, young pine"
    },
    {
      "question": "括約筋",
      "answer": "かつやくきん",
      "meaning": "sphincter, sphincter muscle, constrictor"
    },
    {
      "question": "瘤",
      "answer": "こぶ",
      "meaning": "bump, lump, protuberance, swelling"
    },
    {
      "question": "縞模様",
      "answer": "しまもよう",
      "meaning": "striped pattern"
    },
    {
      "question": "帰する",
      "answer": "きする",
      "meaning": "to come to (in the end), to end in, to attribute, to blame"
    },
    {
      "question": "慰み",
      "answer": "なぐさみ",
      "meaning": "amusement, diversion (to pass time), pastime, recreation"
    },
    {
      "question": "死語",
      "answer": "しご",
      "meaning": "dead language, extinct language, obsolete word, word that has become passé"
    },
    {
      "question": "消臭",
      "answer": "しょうしゅう",
      "meaning": "deodorization"
    },
    {
      "question": "跡目",
      "answer": "あとめ",
      "meaning": "headship of a family, family property"
    },
    {
      "question": "鎧う",
      "answer": "よろう",
      "meaning": "to put on armour (armor), to wear armour, to arm oneself, to wear, to cover"
    },
    {
      "question": "藪の中",
      "answer": "やぶのなか",
      "meaning": "inability to discern the truth due to conflicting testimony"
    },
    {
      "question": "意思決定",
      "answer": "いしけってい",
      "meaning": "decision-making"
    },
    {
      "question": "後払い",
      "answer": "あとばらい,ごばらい",
      "meaning": "deferred payment"
    },
    {
      "question": "土人形",
      "answer": "つちにんぎょう",
      "meaning": "clay doll, clay figure, clay figurine"
    },
    {
      "question": "振興",
      "answer": "しんこう",
      "meaning": "promotion, encouragement"
    },
    {
      "question": "述懐",
      "answer": "じゅっかい",
      "meaning": "speaking about (one's thoughts, memories, etc.), relating (one's feelings, reminiscences, etc.), rec"
    },
    {
      "question": "毒虫",
      "answer": "どくむし",
      "meaning": "poisonous insect"
    },
    {
      "question": "容積",
      "answer": "ようせき",
      "meaning": "capacity, volume"
    },
    {
      "question": "負け組",
      "answer": "まけぐみ",
      "meaning": "losers (those who have 'failed' socially, economically, etc.)"
    },
    {
      "question": "診断書",
      "answer": "しんだんしょ",
      "meaning": "medical certificate"
    },
    {
      "question": "旅慣れる",
      "answer": "たびなれる",
      "meaning": "to be accustomed to traveling (travelling)"
    },
    {
      "question": "滑り出す",
      "answer": "すべりだす",
      "meaning": "to begin slipping or sliding, to make a start upon"
    },
    {
      "question": "次善",
      "answer": "じぜん",
      "meaning": "second best"
    },
    {
      "question": "組織力",
      "answer": "そしきりょく",
      "meaning": "organizational capability, organisational capability"
    },
    {
      "question": "護国",
      "answer": "ごこく",
      "meaning": "defense of one's country, defence of one's country"
    },
    {
      "question": "容",
      "answer": "かたち,よう,かんばせ",
      "meaning": "form, shape, figure, visage, countenance, face, honor (honour), dignity"
    },
    {
      "question": "汚濁",
      "answer": "おだく",
      "meaning": "pollution, contamination, corruption, graft"
    },
    {
      "question": "辞去",
      "answer": "じきょ",
      "meaning": "leaving, quitting, retiring"
    },
    {
      "question": "会費",
      "answer": "かいひ",
      "meaning": "membership fee"
    },
    {
      "question": "小気味",
      "answer": "こきみ,こきび",
      "meaning": "sentiment, feeling"
    },
    {
      "question": "発破",
      "answer": "はっぱ",
      "meaning": "explosive blast (in construction, mining, etc.), blasting"
    },
    {
      "question": "織り成す",
      "answer": "おりなす",
      "meaning": "to interweave"
    },
    {
      "question": "同名",
      "answer": "どうめい,どうみょう",
      "meaning": "same name, homonym"
    },
    {
      "question": "凍え死ぬ",
      "answer": "こごえしぬ,こごえじぬ",
      "meaning": "to freeze to death, to die of cold"
    },
    {
      "question": "方陣",
      "answer": "ほうじん",
      "meaning": "square formation (of troops), magic square"
    },
    {
      "question": "機動部隊",
      "answer": "きどうぶたい",
      "meaning": "mobile troops, mechanized unit, mechanised unit, naval task force"
    },
    {
      "question": "中衛",
      "answer": "ちゅうえい",
      "meaning": "middle guard, halfback (e.g. football), center forward (e.g. volleyball), centre forward"
    },
    {
      "question": "太陽神",
      "answer": "たいようしん",
      "meaning": "sun god"
    },
    {
      "question": "陣容",
      "answer": "じんよう",
      "meaning": "battle formation, battle array, lineup (of a team, etc.), cast, staff, team structure"
    },
    {
      "question": "清書",
      "answer": "せいしょ",
      "meaning": "fair copy, clean copy"
    },
    {
      "question": "戦歴",
      "answer": "せんれき",
      "meaning": "military service, combat experience"
    },
    {
      "question": "故事",
      "answer": "こじ",
      "meaning": "historical event, ancient event, tradition, folklore, legend, origin"
    },
    {
      "question": "肩身",
      "answer": "かたみ",
      "meaning": "shoulders, body, honour, honor, prestige, face"
    },
    {
      "question": "拙僧",
      "answer": "せっそう",
      "meaning": "I, as a mere priest, this humble servant of Buddha"
    },
    {
      "question": "家元",
      "answer": "いえもと",
      "meaning": "head of a school (of music, dance), head family of a school"
    },
    {
      "question": "調薬",
      "answer": "ちょうやく",
      "meaning": "dose"
    },
    {
      "question": "薩摩",
      "answer": "さつま",
      "meaning": "Satsuma (former province located in the west of present-day Kagoshima Prefecture), sweet potato (Ipo"
    },
    {
      "question": "兵役",
      "answer": "へいえき",
      "meaning": "military service, conscription"
    },
    {
      "question": "奴隷制度",
      "answer": "どれいせいど",
      "meaning": "slavery"
    },
    {
      "question": "穏和",
      "answer": "おんわ",
      "meaning": "gentle (nature, personality, etc.), mild, quiet, pleasant, moderate (statement, measure, etc.), temp"
    },
    {
      "question": "後発",
      "answer": "こうはつ",
      "meaning": "starting late, late departure"
    },
    {
      "question": "焼き色",
      "answer": "やきいろ",
      "meaning": "brown colour (created by roasting or firing)"
    },
    {
      "question": "血の巡り",
      "answer": "ちのめぐり",
      "meaning": "circulation of the blood, apprehension"
    },
    {
      "question": "生活水準",
      "answer": "せいかつすいじゅん",
      "meaning": "standard of living"
    },
    {
      "question": "孤軍奮闘",
      "answer": "こぐんふんとう",
      "meaning": "fighting alone"
    },
    {
      "question": "神意",
      "answer": "しんい",
      "meaning": "divine will"
    },
    {
      "question": "市外",
      "answer": "しがい",
      "meaning": "outside the city area, suburbs"
    },
    {
      "question": "養護施設",
      "answer": "ようごしせつ",
      "meaning": "children's home, child care institution, orphanage"
    },
    {
      "question": "年嵩",
      "answer": "としかさ",
      "meaning": "senior, older, elderly"
    },
    {
      "question": "具申",
      "answer": "ぐしん",
      "meaning": "offering a full report to a superior"
    },
    {
      "question": "骨盤",
      "answer": "こつばん",
      "meaning": "pelvis"
    },
    {
      "question": "不徳",
      "answer": "ふとく",
      "meaning": "lack of virtue, immorality, vice, depravity, unworthiness"
    },
    {
      "question": "紅一点",
      "answer": "こういってん",
      "meaning": "the lone woman (e.g. bright flower) in a group"
    },
    {
      "question": "修道",
      "answer": "しゅうどう",
      "meaning": "learning, studying the fine arts"
    },
    {
      "question": "磐",
      "answer": "いわ",
      "meaning": "rock, boulder, crag, cliff, anchor"
    },
    {
      "question": "鳶",
      "answer": "とび,とんび",
      "meaning": "black kite (Milvus migrans), construction worker, scaffold erector, firefighter, fire hook, reddish"
    },
    {
      "question": "軽自動車",
      "answer": "けいじどうしゃ",
      "meaning": "light motor vehicle (up to 660cc and 64bhp), k-car, kei car"
    },
    {
      "question": "助平",
      "answer": "すけべ,すけべい",
      "meaning": "lewdness, lewd person, pervert, lecher"
    },
    {
      "question": "専門職",
      "answer": "せんもんしょく",
      "meaning": "professional job, profession"
    },
    {
      "question": "享年",
      "answer": "きょうねん",
      "meaning": "one's age at death"
    },
    {
      "question": "商魂",
      "answer": "しょうこん",
      "meaning": "commercial spirit"
    },
    {
      "question": "寝姿",
      "answer": "ねすがた",
      "meaning": "one's figure during sleep"
    },
    {
      "question": "城館",
      "answer": "じょうかん",
      "meaning": "fortified mansion"
    },
    {
      "question": "葉桜",
      "answer": "はざくら",
      "meaning": "cherry tree in leaf, cherry tree whose blossoms have fallen, revealing the young leaves"
    },
    {
      "question": "常闇",
      "answer": "とこやみ",
      "meaning": "everlasting darkness"
    },
    {
      "question": "草食系",
      "answer": "そうしょくけい",
      "meaning": "man who is uninterested in aggressively pursuing women, peaceable men who don't approach women as po"
    },
    {
      "question": "名曲",
      "answer": "めいきょく",
      "meaning": "famous piece of music, excellent song, (musical) masterpiece"
    },
    {
      "question": "車種",
      "answer": "しゃしゅ",
      "meaning": "car model, type of (wheeled) vehicle, vehicle classification"
    },
    {
      "question": "結構人",
      "answer": "けっこうじん",
      "meaning": "nice person, good-natured person"
    },
    {
      "question": "都知事",
      "answer": "とちじ",
      "meaning": "metropolitan governor, governor of Tokyo"
    },
    {
      "question": "双璧",
      "answer": "そうへき",
      "meaning": "(two) matchless things, (two) matchless people, pair of bright jewels"
    },
    {
      "question": "荷重",
      "answer": "かじゅう,におも",
      "meaning": "load, loading, weight (of a load), heavy load, burden of responsibility, heavy duty"
    },
    {
      "question": "競り",
      "answer": "せり",
      "meaning": "competing, competition, auction"
    },
    {
      "question": "委細",
      "answer": "いさい",
      "meaning": "details, particulars"
    },
    {
      "question": "物真似",
      "answer": "ものまね",
      "meaning": "mimicry, imitation (of someone, something)"
    },
    {
      "question": "評",
      "answer": "ひょう",
      "meaning": "criticism, commentary, review"
    },
    {
      "question": "夜店",
      "answer": "よみせ",
      "meaning": "night stall, night shop, night fair"
    },
    {
      "question": "帰属",
      "answer": "きぞく",
      "meaning": "belonging, ascription, attribution, imputation, possession, jurisdiction, reversion, return, restora"
    },
    {
      "question": "波音",
      "answer": "なみおと",
      "meaning": "the sound of waves"
    },
    {
      "question": "網の目",
      "answer": "あみのめ",
      "meaning": "mesh (of a net)"
    },
    {
      "question": "目的意識",
      "answer": "もくてきいしき",
      "meaning": "sense of purpose"
    },
    {
      "question": "虚栄心",
      "answer": "きょえいしん",
      "meaning": "vanity"
    },
    {
      "question": "我が強い",
      "answer": "ががつよい",
      "meaning": "egoistic, selfish, self-willed"
    },
    {
      "question": "朔",
      "answer": "さく,つきたち,ついたち",
      "meaning": "new moon, first day of the lunar month, (in ancient China) next year's calendar and decrees (distrib"
    },
    {
      "question": "蛭",
      "answer": "ひる",
      "meaning": "leech"
    },
    {
      "question": "男好き",
      "answer": "おとこずき",
      "meaning": "attractive to men, in a style (appearance, look, etc.) that men fall for, amorous woman"
    },
    {
      "question": "怒らす",
      "answer": "いからす",
      "meaning": "to anger, to displease, to offend, to square (one's shoulders), to make stern (e.g. eyes), to raise"
    },
    {
      "question": "較べる",
      "answer": "くらべる",
      "meaning": "to compare, to make a comparison, to compete, to vie"
    },
    {
      "question": "首吊り",
      "answer": "くびつり",
      "meaning": "hanging (by the neck)"
    },
    {
      "question": "夕刊",
      "answer": "ゆうかん",
      "meaning": "evening paper"
    },
    {
      "question": "勘案",
      "answer": "かんあん",
      "meaning": "taking into consideration, giving consideration (to)"
    },
    {
      "question": "偏に",
      "answer": "ひとえに",
      "meaning": "wholly (due to), entirely, solely, earnestly, intently, sincerely"
    },
    {
      "question": "僭越",
      "answer": "せんえつ",
      "meaning": "presumptuous, arrogant, audacious, forward, insolent"
    },
    {
      "question": "唯々諾々",
      "answer": "いいだくだく",
      "meaning": "obedient, submissive, tame, slavish"
    },
    {
      "question": "略式",
      "answer": "りゃくしき",
      "meaning": "informal, simplified"
    },
    {
      "question": "立地条件",
      "answer": "りっちじょうけん",
      "meaning": "conditions of a location, suitability of a location, convenience of a location"
    },
    {
      "question": "嬲り殺し",
      "answer": "なぶりごろし",
      "meaning": "torture to death, torment to death"
    },
    {
      "question": "大石",
      "answer": "たいせき,おおいし",
      "meaning": "large stone, boulder, large group of stones (in the game of go)"
    },
    {
      "question": "充たす",
      "answer": "みたす",
      "meaning": "to satisfy (conditions, one's appetite, etc.), to meet (e.g. demands), to fulfill, to gratify, to fi"
    },
    {
      "question": "巡航",
      "answer": "じゅんこう",
      "meaning": "cruise, cruising"
    },
    {
      "question": "猛牛",
      "answer": "もうぎゅう",
      "meaning": "raging bull, ferocious bull"
    },
    {
      "question": "円い",
      "answer": "まるい,まろい",
      "meaning": "round, circular, spherical, curved, smooth, harmonious, calm, peaceful, amiable, amicable"
    },
    {
      "question": "目玉商品",
      "answer": "めだましょうひん",
      "meaning": "bargain goods, eye-catching goods, featured product, loss leader"
    },
    {
      "question": "鈍足",
      "answer": "どんそく",
      "meaning": "slow-footed"
    },
    {
      "question": "姓名",
      "answer": "せいめい",
      "meaning": "(full) name, family name and given name"
    },
    {
      "question": "御髪",
      "answer": "おぐし,みぐし",
      "meaning": "hair"
    },
    {
      "question": "閉会",
      "answer": "へいかい",
      "meaning": "closure (of a ceremony, event, meeting, etc.)"
    },
    {
      "question": "年齢層",
      "answer": "ねんれいそう",
      "meaning": "age range, age-group, age bracket"
    },
    {
      "question": "氷雨",
      "answer": "ひさめ",
      "meaning": "hail, sleet, chilly rain, freezing rain"
    },
    {
      "question": "冬将軍",
      "answer": "ふゆしょうぐん",
      "meaning": "General Winter, hard winter, Jack Frost"
    },
    {
      "question": "学説",
      "answer": "がくせつ",
      "meaning": "theory"
    },
    {
      "question": "解法",
      "answer": "かいほう",
      "meaning": "(key to) solution"
    },
    {
      "question": "剣山",
      "answer": "けんざん",
      "meaning": "needle-point holder (in ikebana), frog"
    },
    {
      "question": "女子高",
      "answer": "じょしこう",
      "meaning": "girls' high school"
    },
    {
      "question": "不定",
      "answer": "ふじょう,ふてい",
      "meaning": "uncertainty, insecurity, inconstancy, indefinite, undecided"
    },
    {
      "question": "急場",
      "answer": "きゅうば",
      "meaning": "emergency"
    },
    {
      "question": "山吹",
      "answer": "やまぶき",
      "meaning": "kerria (Kerria japonica), Japanese yellow rose, bright golden yellow, gold coin (formerly used in Ja"
    },
    {
      "question": "智恵",
      "answer": "ちえ",
      "meaning": "wisdom, wit, sagacity, sense, intelligence, prajna (insight leading to enlightenment)"
    },
    {
      "question": "医大",
      "answer": "いだい",
      "meaning": "medical school"
    },
    {
      "question": "漁港",
      "answer": "ぎょこう",
      "meaning": "fishing harbour, fishing harbor"
    },
    {
      "question": "手間賃",
      "answer": "てまちん",
      "meaning": "payment (for labour), pay, charge, wages"
    },
    {
      "question": "造園",
      "answer": "ぞうえん",
      "meaning": "landscape gardening, landscape architecture"
    },
    {
      "question": "争乱",
      "answer": "そうらん",
      "meaning": "conflict, strife"
    },
    {
      "question": "原罪",
      "answer": "げんざい",
      "meaning": "original sin"
    },
    {
      "question": "示談",
      "answer": "じだん",
      "meaning": "settlement out of court, private settlement"
    },
    {
      "question": "御言葉",
      "answer": "おことば,みことば",
      "meaning": "(your) words, what you say, what you have said, a few words (of welcome, advice, etc.), God's word,"
    },
    {
      "question": "戦端",
      "answer": "せんたん",
      "meaning": "opening of hostilities"
    },
    {
      "question": "我欲",
      "answer": "がよく",
      "meaning": "selfishness"
    },
    {
      "question": "俗称",
      "answer": "ぞくしょう",
      "meaning": "common name, popular name"
    },
    {
      "question": "追突",
      "answer": "ついとつ",
      "meaning": "rear-end collision"
    },
    {
      "question": "起爆剤",
      "answer": "きばくざい",
      "meaning": "triggering explosive"
    },
    {
      "question": "胸を貸す",
      "answer": "むねをかす",
      "meaning": "to allow a less skilled person to practice with one (esp. in sumo)"
    },
    {
      "question": "連合艦隊",
      "answer": "れんごうかんたい",
      "meaning": "combined fleet"
    },
    {
      "question": "大西洋",
      "answer": "たいせいよう",
      "meaning": "Atlantic Ocean"
    },
    {
      "question": "出展",
      "answer": "しゅってん",
      "meaning": "exhibit, display"
    },
    {
      "question": "偶数",
      "answer": "ぐうすう",
      "meaning": "even number"
    },
    {
      "question": "東南",
      "answer": "とうなん,ひがしみなみ",
      "meaning": "south-east"
    },
    {
      "question": "間近い",
      "answer": "まぢかい",
      "meaning": "near at hand"
    },
    {
      "question": "大荒れ",
      "answer": "おおあれ",
      "meaning": "great storm, agitation, upheaval"
    },
    {
      "question": "松葉",
      "answer": "まつば",
      "meaning": "pine needle"
    },
    {
      "question": "僧兵",
      "answer": "そうへい",
      "meaning": "priest soldier, warrior monk"
    },
    {
      "question": "日本茶",
      "answer": "にほんちゃ",
      "meaning": "Japanese tea"
    },
    {
      "question": "無血",
      "answer": "むけつ",
      "meaning": "bloodless"
    },
    {
      "question": "現代的",
      "answer": "げんだいてき",
      "meaning": "modernistic"
    },
    {
      "question": "終局",
      "answer": "しゅうきょく",
      "meaning": "end, close, conclusion, end of a game of go, shogi, etc."
    },
    {
      "question": "蔑称",
      "answer": "べっしょう",
      "meaning": "disparaging words, derogatory term, insult, epithet"
    },
    {
      "question": "童子",
      "answer": "どうじ",
      "meaning": "boy, kid, child"
    },
    {
      "question": "一騎討ち",
      "answer": "いっきうち",
      "meaning": "personal combat, one-to-one fight"
    },
    {
      "question": "酒杯",
      "answer": "しゅはい",
      "meaning": "sake cup, wine cup"
    },
    {
      "question": "学徒",
      "answer": "がくと",
      "meaning": "student, follower, students and pupils"
    },
    {
      "question": "世直し",
      "answer": "よなおし",
      "meaning": "world reformation"
    },
    {
      "question": "釣り人",
      "answer": "つりびと",
      "meaning": "angler"
    },
    {
      "question": "被り物",
      "answer": "かぶりもの",
      "meaning": "headgear, headdress, (novelty) mask, head mask"
    },
    {
      "question": "自傷行為",
      "answer": "じしょうこうい",
      "meaning": "act of self-harm, self-injurious behavior, self-injurious behaviour"
    },
    {
      "question": "聴き入る",
      "answer": "ききいる",
      "meaning": "to listen attentively to, to be lost in"
    },
    {
      "question": "尻餅",
      "answer": "しりもち",
      "meaning": "falling on one's backside (behind, bottom), pratfall, mochi used to celebrate a child's first birthd"
    },
    {
      "question": "焼き討ち",
      "answer": "やきうち",
      "meaning": "setting on fire, setting afire"
    },
    {
      "question": "球根",
      "answer": "きゅうこん",
      "meaning": "(plant) bulb"
    },
    {
      "question": "残り火",
      "answer": "のこりび",
      "meaning": "embers"
    },
    {
      "question": "排気ガス",
      "answer": "はいきガス",
      "meaning": "exhaust fumes"
    },
    {
      "question": "山口",
      "answer": "やまぐち",
      "meaning": "Yamaguchi (city, prefecture)"
    },
    {
      "question": "調伏",
      "answer": "ちょうぶく,じょうぶく",
      "meaning": "curse, exorcism"
    },
    {
      "question": "議事録",
      "answer": "ぎじろく",
      "meaning": "record of proceedings, minutes"
    },
    {
      "question": "夜泣き",
      "answer": "よなき",
      "meaning": "crying (of an infant) at night, baby colic"
    },
    {
      "question": "滑り止め",
      "answer": "すべりどめ",
      "meaning": "non-slip device (material, tread, etc.), non-skid, anti-slip, anti-skid, taking an entrance examinat"
    },
    {
      "question": "実名",
      "answer": "じつめい",
      "meaning": "real name"
    },
    {
      "question": "突っ返す",
      "answer": "つっかえす",
      "meaning": "to deal a blow in return, to hit back, to punch back, to reject, to send back"
    },
    {
      "question": "改宗",
      "answer": "かいしゅう",
      "meaning": "religious conversion"
    },
    {
      "question": "異口同音",
      "answer": "いくどうおん,いこうどうおん",
      "meaning": "(saying) with one voice, unanimously, in chorus, in unison, as one"
    },
    {
      "question": "飽食",
      "answer": "ほうしょく",
      "meaning": "gluttony, satiation, engorgement"
    },
    {
      "question": "鶯",
      "answer": "うぐいす",
      "meaning": "Japanese bush warbler (Horornis diphone), Japanese nightingale, greenish brown, having a beautiful v"
    },
    {
      "question": "盥",
      "answer": "たらい",
      "meaning": "tub, washbasin, washbowl"
    },
    {
      "question": "見蕩れる",
      "answer": "みとれる",
      "meaning": "to be fascinated (by), to be captivated by, to be enchanted by, to gaze admiringly at, to watch in f"
    },
    {
      "question": "素粒子",
      "answer": "そりゅうし",
      "meaning": "elementary particle, particle"
    },
    {
      "question": "後詰め",
      "answer": "ごづめ",
      "meaning": "rear guard"
    },
    {
      "question": "製本",
      "answer": "せいほん",
      "meaning": "book making (binding, publishing)"
    },
    {
      "question": "無駄骨",
      "answer": "むだぼね",
      "meaning": "useless, waste of time and effort, pointless, vain efforts"
    },
    {
      "question": "河内",
      "answer": "ハノイ,かわち",
      "meaning": "Hanoi (Vietnam), Kawachi (former province located in the east of present-day Osaka Prefecture)"
    },
    {
      "question": "くノ一",
      "answer": "くのいち",
      "meaning": "female ninja, woman"
    },
    {
      "question": "白羽",
      "answer": "しらは",
      "meaning": "white feather"
    },
    {
      "question": "畝",
      "answer": "うね,せ,ほ",
      "meaning": "ridge (in field), row of raised earth when planting crops, rib (cloth, mountains, sea), cord (e.g. c"
    },
    {
      "question": "忘年会",
      "answer": "ぼうねんかい",
      "meaning": "year-end party, 'forget-the-year' party, bōnenkai"
    },
    {
      "question": "直截",
      "answer": "ちょくせつ,ちょくさい",
      "meaning": "direct, frank, straightforward, plain, decisive, prompt"
    },
    {
      "question": "捲く",
      "answer": "まく",
      "meaning": "to wind, to coil, to roll, to wear (e.g. turban, scarf), to envelope, to shroud, to outflank, to ski"
    },
    {
      "question": "滅多打ち",
      "answer": "めったうち",
      "meaning": "showering with blows"
    },
    {
      "question": "火元",
      "answer": "ひもと",
      "meaning": "origin of a fire"
    },
    {
      "question": "新旧",
      "answer": "しんきゅう",
      "meaning": "new and old, incoming and outgoing"
    },
    {
      "question": "脂っこい",
      "answer": "あぶらっこい",
      "meaning": "greasy, fatty, oily"
    },
    {
      "question": "世情",
      "answer": "せじょう",
      "meaning": "the ways of the world, human nature"
    },
    {
      "question": "定期船",
      "answer": "ていきせん",
      "meaning": "(ocean) liner"
    },
    {
      "question": "調う",
      "answer": "ととのう",
      "meaning": "to be ready, to be prepared, to be arranged, to be in order, to be put in order, to be well-ordered,"
    },
    {
      "question": "一気呵成",
      "answer": "いっきかせい",
      "meaning": "finishing writing, work, etc. at a stroke (stretch), knocking something off without a break"
    },
    {
      "question": "趣く",
      "answer": "おもむく,おもぶく",
      "meaning": "to go in the direction of, to proceed toward, to proceed according to, to repair to, to betake onese"
    },
    {
      "question": "准尉",
      "answer": "じゅんい",
      "meaning": "warrant officer"
    },
    {
      "question": "聖句",
      "answer": "せいく",
      "meaning": "scripture, passage from scripture"
    },
    {
      "question": "美大",
      "answer": "びだい",
      "meaning": "college of the arts, university of the arts, art university"
    },
    {
      "question": "官憲",
      "answer": "かんけん",
      "meaning": "officials, authorities"
    },
    {
      "question": "蛍光",
      "answer": "けいこう",
      "meaning": "fluorescence"
    },
    {
      "question": "九回",
      "answer": "きゅうかい",
      "meaning": "nine times, twisting around many times"
    },
    {
      "question": "有機物",
      "answer": "ゆうきぶつ",
      "meaning": "organic matter"
    },
    {
      "question": "揺蕩う",
      "answer": "たゆたう,たゆとう",
      "meaning": "to sway to and fro, to drift about, to flutter, to flicker, to be fickle, to be irresolute, to vacil"
    },
    {
      "question": "酸性",
      "answer": "さんせい",
      "meaning": "acidity, acidic"
    },
    {
      "question": "自活",
      "answer": "じかつ",
      "meaning": "self-support"
    },
    {
      "question": "近未来",
      "answer": "きんみらい",
      "meaning": "near future"
    },
    {
      "question": "女癖",
      "answer": "おんなぐせ",
      "meaning": "philandering, itch for women"
    },
    {
      "question": "首脳部",
      "answer": "しゅのうぶ",
      "meaning": "executives, top management, governing body"
    },
    {
      "question": "外務大臣",
      "answer": "がいむだいじん",
      "meaning": "Minister for Foreign Affairs"
    },
    {
      "question": "薬箱",
      "answer": "くすりばこ",
      "meaning": "medicine box"
    },
    {
      "question": "自己愛",
      "answer": "じこあい",
      "meaning": "narcissism, self-love"
    },
    {
      "question": "力学",
      "answer": "りきがく",
      "meaning": "mechanics, dynamics"
    },
    {
      "question": "直方体",
      "answer": "ちょくほうたい",
      "meaning": "right-angled parallelepiped, cuboid, rectangular solid"
    },
    {
      "question": "考古学",
      "answer": "こうこがく",
      "meaning": "archaeology, archeology"
    },
    {
      "question": "端麗",
      "answer": "たんれい",
      "meaning": "grace, beauty, elegance"
    },
    {
      "question": "心痛",
      "answer": "しんつう",
      "meaning": "worry, mental agony, heartache"
    },
    {
      "question": "土足",
      "answer": "どそく",
      "meaning": "shod feet, wearing shoes, muddy feet, dirty feet"
    },
    {
      "question": "面汚し",
      "answer": "つらよごし",
      "meaning": "disgrace, shame"
    },
    {
      "question": "頭痛の種",
      "answer": "ずつうのたね",
      "meaning": "cause for headaches, pain in the neck, source of worry"
    },
    {
      "question": "膝を打つ",
      "answer": "ひざをうつ",
      "meaning": "to express sudden recognition and being impressed, to slap one's knee"
    },
    {
      "question": "本気度",
      "answer": "ほんきど",
      "meaning": "(degree of) seriousness, level of commitment"
    },
    {
      "question": "顎で使う",
      "answer": "あごでつかう",
      "meaning": "to set somebody to work in an arrogant fashion, to push somebody around, to indicate by pointing one"
    },
    {
      "question": "四聖",
      "answer": "しせい",
      "meaning": "the four great sages (Buddha, Christ, Confucius, Socrates)"
    },
    {
      "question": "宮崎",
      "answer": "みやざき",
      "meaning": "Miyazaki (city, prefecture)"
    },
    {
      "question": "雪像",
      "answer": "せつぞう",
      "meaning": "snow sculpture"
    },
    {
      "question": "止まり木",
      "answer": "とまりぎ",
      "meaning": "perch, barstool"
    },
    {
      "question": "菱形",
      "answer": "ひしがた,りょうけい",
      "meaning": "rhombus, rhomb, lozenge, diamond shape"
    },
    {
      "question": "三位一体",
      "answer": "さんみいったい",
      "meaning": "the Trinity (in Christianity), three parts, three components, three factors, three aspects"
    },
    {
      "question": "測量",
      "answer": "そくりょう",
      "meaning": "measurement, surveying"
    },
    {
      "question": "濾過",
      "answer": "ろか",
      "meaning": "filtration, filtering, percolation"
    },
    {
      "question": "半周",
      "answer": "はんしゅう",
      "meaning": "semicircle, hemicycle, half globe, to go halfway round (e.g. the earth)"
    },
    {
      "question": "一束",
      "answer": "いっそく,ひとたば",
      "meaning": "a bundle, a hundred"
    },
    {
      "question": "言葉数",
      "answer": "ことばかず",
      "meaning": "number of words, vocality"
    },
    {
      "question": "能登",
      "answer": "のと",
      "meaning": "Noto (former province located in the north of present-day Ishikawa Prefecture), Noto (peninsula)"
    },
    {
      "question": "姐御",
      "answer": "あねご",
      "meaning": "elder sister"
    },
    {
      "question": "冬支度",
      "answer": "ふゆじたく",
      "meaning": "preparations for winter"
    },
    {
      "question": "三輪",
      "answer": "さんりん",
      "meaning": "three wheels"
    },
    {
      "question": "豆乳",
      "answer": "とうにゅう",
      "meaning": "soy milk"
    },
    {
      "question": "磁器",
      "answer": "じき",
      "meaning": "porcelain (esp. hard-paste porcelain), china, chinaware"
    },
    {
      "question": "鳥肉",
      "answer": "とりにく,ちょうにく",
      "meaning": "chicken meat, fowl, poultry, bird meat"
    },
    {
      "question": "聴診器",
      "answer": "ちょうしんき",
      "meaning": "stethoscope"
    },
    {
      "question": "駄作",
      "answer": "ださく",
      "meaning": "poor piece of work, rubbish, trash"
    },
    {
      "question": "駆け",
      "answer": "かけ",
      "meaning": "canter, gallop"
    },
    {
      "question": "血祭り",
      "answer": "ちまつり",
      "meaning": "killing an enemy soldier before the start of a battle to raise spirits, blood offering, killing viol"
    },
    {
      "question": "仲立ち",
      "answer": "なかだち",
      "meaning": "mediation, agency, agent, mediator, middleman, go-between"
    },
    {
      "question": "学芸会",
      "answer": "がくげいかい",
      "meaning": "school arts festival"
    },
    {
      "question": "末尾",
      "answer": "まつび",
      "meaning": "end (e.g. of report, document, paragraph, etc.)"
    },
    {
      "question": "雨脚",
      "answer": "あまあし,あめあし,うきゃく",
      "meaning": "passing shower, streaks of pouring rain"
    },
    {
      "question": "拾い物",
      "answer": "ひろいもの",
      "meaning": "a find, windfall, bargain"
    },
    {
      "question": "食べ頃",
      "answer": "たべごろ",
      "meaning": "good for eating, ripe enough for eating, in season"
    },
    {
      "question": "御所",
      "answer": "ごしょ,おところ",
      "meaning": "imperial palace (esp. Kyoto Imperial Palace), imperial residence, residence of a shogun, minister, e"
    },
    {
      "question": "主権",
      "answer": "しゅけん",
      "meaning": "sovereignty, supremacy, dominion"
    },
    {
      "question": "雑菌",
      "answer": "ざっきん",
      "meaning": "microorganisms, saprophyte, saprophytic bacteria"
    },
    {
      "question": "起業",
      "answer": "きぎょう",
      "meaning": "starting a business, promotion of enterprise"
    },
    {
      "question": "一発芸",
      "answer": "いっぱつげい",
      "meaning": "one-liner, funny joke, gag, quick trick"
    },
    {
      "question": "短針",
      "answer": "たんしん",
      "meaning": "short hand, hour hand"
    },
    {
      "question": "綺羅",
      "answer": "きら",
      "meaning": "fine clothes"
    },
    {
      "question": "安楽死",
      "answer": "あんらくし",
      "meaning": "euthanasia"
    },
    {
      "question": "納戸",
      "answer": "なんど",
      "meaning": "storage room, storeroom, closet, grayish blue"
    },
    {
      "question": "暗色",
      "answer": "あんしょく",
      "meaning": "dark colour, dark color"
    },
    {
      "question": "空路",
      "answer": "くうろ",
      "meaning": "air lane"
    },
    {
      "question": "猥雑",
      "answer": "わいざつ",
      "meaning": "vulgar, indecent, crude, sordid, jumbled (of a place), disorderly, chaotic, messy"
    },
    {
      "question": "社会復帰",
      "answer": "しゃかいふっき",
      "meaning": "rehabilitation (in society)"
    },
    {
      "question": "粉骨砕身",
      "answer": "ふんこつさいしん",
      "meaning": "making one's best exertions"
    },
    {
      "question": "二面性",
      "answer": "にめんせい",
      "meaning": "dual nature, bilateral character, two-facedness, two-sidedness"
    },
    {
      "question": "業種",
      "answer": "ぎょうしゅ",
      "meaning": "type of industry"
    },
    {
      "question": "装塡",
      "answer": "そうてん",
      "meaning": "loading, charging, filling"
    },
    {
      "question": "山梨",
      "answer": "やまなし",
      "meaning": "Yamanashi (city, prefecture), wild nashi (Pyrus pyrifolia var. pyrifolia), wild Japanese pear"
    },
    {
      "question": "目鼻",
      "answer": "めはな",
      "meaning": "eyes and nose, looks, facial features, shape, form"
    },
    {
      "question": "担ぎ出す",
      "answer": "かつぎだす",
      "meaning": "to carry something out of a place, to elevate (someone) to a high position, to convince someone to a"
    },
    {
      "question": "平熱",
      "answer": "へいねつ",
      "meaning": "normal temperature"
    },
    {
      "question": "先見の明",
      "answer": "せんけんのめい",
      "meaning": "foresight, prescience"
    },
    {
      "question": "足が重い",
      "answer": "あしがおもい",
      "meaning": "heavy-footed, slow of foot, reluctant, disinclined, unwilling"
    },
    {
      "question": "小官",
      "answer": "しょうかん",
      "meaning": "petty official, I, me"
    },
    {
      "question": "出目",
      "answer": "でめ",
      "meaning": "protruding eyes, number of pips visible after a throw of the dice"
    },
    {
      "question": "打球",
      "answer": "だきゅう",
      "meaning": "batting, batted ball"
    },
    {
      "question": "招き猫",
      "answer": "まねきねこ",
      "meaning": "beckoning cat, figure of a cat with one paw raised (usu. white porcelain)"
    },
    {
      "question": "禁則",
      "answer": "きんそく",
      "meaning": "prohibition"
    },
    {
      "question": "避妊具",
      "answer": "ひにんぐ",
      "meaning": "contraceptive device, birth-control device"
    },
    {
      "question": "復調",
      "answer": "ふくちょう",
      "meaning": "demodulation, recovery, getting back to form"
    },
    {
      "question": "中心点",
      "answer": "ちゅうしんてん",
      "meaning": "center, centre"
    },
    {
      "question": "守勢",
      "answer": "しゅせい",
      "meaning": "(being on the) defensive"
    },
    {
      "question": "応急手当",
      "answer": "おうきゅうてあて",
      "meaning": "first-aid (treatment)"
    },
    {
      "question": "対抗馬",
      "answer": "たいこうば",
      "meaning": "a rival horse or candidate"
    },
    {
      "question": "文学的",
      "answer": "ぶんがくてき",
      "meaning": "literary"
    },
    {
      "question": "下の下",
      "answer": "げのげ",
      "meaning": "the lowest (of its kind), the poorest"
    },
    {
      "question": "宗主",
      "answer": "そうしゅ",
      "meaning": "suzerain"
    },
    {
      "question": "岐阜",
      "answer": "ぎふ",
      "meaning": "Gifu (city, prefecture)"
    },
    {
      "question": "円ら",
      "answer": "つぶら",
      "meaning": "round and cute (esp. of eyes)"
    },
    {
      "question": "船外",
      "answer": "せんがい",
      "meaning": "outside the boat (ship, spaceship, etc.), outboard, extravehicular"
    },
    {
      "question": "全隊",
      "answer": "ぜんたい",
      "meaning": "the entire force (of soldiers)"
    },
    {
      "question": "涙混じり",
      "answer": "なみだまじり",
      "meaning": "(doing something) in tears"
    },
    {
      "question": "運次第",
      "answer": "うんしだい",
      "meaning": "dependent on luck, matter of luck"
    },
    {
      "question": "流れ作業",
      "answer": "ながれさぎょう",
      "meaning": "assembly-line system"
    },
    {
      "question": "一堂",
      "answer": "いちどう",
      "meaning": "one building (hall, temple, shrine, room), same room, same place, same building"
    },
    {
      "question": "任官",
      "answer": "にんかん",
      "meaning": "appointment (to an office), investiture, commission"
    },
    {
      "question": "左方",
      "answer": "さほう",
      "meaning": "left side"
    },
    {
      "question": "血染め",
      "answer": "ちぞめ",
      "meaning": "bloodstained"
    },
    {
      "question": "倍する",
      "answer": "ばいする",
      "meaning": "to double, to increase"
    },
    {
      "question": "一打",
      "answer": "いちだ",
      "meaning": "stroke, blow"
    },
    {
      "question": "煮付け",
      "answer": "につけ",
      "meaning": "vegetables or fish boiled in soy sauce"
    },
    {
      "question": "弾き",
      "answer": "はじき,ひき",
      "meaning": "gun, pistol, tiddlywinks, marbles, repellence, player (of music, instrument, etc.)"
    },
    {
      "question": "間欠泉",
      "answer": "かんけつせん",
      "meaning": "geyser"
    },
    {
      "question": "軽妙",
      "answer": "けいみょう",
      "meaning": "light and easy, lambent, clever, witty, smart"
    },
    {
      "question": "無機",
      "answer": "むき",
      "meaning": "inorganic"
    },
    {
      "question": "大店",
      "answer": "おおだな",
      "meaning": "large store"
    },
    {
      "question": "筆者",
      "answer": "ひっしゃ",
      "meaning": "writer, author"
    },
    {
      "question": "裏金",
      "answer": "うらがね",
      "meaning": "bribe, secret fund, slush fund, money for bribery"
    },
    {
      "question": "後援",
      "answer": "こうえん",
      "meaning": "support, backing"
    },
    {
      "question": "厚紙",
      "answer": "あつがみ",
      "meaning": "cardboard, thick paper"
    },
    {
      "question": "合わせ鏡",
      "answer": "あわせかがみ",
      "meaning": "opposite mirrors"
    },
    {
      "question": "幽霊部員",
      "answer": "ゆうれいぶいん",
      "meaning": "member of a (school) club who does not partake in the club's activities"
    },
    {
      "question": "座椅子",
      "answer": "ざいす",
      "meaning": "tatami chair, legless chair, small, legless chair used while sitting on tatami"
    },
    {
      "question": "胃の腑",
      "answer": "いのふ",
      "meaning": "stomach"
    },
    {
      "question": "地で行く",
      "answer": "じでいく,じでゆく",
      "meaning": "to do for real, to do in real life, to carry (a story) into actual practice"
    },
    {
      "question": "思し召し",
      "answer": "おぼしめし",
      "meaning": "thoughts, opinion, (one's) discretion, however much money you wish to give (as alms, a fee at a muse"
    },
    {
      "question": "老婆心",
      "answer": "ろうばしん",
      "meaning": "solicitude, consideration, concern, (excessive) kindness"
    },
    {
      "question": "荒れ",
      "answer": "あれ",
      "meaning": "stormy weather, tempest, chaps (of skin)"
    },
    {
      "question": "帖",
      "answer": "じょう",
      "meaning": "folding book, counter for units of paper and nori (48 pages of Mino paper; 20 pages of hanshi; 10 sh"
    },
    {
      "question": "柄頭",
      "answer": "つかがしら",
      "meaning": "pommel"
    },
    {
      "question": "洋画",
      "answer": "ようが",
      "meaning": "Western painting, Western film, Western movie"
    },
    {
      "question": "多角的",
      "answer": "たかくてき",
      "meaning": "multilateral, many-sided, diversified"
    },
    {
      "question": "水月",
      "answer": "すいげつ",
      "meaning": "water and moon, the Moon reflected on the water, pit of the stomach, solar plexus"
    },
    {
      "question": "杜",
      "answer": "もり",
      "meaning": "forest, shrine grove"
    },
    {
      "question": "自然公園",
      "answer": "しぜんこうえん",
      "meaning": "nature park, natural park"
    },
    {
      "question": "薬剤師",
      "answer": "やくざいし",
      "meaning": "pharmacist, chemist"
    },
    {
      "question": "代打",
      "answer": "だいだ",
      "meaning": "pinch-hitting"
    },
    {
      "question": "首位",
      "answer": "しゅい",
      "meaning": "first place, head position, leading position"
    },
    {
      "question": "毛細血管",
      "answer": "もうさいけっかん",
      "meaning": "capillary vessel, capillary"
    },
    {
      "question": "軟体動物",
      "answer": "なんたいどうぶつ",
      "meaning": "mollusc, mollusk"
    },
    {
      "question": "雨足",
      "answer": "あまあし,あめあし",
      "meaning": "passing shower, streaks of pouring rain"
    },
    {
      "question": "生活空間",
      "answer": "せいかつくうかん",
      "meaning": "living space"
    },
    {
      "question": "海蛇",
      "answer": "うみへび",
      "meaning": "sea snake, worm eel (Ophichthidae spp.), snake eel"
    },
    {
      "question": "木の間",
      "answer": "このま",
      "meaning": "in the trees"
    },
    {
      "question": "駄賃",
      "answer": "だちん",
      "meaning": "reward, recompense, tip, conveyance charge, packhorse charge"
    },
    {
      "question": "往年",
      "answer": "おうねん",
      "meaning": "years gone by, earlier years, former years, the past"
    },
    {
      "question": "混線",
      "answer": "こんせん",
      "meaning": "crossed wires or lines (of communication), confusion"
    },
    {
      "question": "可否",
      "answer": "かひ",
      "meaning": "propriety, right and wrong, advisability, possibility, pro and con, ayes and noes"
    },
    {
      "question": "荒業",
      "answer": "あらわざ",
      "meaning": "physical labor, physical labour, manual work, heavy work, drastic move (e.g. hold or strike in marti"
    },
    {
      "question": "醸造",
      "answer": "じょうぞう",
      "meaning": "brewing"
    },
    {
      "question": "読み手",
      "answer": "よみて",
      "meaning": "reader (person), person who reads the cards (in karuta games), composer (of a poem)"
    },
    {
      "question": "新造",
      "answer": "しんぞう,しんぞ",
      "meaning": "new, newly made, newly-built ship, new boat, unmarried woman of about 20, newly-married woman, new p"
    },
    {
      "question": "締め括る",
      "answer": "しめくくる",
      "meaning": "to bring to a finish, to bind firmly, to superintend"
    },
    {
      "question": "翻意",
      "answer": "ほんい",
      "meaning": "changing one's mind"
    },
    {
      "question": "反作用",
      "answer": "はんさよう",
      "meaning": "reaction"
    },
    {
      "question": "長考",
      "answer": "ちょうこう",
      "meaning": "thinking (about a matter) for a long time, contemplating for a long time, lengthy consideration, pon"
    },
    {
      "question": "立ち眩み",
      "answer": "たちくらみ",
      "meaning": "dizziness (from standing up too fast), orthostatic syncope, lightheadedness, vertigo"
    },
    {
      "question": "慣用句",
      "answer": "かんようく",
      "meaning": "idiom, set phrase, idiomatic phrase"
    },
    {
      "question": "仕事着",
      "answer": "しごとぎ",
      "meaning": "work clothes, business suit"
    },
    {
      "question": "気功",
      "answer": "きこう",
      "meaning": "breathing exercise, breath control, spirit cultivation, chi kung, qigong"
    },
    {
      "question": "幕間",
      "answer": "まくあい,まくま",
      "meaning": "intermission (between acts), interlude"
    },
    {
      "question": "新生児",
      "answer": "しんせいじ",
      "meaning": "newborn baby"
    },
    {
      "question": "敷布",
      "answer": "しきふ",
      "meaning": "sheet, sheeting"
    },
    {
      "question": "大宇宙",
      "answer": "だいうちゅう",
      "meaning": "macrocosmos, macrocosm, the universe, the cosmos"
    },
    {
      "question": "一覧表",
      "answer": "いちらんひょう",
      "meaning": "list, table, schedule, catalogue, catalog"
    },
    {
      "question": "下味",
      "answer": "したあじ",
      "meaning": "seasoning of food"
    },
    {
      "question": "取り得",
      "answer": "とりえ,とりどく",
      "meaning": "worth, merit, value, good point, redeeming feature, saving grace, gain, profit"
    },
    {
      "question": "拝み倒す",
      "answer": "おがみたおす",
      "meaning": "to persuade someone to consent, to entreat repeatedly, to beg, to implore"
    },
    {
      "question": "太鼓判",
      "answer": "たいこばん",
      "meaning": "large seal, large stamp, seal of approval, guarantee, endorsement"
    },
    {
      "question": "仲居",
      "answer": "なかい",
      "meaning": "waitress (in a ryokan or traditional restaurant), hostess"
    },
    {
      "question": "品評会",
      "answer": "ひんぴょうかい",
      "meaning": "competitive show, fair"
    },
    {
      "question": "公文書",
      "answer": "こうぶんしょ",
      "meaning": "official document, archives"
    },
    {
      "question": "残光",
      "answer": "ざんこう",
      "meaning": "afterglow"
    },
    {
      "question": "有機的",
      "answer": "ゆうきてき",
      "meaning": "organic, coordinated, working in a coordinated fashion"
    },
    {
      "question": "不戦敗",
      "answer": "ふせんぱい",
      "meaning": "loss by default, default"
    },
    {
      "question": "生演奏",
      "answer": "なまえんそう",
      "meaning": "live music or performance"
    },
    {
      "question": "医局",
      "answer": "いきょく",
      "meaning": "medical office (esp. in a hospital), doctor's office"
    },
    {
      "question": "鏡像",
      "answer": "きょうぞう",
      "meaning": "reflection in a mirror, reflected image, mirror image, inverse (of a point)"
    },
    {
      "question": "雁首",
      "answer": "かりくび,がんくび",
      "meaning": "glans, head of a penis, goose's neck, head of a pipe, incl. the bowl and stem attachment, neck, head"
    },
    {
      "question": "誘引",
      "answer": "ゆういん",
      "meaning": "enticement, inducement, attraction"
    },
    {
      "question": "中小",
      "answer": "ちゅうしょう",
      "meaning": "small and medium"
    },
    {
      "question": "骨髄",
      "answer": "こつずい",
      "meaning": "bone marrow, medulla, true spirit, one's mind"
    },
    {
      "question": "病巣",
      "answer": "びょうそう",
      "meaning": "focus, nidus, lesion"
    },
    {
      "question": "掛け金",
      "answer": "かけきん,かけがね",
      "meaning": "installment, instalment, premium, bill, latch, lock, sneck, joint of the jaw"
    },
    {
      "question": "弄くる",
      "answer": "いじくる",
      "meaning": "to finger, to tamper (with)"
    },
    {
      "question": "ゲリラ戦",
      "answer": "ゲリラせん",
      "meaning": "guerrilla warfare"
    },
    {
      "question": "終生",
      "answer": "しゅうせい",
      "meaning": "all one's life, throughout one's life, as long as one lives"
    },
    {
      "question": "平均寿命",
      "answer": "へいきんじゅみょう",
      "meaning": "life expectancy"
    },
    {
      "question": "癖毛",
      "answer": "くせげ",
      "meaning": "kinky hair, frizzy hair, unruly hair, curly hair"
    },
    {
      "question": "急斜面",
      "answer": "きゅうしゃめん",
      "meaning": "steep slope"
    },
    {
      "question": "全問",
      "answer": "ぜんもん",
      "meaning": "all the questions (in an exam, quiz, etc.)"
    },
    {
      "question": "重き",
      "answer": "おもき",
      "meaning": "importance, emphasis, stress"
    },
    {
      "question": "樵",
      "answer": "きこり",
      "meaning": "woodcutter, lumberjack, logger"
    },
    {
      "question": "尉",
      "answer": "じょう",
      "meaning": "inspector (third highest of the four administrative ranks of the ritsuryo system), (noh) old man, wh"
    },
    {
      "question": "祭儀",
      "answer": "さいぎ",
      "meaning": "rites, ritual"
    },
    {
      "question": "学習塾",
      "answer": "がくしゅうじゅく",
      "meaning": "cram school, private tutoring school"
    },
    {
      "question": "荻",
      "answer": "おぎ",
      "meaning": "Amur silvergrass (Miscanthus sacchariflorus)"
    },
    {
      "question": "揚力",
      "answer": "ようりょく",
      "meaning": "dynamic lift, lifting power"
    },
    {
      "question": "萎びる",
      "answer": "しなびる",
      "meaning": "to shrivel (e.g. cut vegetables, skin), to wilt, to fade, to wither, to be wizened"
    },
    {
      "question": "法事",
      "answer": "ほうじ",
      "meaning": "Buddhist memorial service"
    },
    {
      "question": "効果覿面",
      "answer": "こうかてきめん",
      "meaning": "having an immediate effect, taking immediate effect"
    },
    {
      "question": "大別",
      "answer": "たいべつ",
      "meaning": "general classification, broad categorization"
    },
    {
      "question": "鳥人",
      "answer": "ちょうじん",
      "meaning": "aviator, flying ace, birdman"
    },
    {
      "question": "礼法",
      "answer": "れいほう",
      "meaning": "etiquette, courtesy, manners"
    },
    {
      "question": "取調べ",
      "answer": "とりしらべ",
      "meaning": "investigation (e.g. by police or prosecutors), examination, inquiry, enquiry"
    },
    {
      "question": "断線",
      "answer": "だんせん",
      "meaning": "disconnection, interruption, burn-out"
    },
    {
      "question": "休職",
      "answer": "きゅうしょく",
      "meaning": "temporary retirement, suspension from office"
    },
    {
      "question": "波間",
      "answer": "なみま,なみあい,はかん",
      "meaning": "interval between the waves, gap between waves"
    },
    {
      "question": "絶倫",
      "answer": "ぜつりん",
      "meaning": "matchless, peerless, unequaled, unequalled, unparalleled, unrivaled"
    },
    {
      "question": "三つ巴",
      "answer": "みつどもえ",
      "meaning": "3 fat-comma shapes arranged to form a circle, 3-way struggle (wrestling, etc.)"
    },
    {
      "question": "皮肉屋",
      "answer": "ひにくや",
      "meaning": "ironist, sarcastic person, sharp tongue, satirist"
    },
    {
      "question": "愛の結晶",
      "answer": "あいのけっしょう",
      "meaning": "fruit of love, children"
    },
    {
      "question": "精魂",
      "answer": "せいこん",
      "meaning": "soul, spirit"
    },
    {
      "question": "信濃",
      "answer": "しなの",
      "meaning": "Shinano (former province located in present-day Nagano Prefecture and parts of Gifu Prefecture)"
    },
    {
      "question": "巫",
      "answer": "かんなぎ",
      "meaning": "medium, diviner, shaman, oracle"
    },
    {
      "question": "工兵",
      "answer": "こうへい",
      "meaning": "combat engineer, military engineer, combat engineering, military engineering"
    },
    {
      "question": "社会科",
      "answer": "しゃかいか",
      "meaning": "social studies"
    },
    {
      "question": "断層",
      "answer": "だんそう",
      "meaning": "fault, dislocation, gap, discrepancy"
    },
    {
      "question": "神通力",
      "answer": "じんつうりき,じんずうりき,じんづうりき",
      "meaning": "supernatural power, divine power, magical power"
    },
    {
      "question": "氷河期",
      "answer": "ひょうがき",
      "meaning": "glacial period, glacial epoch, glacial era, ice age, tough period, drought (of opportunities, jobs,"
    },
    {
      "question": "物書き",
      "answer": "ものかき",
      "meaning": "writer, copyist"
    },
    {
      "question": "介助",
      "answer": "かいじょ",
      "meaning": "help, assistance, aid"
    },
    {
      "question": "過負荷",
      "answer": "かふか",
      "meaning": "overload"
    },
    {
      "question": "奥の間",
      "answer": "おくのま",
      "meaning": "inner room"
    },
    {
      "question": "車座",
      "answer": "くるまざ",
      "meaning": "sitting in a circle"
    },
    {
      "question": "年来",
      "answer": "ねんらい",
      "meaning": "for some years"
    },
    {
      "question": "講談",
      "answer": "こうだん",
      "meaning": "storytelling (of war chronicles, revenge tales, etc.) with highly dramatic delivery, story"
    },
    {
      "question": "岩礁",
      "answer": "がんしょう",
      "meaning": "reef"
    },
    {
      "question": "風水",
      "answer": "ふうすい",
      "meaning": "feng shui, fengshui, wind and water"
    },
    {
      "question": "繁る",
      "answer": "しげる",
      "meaning": "to grow thickly, to be in full leaf, to be rampant, to luxuriate, to be luxurious"
    },
    {
      "question": "投げ合う",
      "answer": "なげあう",
      "meaning": "to throw something to each other, to pass something back and forth, to bandy something around, to ta"
    },
    {
      "question": "揚げ句",
      "answer": "あげく",
      "meaning": "after (a long process), at the end of, last line (of a renga)"
    },
    {
      "question": "公明正大",
      "answer": "こうめいせいだい",
      "meaning": "fair, just and upright, open and honest, aboveboard, honourable"
    },
    {
      "question": "離散",
      "answer": "りさん",
      "meaning": "dispersal, scattering, discrete"
    },
    {
      "question": "狛犬",
      "answer": "こまいぬ",
      "meaning": "(stone) guardian lion-dogs at Shinto shrine"
    },
    {
      "question": "軋る",
      "answer": "きしる",
      "meaning": "to creak, to squeak, to grate, to grind, to rasp"
    },
    {
      "question": "定期便",
      "answer": "ていきびん",
      "meaning": "regular service"
    },
    {
      "question": "拡充",
      "answer": "かくじゅう",
      "meaning": "expansion"
    },
    {
      "question": "体重計",
      "answer": "たいじゅうけい",
      "meaning": "scale, bathroom scale, weighing machine"
    },
    {
      "question": "鬼女",
      "answer": "きじょ",
      "meaning": "demoness, witch, ogress, she-devil, married woman"
    },
    {
      "question": "型紙",
      "answer": "かたがみ",
      "meaning": "pattern paper (for dressmaking)"
    },
    {
      "question": "脳死",
      "answer": "のうし",
      "meaning": "brain death"
    },
    {
      "question": "葉擦れ",
      "answer": "はずれ",
      "meaning": "rustling of leaves, rustling of grass"
    },
    {
      "question": "凭れる",
      "answer": "もたれる",
      "meaning": "to lean against, to lean on, to recline on, to lie heavy (on the stomach), to be uneasily digested"
    },
    {
      "question": "論調",
      "answer": "ろんちょう",
      "meaning": "tone (of argument), tenor, drift"
    },
    {
      "question": "不粋",
      "answer": "ぶすい",
      "meaning": "boorish, inelegant, unpolished, unromantic, tactless"
    },
    {
      "question": "自主トレ",
      "answer": "じしゅトレ",
      "meaning": "independent training (e.g. of athletes working without a coach)"
    },
    {
      "question": "軽トラ",
      "answer": "けいトラ",
      "meaning": "minitruck, light truck, small truck, light pickup"
    },
    {
      "question": "標準語",
      "answer": "ひょうじゅんご",
      "meaning": "standard language (used in government, education, etc.), standard Japanese"
    },
    {
      "question": "信義",
      "answer": "しんぎ",
      "meaning": "faith, fidelity, loyalty"
    },
    {
      "question": "考え物",
      "answer": "かんがえもの",
      "meaning": "puzzle, problem"
    },
    {
      "question": "受動的",
      "answer": "じゅどうてき",
      "meaning": "passive"
    },
    {
      "question": "激増",
      "answer": "げきぞう",
      "meaning": "sharp increase, sudden rise"
    },
    {
      "question": "具象",
      "answer": "ぐしょう",
      "meaning": "embodying, expressing concretely"
    },
    {
      "question": "収斂",
      "answer": "しゅうれん",
      "meaning": "astringency, constriction, contraction, collecting (e.g. opinions), putting together, summarizing, e"
    },
    {
      "question": "放送局",
      "answer": "ほうそうきょく",
      "meaning": "broadcasting station, broadcaster"
    },
    {
      "question": "軍略",
      "answer": "ぐんりゃく",
      "meaning": "strategy, tactics"
    },
    {
      "question": "銃創",
      "answer": "じゅうそう",
      "meaning": "gunshot wound"
    },
    {
      "question": "世渡り",
      "answer": "よわたり",
      "meaning": "making a living, getting on in the world, subsistence"
    },
    {
      "question": "吶喊",
      "answer": "とっかん",
      "meaning": "battlecry, cheer, cry where one breathes in a large volume of air and then releases it suddenly in a"
    },
    {
      "question": "明晰夢",
      "answer": "めいせきむ",
      "meaning": "lucid dream, dream in which the dreamer is aware that they are dreaming"
    },
    {
      "question": "菜の花",
      "answer": "なのはな",
      "meaning": "rape blossoms, rapeseed flowers"
    },
    {
      "question": "噴煙",
      "answer": "ふんえん",
      "meaning": "(eruption of) smoke"
    },
    {
      "question": "仕る",
      "answer": "つかまつる",
      "meaning": "to serve, to do"
    },
    {
      "question": "公民館",
      "answer": "こうみんかん",
      "meaning": "public hall, community center, community centre"
    },
    {
      "question": "消防士",
      "answer": "しょうぼうし",
      "meaning": "firefighter, fireman"
    },
    {
      "question": "通夜",
      "answer": "つや,つうや",
      "meaning": "all-night vigil over a body, wake"
    },
    {
      "question": "海千山千",
      "answer": "うみせんやません",
      "meaning": "sly old dog, old fox"
    },
    {
      "question": "礼金",
      "answer": "れいきん",
      "meaning": "money (given as thanks), reward money, fee, recompense, remuneration, honorarium, key money, fee pai"
    },
    {
      "question": "根から",
      "answer": "ねから",
      "meaning": "since the beginning, natural-born (salesman, etc.), absolutely (not), (not) at all"
    },
    {
      "question": "商業都市",
      "answer": "しょうぎょうとし",
      "meaning": "commercial city"
    },
    {
      "question": "体高",
      "answer": "たいこう",
      "meaning": "height (measured at the withers)"
    },
    {
      "question": "寝巻",
      "answer": "ねまき",
      "meaning": "sleep-wear, nightclothes, pyjamas, pajamas, nightgown, nightdress"
    },
    {
      "question": "水害",
      "answer": "すいがい",
      "meaning": "water damage, flood disaster"
    },
    {
      "question": "土色",
      "answer": "つちいろ",
      "meaning": "earth (color, colour), ashen, deathly pale"
    },
    {
      "question": "返金",
      "answer": "へんきん",
      "meaning": "repayment"
    },
    {
      "question": "金目",
      "answer": "かねめ,きんめ",
      "meaning": "monetary value, Edo-period unit of gold coinage, golden eyes (of a cat, etc.), splendid alfonsino (B"
    },
    {
      "question": "春の日",
      "answer": "はるのひ",
      "meaning": "day of spring, spring sun"
    },
    {
      "question": "心が弾む",
      "answer": "こころがはずむ",
      "meaning": "to be excited, to be elated"
    },
    {
      "question": "乳液",
      "answer": "にゅうえき",
      "meaning": "latex (milky fluid found in plants), milky lotion (cosmetic), body milk"
    },
    {
      "question": "答辞",
      "answer": "とうじ",
      "meaning": "address in reply (e.g. at a ceremony), formal reply"
    },
    {
      "question": "自動拳銃",
      "answer": "じどうけんじゅう",
      "meaning": "automatic pistol"
    },
    {
      "question": "警察犬",
      "answer": "けいさつけん",
      "meaning": "police dog, K9"
    },
    {
      "question": "挙",
      "answer": "きょ",
      "meaning": "action, behavior, behaviour, move, recommendation (of a person for a position)"
    },
    {
      "question": "省庁",
      "answer": "しょうちょう",
      "meaning": "ministries and government offices, the authorities"
    },
    {
      "question": "苛酷",
      "answer": "かこく",
      "meaning": "severe, harsh, hard, cruel, rigorous"
    },
    {
      "question": "大望",
      "answer": "たいもう,たいぼう",
      "meaning": "aspiration, ambition"
    },
    {
      "question": "粘着性",
      "answer": "ねんちゃくせい",
      "meaning": "adhesion, stickiness, viscosity"
    },
    {
      "question": "新着",
      "answer": "しんちゃく",
      "meaning": "new arrivals, new acquisitions"
    },
    {
      "question": "経年劣化",
      "answer": "けいねんれっか",
      "meaning": "degradation over time, time-related deterioration"
    },
    {
      "question": "国柄",
      "answer": "くにがら",
      "meaning": "national character, regional character"
    },
    {
      "question": "不束者",
      "answer": "ふつつかもの",
      "meaning": "incompetent person, ignoramus"
    },
    {
      "question": "金眼",
      "answer": "きんめ",
      "meaning": "golden eyes (of a cat, etc.), splendid alfonsino (Beryx splendens)"
    },
    {
      "question": "天の声",
      "answer": "てんのこえ",
      "meaning": "heavenly voice, off the record instructions, influential person's opinion, powerful person's verdict"
    },
    {
      "question": "榴弾",
      "answer": "りゅうだん",
      "meaning": "high-explosive projectile"
    },
    {
      "question": "東欧",
      "answer": "とうおう",
      "meaning": "Eastern Europe"
    },
    {
      "question": "隠遁",
      "answer": "いんとん",
      "meaning": "retirement (from the world), seclusion"
    },
    {
      "question": "新星",
      "answer": "しんせい",
      "meaning": "nova, new face, new star"
    },
    {
      "question": "箸を取る",
      "answer": "はしをとる",
      "meaning": "to take up one's chopsticks (to begin a meal), to start to eat, to eat"
    },
    {
      "question": "頼り甲斐",
      "answer": "たよりがい",
      "meaning": "reliability, trustworthiness, dependability"
    },
    {
      "question": "次官",
      "answer": "じかん,すけ",
      "meaning": "vice-minister, undersecretary, assistant director (second highest of the four administrative positio"
    },
    {
      "question": "手摺り",
      "answer": "てすり,てずり",
      "meaning": "handrail, railing, banister, printing by hand, hand-printing"
    },
    {
      "question": "被り",
      "answer": "かぶり",
      "meaning": "headdress, crown, covering, fogging (photography), blushing"
    },
    {
      "question": "饐える",
      "answer": "すえる",
      "meaning": "to go bad, to turn sour"
    },
    {
      "question": "変則",
      "answer": "へんそく",
      "meaning": "irregularity, anomaly"
    },
    {
      "question": "権謀術数",
      "answer": "けんぼうじゅっすう",
      "meaning": "trickery, wiles, finesse, Machiavellism"
    },
    {
      "question": "大台",
      "answer": "おおだい",
      "meaning": "(major) mark, level, barrier, 100-yen unit (stock market)"
    },
    {
      "question": "用命",
      "answer": "ようめい",
      "meaning": "command, order, request"
    },
    {
      "question": "知恵熱",
      "answer": "ちえねつ,ちえぼとり",
      "meaning": "teething fever, developmental fever, fever that brings with it an intellectual or psycho-development"
    },
    {
      "question": "農奴",
      "answer": "のうど",
      "meaning": "serf"
    },
    {
      "question": "邪法",
      "answer": "じゃほう",
      "meaning": "heresy, heretical teachings, black magic"
    },
    {
      "question": "竹筒",
      "answer": "たけづつ",
      "meaning": "container made by cutting a piece of bamboo lengthways, bamboo tube, bamboo cylinder"
    },
    {
      "question": "用務員",
      "answer": "ようむいん",
      "meaning": "orderly, janitor"
    },
    {
      "question": "佃煮",
      "answer": "つくだに",
      "meaning": "preserved food boiled in soy"
    },
    {
      "question": "揚げ",
      "answer": "あげ",
      "meaning": "tuck (e.g. in a dress), frying, fried food, aburaage, thin deep-fried slices of tofu"
    },
    {
      "question": "送付",
      "answer": "そうふ",
      "meaning": "sending (esp. email attachments), forwarding, remitting"
    },
    {
      "question": "手慰み",
      "answer": "てなぐさみ",
      "meaning": "fingering an object (in killing time), amusing oneself, diversion, gambling"
    },
    {
      "question": "無上",
      "answer": "むじょう",
      "meaning": "supreme, greatest, highest, best"
    },
    {
      "question": "若しくは",
      "answer": "もしくは",
      "meaning": "or, otherwise"
    },
    {
      "question": "漂着",
      "answer": "ひょうちゃく",
      "meaning": "drifting ashore"
    },
    {
      "question": "元彼",
      "answer": "もとかれ",
      "meaning": "former boyfriend, ex-boyfriend"
    },
    {
      "question": "体内時計",
      "answer": "たいないどけい",
      "meaning": "biological clock"
    },
    {
      "question": "小奇麗",
      "answer": "こぎれい",
      "meaning": "neat, trim, tidy, pretty"
    },
    {
      "question": "肺活量",
      "answer": "はいかつりょう",
      "meaning": "lung capacity"
    },
    {
      "question": "長風呂",
      "answer": "ながぶろ",
      "meaning": "long bath, staying in the bath for a long time"
    },
    {
      "question": "弱冠",
      "answer": "じゃっかん",
      "meaning": "twenty years of age, youth, early age, tender age of ..."
    },
    {
      "question": "兄姉",
      "answer": "けいし,きょうだい",
      "meaning": "brother and sister"
    },
    {
      "question": "里芋",
      "answer": "さといも",
      "meaning": "taro (Colocasia esculenta), dasheen, eddo"
    },
    {
      "question": "立ち働く",
      "answer": "たちはたらく",
      "meaning": "to go about one's work"
    },
    {
      "question": "諸手",
      "answer": "もろて,もろで",
      "meaning": "both hands"
    },
    {
      "question": "慰労",
      "answer": "いろう",
      "meaning": "recognition of services"
    },
    {
      "question": "生焼け",
      "answer": "なまやけ",
      "meaning": "half-roasted, half-baked, rare"
    },
    {
      "question": "大坂",
      "answer": "おおさか,おおざか",
      "meaning": "Osaka (city, prefecture), large hill"
    },
    {
      "question": "工務店",
      "answer": "こうむてん",
      "meaning": "engineering firm, contractor"
    },
    {
      "question": "密書",
      "answer": "みっしょ",
      "meaning": "secret message"
    },
    {
      "question": "琵琶湖",
      "answer": "びわこ",
      "meaning": "Lake Biwa"
    },
    {
      "question": "権益",
      "answer": "けんえき",
      "meaning": "(one's) interests"
    },
    {
      "question": "七度",
      "answer": "ななたび,しちど",
      "meaning": "seven times, many times, seventh (interval)"
    },
    {
      "question": "手練手管",
      "answer": "てれんてくだ",
      "meaning": "wiles, art of coaxing"
    },
    {
      "question": "襟を正す",
      "answer": "えりをただす",
      "meaning": "to straighten oneself, to straighten one's clothes and one's posture, to adopt a more serious attitu"
    },
    {
      "question": "食が進む",
      "answer": "しょくがすすむ",
      "meaning": "to have a good appetite"
    },
    {
      "question": "汚名返上",
      "answer": "おめいへんじょう",
      "meaning": "clear one's name, redeem oneself, clear (vindicate) one's honor (reputation)"
    },
    {
      "question": "柴犬",
      "answer": "しばいぬ,しばけん",
      "meaning": "shiba (Japanese breed of dog), shiba inu, brushwood dog"
    },
    {
      "question": "空砲",
      "answer": "くうほう",
      "meaning": "empty gun, gun loaded with blanks, firing a blank"
    },
    {
      "question": "多寡",
      "answer": "たか",
      "meaning": "degree (of something), greatness or smallness (of something), quantity, number, amount, size"
    },
    {
      "question": "寝技",
      "answer": "ねわざ",
      "meaning": "pinning technique (in wrestling or judo), underhanded dealings"
    },
    {
      "question": "馳走",
      "answer": "ちそう",
      "meaning": "treat, banquet, feast, entertainment, goodies, running about"
    },
    {
      "question": "日陰者",
      "answer": "ひかげもの",
      "meaning": "person who avoids others, social outcast"
    },
    {
      "question": "作り込む",
      "answer": "つくりこむ",
      "meaning": "to perfect, to detail, to polish, to bring to completion, to make (inside something)"
    },
    {
      "question": "肉食動物",
      "answer": "にくしょくどうぶつ",
      "meaning": "carnivore"
    },
    {
      "question": "舞姫",
      "answer": "まいひめ,ぶき",
      "meaning": "female dancer, dancing girl, danseuse"
    },
    {
      "question": "演武",
      "answer": "えんぶ",
      "meaning": "martial arts demonstration, martial arts training"
    },
    {
      "question": "空隙",
      "answer": "くうげき",
      "meaning": "vacant space, aperture, gap, opening"
    },
    {
      "question": "遠退く",
      "answer": "とおのく",
      "meaning": "to become distant, to recede"
    },
    {
      "question": "靴紐",
      "answer": "くつひも",
      "meaning": "shoelace, bootlace"
    },
    {
      "question": "多勢",
      "answer": "たぜい",
      "meaning": "great numbers, numerical superiority"
    },
    {
      "question": "幕が開く",
      "answer": "まくがあく",
      "meaning": "to start an act (of a play), to have curtains open, to have an (event, period of history, etc.) star"
    },
    {
      "question": "二宮",
      "answer": "にぐう",
      "meaning": "the Two Ise Shrines"
    },
    {
      "question": "乱数",
      "answer": "らんすう",
      "meaning": "random number"
    },
    {
      "question": "白波",
      "answer": "しらなみ",
      "meaning": "whitecaps, white-crested waves, thief"
    },
    {
      "question": "前人未到",
      "answer": "ぜんじんみとう",
      "meaning": "untrodden (region, field of study, etc.), unprecedented (discovery, achievement, etc.)"
    },
    {
      "question": "売り捌く",
      "answer": "うりさばく",
      "meaning": "to sell out, to sell widely, to sell on a large scale"
    },
    {
      "question": "明太子",
      "answer": "めんたいこ",
      "meaning": "walleye pollack roe (generally served salted and spiced with red pepper)"
    },
    {
      "question": "視神経",
      "answer": "ししんけい",
      "meaning": "optic nerve"
    },
    {
      "question": "原液",
      "answer": "げんえき",
      "meaning": "undiluted solution (of)"
    },
    {
      "question": "汚れ役",
      "answer": "よごれやく",
      "meaning": "role of a villain (film, drama, etc.), bad-guy role, social outcast role"
    },
    {
      "question": "貴賤",
      "answer": "きせん",
      "meaning": "high and low (social standing)"
    },
    {
      "question": "大見得",
      "answer": "おおみえ",
      "meaning": "dramatic pose, grand gesture, grandstanding"
    },
    {
      "question": "青磁",
      "answer": "せいじ,あおじ",
      "meaning": "celadon porcelain"
    },
    {
      "question": "塾生",
      "answer": "じゅくせい",
      "meaning": "private-school student"
    },
    {
      "question": "半死",
      "answer": "はんし",
      "meaning": "half-dead"
    },
    {
      "question": "可変",
      "answer": "かへん",
      "meaning": "variable, changeable, convertible, controllable"
    },
    {
      "question": "国母",
      "answer": "こくぼ",
      "meaning": "empress, empress dowager"
    },
    {
      "question": "綺麗好き",
      "answer": "きれいずき",
      "meaning": "love of cleanliness, liking to keep things clean, tidiness (of people), neatness"
    },
    {
      "question": "拭き掃除",
      "answer": "ふきそうじ",
      "meaning": "cleaning, scrubbing"
    },
    {
      "question": "映り",
      "answer": "うつり",
      "meaning": "projection, reflection, image, reception (e.g. TV), picture quality, match, harmony"
    },
    {
      "question": "法務",
      "answer": "ほうむ",
      "meaning": "judicial affairs, clerical duty (in a temple)"
    },
    {
      "question": "黒山",
      "answer": "くろやま",
      "meaning": "large crowd, mass of people"
    },
    {
      "question": "千代",
      "answer": "ちよ",
      "meaning": "thousand years, very long period, forever"
    },
    {
      "question": "絵図",
      "answer": "えず",
      "meaning": "illustration, drawing"
    },
    {
      "question": "効用",
      "answer": "こうよう",
      "meaning": "use, utility, effect, benefit"
    },
    {
      "question": "印字",
      "answer": "いんじ",
      "meaning": "printing, typing, printed character, typed character, character(s) carved onto a seal"
    },
    {
      "question": "号車",
      "answer": "ごうしゃ",
      "meaning": "suffix for train car numbers"
    },
    {
      "question": "出征",
      "answer": "しゅっせい",
      "meaning": "going to war, departure for the front, departure for military service (in response to a draft)"
    },
    {
      "question": "檜",
      "answer": "ひのき,ひ",
      "meaning": "hinoki cypress (Chamaecyparis obtusa), Japanese cypress"
    },
    {
      "question": "廃車",
      "answer": "はいしゃ",
      "meaning": "decommissioned vehicle, out of service vehicle, end of life vehicle, deregistered vehicle, unregiste"
    },
    {
      "question": "重税",
      "answer": "じゅうぜい",
      "meaning": "heavy taxation"
    },
    {
      "question": "寸劇",
      "answer": "すんげき",
      "meaning": "short play, skit"
    },
    {
      "question": "脱色",
      "answer": "だっしょく",
      "meaning": "decolourization, decolorization, decolourisation, decolorisation, bleaching"
    },
    {
      "question": "断行",
      "answer": "だんこう,だんぎょう",
      "meaning": "decisive action, carrying out, resolute enforcement, execution, asceticism, practices that eliminate"
    },
    {
      "question": "宮仕え",
      "answer": "みやづかえ",
      "meaning": "court service"
    },
    {
      "question": "長らえる",
      "answer": "ながらえる",
      "meaning": "to have a long life, to live a long time"
    },
    {
      "question": "筋張る",
      "answer": "すじばる",
      "meaning": "to become sinewy, to behave formally"
    },
    {
      "question": "皇太子妃",
      "answer": "こうたいしひ",
      "meaning": "crown princess"
    },
    {
      "question": "熱帯魚",
      "answer": "ねったいぎょ",
      "meaning": "tropical fish"
    },
    {
      "question": "少子化",
      "answer": "しょうしか",
      "meaning": "declining birth rates, decrease in the number of children"
    },
    {
      "question": "八方美人",
      "answer": "はっぽうびじん",
      "meaning": "everybody's friend, person who is affable to everybody, flawlessly beautiful woman, flawless beauty"
    },
    {
      "question": "譲り合う",
      "answer": "ゆずりあう",
      "meaning": "to give and take, to make mutual concessions, to compromise"
    },
    {
      "question": "乾す",
      "answer": "ほす,さぼす",
      "meaning": "to air, to dry, to desiccate, to drain (off), to drink up, to deprive of a role, job, etc., to expos"
    },
    {
      "question": "柚",
      "answer": "ゆず,ゆ,ゆう",
      "meaning": "yuzu (Citrus ichangensis x C. reticulata)"
    },
    {
      "question": "拝",
      "answer": "はい",
      "meaning": "bowing one's head (in respect or worship), worship, respectfully yours"
    },
    {
      "question": "前世紀",
      "answer": "ぜんせいき",
      "meaning": "last century, ancient times"
    },
    {
      "question": "超音速",
      "answer": "ちょうおんそく",
      "meaning": "supersonic speed"
    },
    {
      "question": "放射能",
      "answer": "ほうしゃのう",
      "meaning": "radioactivity"
    },
    {
      "question": "抱負",
      "answer": "ほうふ",
      "meaning": "aspiration, ambition, pretension"
    },
    {
      "question": "脳神経",
      "answer": "のうしんけい",
      "meaning": "cranial nerves, cerebral nerves"
    },
    {
      "question": "終着駅",
      "answer": "しゅうちゃくえき",
      "meaning": "terminal station"
    },
    {
      "question": "名器",
      "answer": "めいき",
      "meaning": "famous utensil, excellent utensil, famed musical instrument (e.g. a Stradivarius), excellent musical"
    },
    {
      "question": "折り合う",
      "answer": "おりあう",
      "meaning": "to reach an agreement, to come to an understanding, to compromise (with), to meet halfway, to get al"
    },
    {
      "question": "紙屑",
      "answer": "かみくず",
      "meaning": "wastepaper, scrap of paper, paper scraps"
    },
    {
      "question": "朝風呂",
      "answer": "あさぶろ",
      "meaning": "morning bath"
    },
    {
      "question": "酒代",
      "answer": "さかだい",
      "meaning": "alcohol expenses, tip"
    },
    {
      "question": "対消滅",
      "answer": "ついしょうめつ",
      "meaning": "annihilation (of particle and anti-particle)"
    },
    {
      "question": "加重",
      "answer": "かじゅう,かちょう",
      "meaning": "weighting (in averaging), aggravation"
    },
    {
      "question": "秋田",
      "answer": "あきた",
      "meaning": "Akita (city, prefecture)"
    },
    {
      "question": "喘息",
      "answer": "ぜんそく",
      "meaning": "asthma"
    },
    {
      "question": "反社会的",
      "answer": "はんしゃかいてき",
      "meaning": "antisocial, contrary to public order or morality, offensive, sociopathic, immoral, obscene, illegal"
    },
    {
      "question": "鉄分",
      "answer": "てつぶん",
      "meaning": "iron (content)"
    },
    {
      "question": "浮き出す",
      "answer": "うきだす",
      "meaning": "to surface, to come to the top, to stand out (e.g. against a background)"
    },
    {
      "question": "叩き返す",
      "answer": "たたきかえす",
      "meaning": "to knock back, to strike back, to beat in revenge"
    },
    {
      "question": "白魔",
      "answer": "はくま",
      "meaning": "heavy snowfall, white devil"
    },
    {
      "question": "本郷",
      "answer": "ほんごう",
      "meaning": "one's hometown"
    },
    {
      "question": "保安官",
      "answer": "ほあんかん",
      "meaning": "peace officer, sheriff"
    },
    {
      "question": "穀倉地帯",
      "answer": "こくそうちたい",
      "meaning": "grain-producing region"
    },
    {
      "question": "面相",
      "answer": "めんそう",
      "meaning": "countenance, features, looks"
    },
    {
      "question": "貿易商",
      "answer": "ぼうえきしょう",
      "meaning": "trader"
    },
    {
      "question": "手籠め",
      "answer": "てごめ",
      "meaning": "rape, violation"
    },
    {
      "question": "信任",
      "answer": "しんにん",
      "meaning": "trust, confidence, credence"
    },
    {
      "question": "降車",
      "answer": "こうしゃ",
      "meaning": "alighting (from a train, bus, etc.), getting off, getting out (of a car)"
    },
    {
      "question": "朴訥",
      "answer": "ぼくとつ",
      "meaning": "unsophisticated, ruggedly honest, artless, unaffected, simple, naive"
    },
    {
      "question": "片面",
      "answer": "かためん",
      "meaning": "one side"
    },
    {
      "question": "名が泣く",
      "answer": "ながなく",
      "meaning": "to not be worthy of the reputation (e.g. restaurant, Diet member, etc.), to not be worth the name, t"
    },
    {
      "question": "証券",
      "answer": "しょうけん",
      "meaning": "bond, bill, certificate, security"
    },
    {
      "question": "潜航",
      "answer": "せんこう",
      "meaning": "submarine voyage, underwater navigation"
    },
    {
      "question": "七三",
      "answer": "しちさん",
      "meaning": "7 or 3 ratio, hair parted on one side"
    },
    {
      "question": "大腿部",
      "answer": "だいたいぶ",
      "meaning": "femur (femora)"
    },
    {
      "question": "治水",
      "answer": "ちすい",
      "meaning": "river management, river improvement, flood control"
    },
    {
      "question": "革紐",
      "answer": "かわひも",
      "meaning": "leather strap, thong, leash"
    },
    {
      "question": "足捌き",
      "answer": "あしさばき",
      "meaning": "footwork (in martial arts, sports, etc.)"
    },
    {
      "question": "勇名",
      "answer": "ゆうめい",
      "meaning": "fame (for one's bravery), great renown"
    },
    {
      "question": "今一",
      "answer": "いまいち",
      "meaning": "not quite (right), not very good, somewhat (lacking)"
    },
    {
      "question": "連戦連勝",
      "answer": "れんせんれんしょう",
      "meaning": "succession of victories"
    },
    {
      "question": "赤っ恥",
      "answer": "あかっぱじ",
      "meaning": "shame, disgrace"
    },
    {
      "question": "栖",
      "answer": "すみか,す",
      "meaning": "dwelling, house, residence, den, habitat, nest, rookery, breeding place, hive, haunt, (spider's) web"
    },
    {
      "question": "卍",
      "answer": "まんじ",
      "meaning": "swastika (esp. counterclockwise form as a Buddhist symbol), fylfot, gammadion, swastika-shaped famil"
    },
    {
      "question": "琵琶",
      "answer": "びわ",
      "meaning": "biwa (Japanese lute)"
    },
    {
      "question": "軍船",
      "answer": "ぐんせん,いくさぶね",
      "meaning": "(wind or human-powered) warship"
    },
    {
      "question": "当夜",
      "answer": "とうや",
      "meaning": "that night, tonight"
    },
    {
      "question": "運航",
      "answer": "うんこう",
      "meaning": "operating (e.g. ships, aircraft)"
    },
    {
      "question": "傑出",
      "answer": "けっしゅつ",
      "meaning": "being outstanding, excelling, being foremost"
    },
    {
      "question": "神棚",
      "answer": "かみだな",
      "meaning": "kamidana, household shrine, home shrine"
    },
    {
      "question": "遮二無二",
      "answer": "しゃにむに",
      "meaning": "desperately, recklessly, rush headlong"
    },
    {
      "question": "亡い",
      "answer": "ない",
      "meaning": "dead"
    },
    {
      "question": "由縁",
      "answer": "ゆえん",
      "meaning": "acquaintance, relation, affinity, reason"
    },
    {
      "question": "盟",
      "answer": "めい",
      "meaning": "alliance, aimag, league, administrative subdivision in Mongolia and Inner Mongolia"
    },
    {
      "question": "療養所",
      "answer": "りょうようじょ,りょうようしょ",
      "meaning": "sanatorium"
    },
    {
      "question": "福引",
      "answer": "ふくびき",
      "meaning": "lottery, tombola, drawing"
    },
    {
      "question": "舷側",
      "answer": "げんそく",
      "meaning": "ship's side, broadside"
    },
    {
      "question": "台地",
      "answer": "だいち",
      "meaning": "plateau, tableland, eminence"
    },
    {
      "question": "隘路",
      "answer": "あいろ",
      "meaning": "defile, narrow path, bottleneck, impasse"
    },
    {
      "question": "祭祀",
      "answer": "さいし",
      "meaning": "ritual, religious service, festival"
    },
    {
      "question": "夜盗",
      "answer": "やとう",
      "meaning": "night burglar"
    },
    {
      "question": "片栗粉",
      "answer": "かたくりこ",
      "meaning": "potato starch, starch of dogtooth violet"
    },
    {
      "question": "遁走",
      "answer": "とんそう",
      "meaning": "flight, escape"
    },
    {
      "question": "子供騙し",
      "answer": "こどもだまし",
      "meaning": "trick that may deceive a child, transparent ploy, mere child's play, kid stuff, puerile trick"
    },
    {
      "question": "女っ気",
      "answer": "おんなっけ",
      "meaning": "female presence"
    },
    {
      "question": "派手好き",
      "answer": "はでずき",
      "meaning": "flamboyant, extravagant, showy, attention-seeking"
    },
    {
      "question": "若菜",
      "answer": "わかな",
      "meaning": "young greens, young herbs"
    },
    {
      "question": "治験",
      "answer": "ちけん",
      "meaning": "clinical trial"
    },
    {
      "question": "怪文書",
      "answer": "かいぶんしょ",
      "meaning": "dubious document, anonymous document containing defamatory statements"
    },
    {
      "question": "ハート形",
      "answer": "ハートがた",
      "meaning": "heart shape"
    },
    {
      "question": "陸上競技",
      "answer": "りくじょうきょうぎ",
      "meaning": "track-and-field events"
    },
    {
      "question": "紙包み",
      "answer": "かみづつみ",
      "meaning": "paper package"
    },
    {
      "question": "白髭",
      "answer": "しろひげ",
      "meaning": "grey moustache, white beard"
    },
    {
      "question": "陰謀論",
      "answer": "いんぼうろん",
      "meaning": "conspiracy theory"
    },
    {
      "question": "檄",
      "answer": "げき",
      "meaning": "(written) appeal, circular, manifesto, encouragement, encouraging words, letter of encouragement"
    },
    {
      "question": "秋晴れ",
      "answer": "あきばれ",
      "meaning": "clear autumnal weather"
    },
    {
      "question": "読み物",
      "answer": "よみもの",
      "meaning": "reading matter, reading material"
    },
    {
      "question": "合作",
      "answer": "がっさく",
      "meaning": "collaboration, joint work"
    },
    {
      "question": "深酒",
      "answer": "ふかざけ",
      "meaning": "heavy drinking"
    },
    {
      "question": "賑やかす",
      "answer": "にぎやかす",
      "meaning": "to make lively, to make exciting"
    },
    {
      "question": "本降り",
      "answer": "ほんぶり",
      "meaning": "heavy rainfall, heavy snowfall, steady rainfall, downpour, raining in earnest"
    },
    {
      "question": "神人",
      "answer": "しんじん,じにん,かみんちゅ",
      "meaning": "gods and men, godlike person, person as powerful as a god, person as refined as a god, low-ranking S"
    },
    {
      "question": "大刀",
      "answer": "たち,だいとう",
      "meaning": "long sword (esp. the tachi, worn on the hip edge down by samurai), large sword, straight single-edge"
    },
    {
      "question": "被服",
      "answer": "ひふく",
      "meaning": "clothing"
    },
    {
      "question": "着流し",
      "answer": "きながし",
      "meaning": "dressing in kimono without hakama (for a man), dressing casually"
    },
    {
      "question": "不退転",
      "answer": "ふたいてん",
      "meaning": "determination, conviction"
    },
    {
      "question": "曲る",
      "answer": "まがる",
      "meaning": "to bend, to curve, to warp, to wind, to twist, to turn, to be awry, to be askew, to be crooked"
    },
    {
      "question": "五人組",
      "answer": "ごにんぐみ",
      "meaning": "five-family unit, five-man group, quintet"
    },
    {
      "question": "傲岸",
      "answer": "ごうがん",
      "meaning": "haughty, arrogant, supercilious"
    },
    {
      "question": "訓示",
      "answer": "くんじ",
      "meaning": "instruction, direction, briefing"
    },
    {
      "question": "土佐",
      "answer": "とさ",
      "meaning": "Tosa (former province located in present-day Kochi Prefecture)"
    },
    {
      "question": "劫",
      "answer": "こう,ごう",
      "meaning": "kalpa (eon, aeon), ko (in go), position that allows for eternal capture and recapture of the same st"
    },
    {
      "question": "鳥頭",
      "answer": "とりかぶと,とりあたま,とりがしら",
      "meaning": "aconite (esp. species Aconitum japonicum), wolfsbane, monkshood, traditional bugaku hat, being very"
    },
    {
      "question": "密航",
      "answer": "みっこう",
      "meaning": "smuggling (people), stowing away"
    },
    {
      "question": "帯同",
      "answer": "たいどう",
      "meaning": "taking (someone) along"
    },
    {
      "question": "黄緑",
      "answer": "きみどり,おうりょく",
      "meaning": "pea green, yellow-green"
    },
    {
      "question": "痩せぎす",
      "answer": "やせぎす",
      "meaning": "skinny"
    },
    {
      "question": "自然環境",
      "answer": "しぜんかんきょう",
      "meaning": "natural (physical) environment"
    },
    {
      "question": "差額",
      "answer": "さがく",
      "meaning": "balance, difference (in price, cost), margin"
    },
    {
      "question": "活劇",
      "answer": "かつげき",
      "meaning": "action film, action movie, action drama, riotous scene, fight scene"
    },
    {
      "question": "郭",
      "answer": "くるわ,かく",
      "meaning": "district, quarter, enclosure, area enclosed by earthwork, red-light district"
    },
    {
      "question": "塩胡椒",
      "answer": "しおこしょう",
      "meaning": "salt and pepper, seasoning with salt and pepper"
    },
    {
      "question": "運輸",
      "answer": "うんゆ",
      "meaning": "transportation"
    },
    {
      "question": "積",
      "answer": "せき",
      "meaning": "product, volume, area"
    },
    {
      "question": "疼痛",
      "answer": "とうつう",
      "meaning": "pain"
    },
    {
      "question": "確度",
      "answer": "かくど",
      "meaning": "degree of accuracy"
    },
    {
      "question": "大大",
      "answer": "だいだい",
      "meaning": "very big, very large, taking up a lot of space"
    },
    {
      "question": "日柄",
      "answer": "ひがら",
      "meaning": "lucky or unlucky aspect of a given day"
    },
    {
      "question": "新撰組",
      "answer": "しんせんぐみ",
      "meaning": "Shinsengumi, Edo period police and military force dedicated to suppressing anti-shogunate activities"
    },
    {
      "question": "刀鍛冶",
      "answer": "かたなかじ",
      "meaning": "swordsmith"
    },
    {
      "question": "古語",
      "answer": "こご",
      "meaning": "obsolete word, old proverb, ancient (Japanese) language"
    },
    {
      "question": "知恵袋",
      "answer": "ちえぶくろ",
      "meaning": "fount of knowledge, the smart one (of a group of people), brains, bag full of wisdom, bag containing"
    },
    {
      "question": "心的",
      "answer": "しんてき",
      "meaning": "mental, psychological, physical"
    },
    {
      "question": "色艶",
      "answer": "いろつや",
      "meaning": "colour and lustre, color and luster, complexion, colour, color"
    },
    {
      "question": "据え置き",
      "answer": "すえおき",
      "meaning": "deferment (e.g. of savings), leaving (a thing) as it stands, unredeemed, unredeemable, irredeemable,"
    },
    {
      "question": "匂わす",
      "answer": "におわす",
      "meaning": "to give off (a smell, scent, aroma), to smell of, to perfume (a room, etc.), to hint at, to suggest,"
    },
    {
      "question": "通り雨",
      "answer": "とおりあめ",
      "meaning": "shower, passing rain"
    },
    {
      "question": "角笛",
      "answer": "つのぶえ",
      "meaning": "horn (instrument; made of animal horn), bugle, hunting horn"
    },
    {
      "question": "機長",
      "answer": "きちょう",
      "meaning": "captain (of an aircraft)"
    },
    {
      "question": "草野球",
      "answer": "くさやきゅう",
      "meaning": "grass-lot baseball"
    },
    {
      "question": "真正",
      "answer": "しんせい",
      "meaning": "genuine, authentic, true, pure"
    },
    {
      "question": "金の卵",
      "answer": "きんのたまご",
      "meaning": "golden child, promising young talent, gold egg, golden egg, gold mine, cash cow, golden goose"
    },
    {
      "question": "独り言つ",
      "answer": "ひとりごつ",
      "meaning": "to talk to oneself, to mutter"
    },
    {
      "question": "雨降り",
      "answer": "あめふり",
      "meaning": "rainfall, rainy weather, rainy, wet"
    },
    {
      "question": "銀世界",
      "answer": "ぎんせかい",
      "meaning": "snowscape"
    },
    {
      "question": "腐心",
      "answer": "ふしん",
      "meaning": "taking great pains (to do), making every effort, having a lot of trouble (doing), racking one's brai"
    },
    {
      "question": "二段目",
      "answer": "にだんめ",
      "meaning": "former name for makushita division"
    },
    {
      "question": "将軍家",
      "answer": "しょうぐんけ",
      "meaning": "family positioned to accede to the shogunate"
    },
    {
      "question": "爪牙",
      "answer": "そうが",
      "meaning": "claws and fangs, claws and tusks, clutches, devious design, means of causing harm, weapon, pawn, sto"
    },
    {
      "question": "通知表",
      "answer": "つうちひょう",
      "meaning": "report card"
    },
    {
      "question": "植生",
      "answer": "しょくせい",
      "meaning": "vegetation"
    },
    {
      "question": "競り合う",
      "answer": "せりあう",
      "meaning": "to struggle for, to compete with, to vie with"
    },
    {
      "question": "家探し",
      "answer": "やさがし,いえさがし",
      "meaning": "searching an entire house, house-hunting"
    },
    {
      "question": "譜",
      "answer": "ふ",
      "meaning": "(sheet) music, (musical) note, (musical) score, genealogy, family tree, record of a game of go, shog"
    },
    {
      "question": "山猫",
      "answer": "やまねこ",
      "meaning": "wildcat (European wildcat, Iriomote cat, Tsushima cat, etc.), wild cat, stray cat"
    },
    {
      "question": "巨匠",
      "answer": "きょしょう",
      "meaning": "master, masterhand, maestro"
    },
    {
      "question": "来期",
      "answer": "らいき",
      "meaning": "next term"
    },
    {
      "question": "押せ押せ",
      "answer": "おせおせ",
      "meaning": "putting on the pressure, pushing forward, being pressed, being under pressure"
    },
    {
      "question": "人伝",
      "answer": "ひとづて",
      "meaning": "hearsay"
    },
    {
      "question": "死傷",
      "answer": "ししょう",
      "meaning": "casualties, injuries and deaths"
    },
    {
      "question": "見開き",
      "answer": "みひらき",
      "meaning": "(two-page) spread, two pages opposite each other"
    },
    {
      "question": "仕事人間",
      "answer": "しごとにんげん",
      "meaning": "fiend for work, workaholic, career-minded person"
    },
    {
      "question": "新陳代謝",
      "answer": "しんちんたいしゃ",
      "meaning": "renewal, replacement, regeneration, rejuvenation, metabolism"
    },
    {
      "question": "蝦夷",
      "answer": "えぞ,えみし",
      "meaning": "Emishi, historical term for non-Yamato peoples in northern Japan, Yezo (northern part of Meiji-era J"
    },
    {
      "question": "小児科",
      "answer": "しょうにか",
      "meaning": "pediatrics"
    },
    {
      "question": "召し使い",
      "answer": "めしつかい",
      "meaning": "servant, menial"
    },
    {
      "question": "御存じ",
      "answer": "ごぞんじ",
      "meaning": "knowing, (an) acquaintance"
    },
    {
      "question": "赤道",
      "answer": "せきどう,あかみち,あかどう",
      "meaning": "equator, non-legal public road (denoted by a red line on cadastral maps; sometimes no longer physica"
    },
    {
      "question": "完走",
      "answer": "かんそう",
      "meaning": "finishing (a race), running the whole distance, reaching the goal, staying the course"
    },
    {
      "question": "上側",
      "answer": "うわかわ,うわがわ",
      "meaning": "upper side, surface"
    },
    {
      "question": "大局的",
      "answer": "たいきょくてき",
      "meaning": "broad (view, perspective, etc.), wide, large"
    },
    {
      "question": "先駆け",
      "answer": "さきがけ",
      "meaning": "pioneer, leader, taking the initiative, forerunner, harbinger, herald, leading an attack, charging a"
    },
    {
      "question": "使い回す",
      "answer": "つかいまわす",
      "meaning": "to use one thing for several purposes, to use the same thing on multiple occasions, to work someone"
    },
    {
      "question": "小百合",
      "answer": "さゆり",
      "meaning": "lily"
    },
    {
      "question": "巨軀",
      "answer": "きょく",
      "meaning": "big frame, large figure, huge body"
    },
    {
      "question": "烈しい",
      "answer": "はげしい",
      "meaning": "violent, furious, tempestuous, extreme, intense, fierce, strong, fervent, vehement, incessant, relen"
    },
    {
      "question": "神経衰弱",
      "answer": "しんけいすいじゃく",
      "meaning": "neurasthenia, nervous breakdown, concentration (card game involving turning over face-down cards to"
    },
    {
      "question": "現況",
      "answer": "げんきょう",
      "meaning": "present condition"
    },
    {
      "question": "年始",
      "answer": "ねんし",
      "meaning": "beginning of the year, new year, New Year's call, New Year's greetings"
    },
    {
      "question": "猿芝居",
      "answer": "さるしばい",
      "meaning": "monkey show, bad acting, overacting, unconvincing performance, farce, clumsy subterfuge"
    },
    {
      "question": "励起",
      "answer": "れいき",
      "meaning": "(electrical) excitation"
    },
    {
      "question": "胸骨",
      "answer": "きょうこつ",
      "meaning": "breastbone, sternum"
    },
    {
      "question": "私闘",
      "answer": "しとう",
      "meaning": "personal struggle"
    },
    {
      "question": "欠け",
      "answer": "かけ",
      "meaning": "fragment, splinter, wane (of the Moon)"
    },
    {
      "question": "盲腸",
      "answer": "もうちょう",
      "meaning": "cecum, caecum, blind gut, (vermiform) appendix, appendicitis"
    },
    {
      "question": "総指揮",
      "answer": "そうしき",
      "meaning": "supreme command, direction over all"
    },
    {
      "question": "年の瀬",
      "answer": "としのせ",
      "meaning": "the year end, end of the year, last days of the year"
    },
    {
      "question": "霊長類",
      "answer": "れいちょうるい",
      "meaning": "primates"
    },
    {
      "question": "剝ぎ取る",
      "answer": "はぎとる",
      "meaning": "to tear off, to strip, to rob"
    },
    {
      "question": "轢き殺す",
      "answer": "ひきころす",
      "meaning": "to kill by running over"
    },
    {
      "question": "一人芝居",
      "answer": "ひとりしばい",
      "meaning": "one-person show, one-woman show, one-man show, performing solo, monodrama"
    },
    {
      "question": "情操教育",
      "answer": "じょうそうきょういく",
      "meaning": "cultivation of aesthetic sensibility, education in good taste"
    },
    {
      "question": "牙城",
      "answer": "がじょう",
      "meaning": "stronghold (esp. of an enemy or opponent), inner citadel, bastion"
    },
    {
      "question": "徴",
      "answer": "ち,しるし,ちょう",
      "meaning": "fourth degree (of the Japanese and Chinese pentatonic scale), sign, indication, omen, symptom, call,"
    },
    {
      "question": "埋蔵金",
      "answer": "まいぞうきん",
      "meaning": "buried gold, buried treasure"
    },
    {
      "question": "罅が入る",
      "answer": "ひびがはいる",
      "meaning": "to get cracked, to develop a crack, to be fissured"
    },
    {
      "question": "郷土",
      "answer": "きょうど",
      "meaning": "native place, birth-place, one's old home, province, region, locality"
    },
    {
      "question": "径",
      "answer": "みち,けい,わたり",
      "meaning": "road, path, street, lane, passage, route, way, distance, journey, road (e.g. to victory), course, wa"
    },
    {
      "question": "花丸",
      "answer": "はなまる",
      "meaning": "encircled flower seal (equiv. of a gold star awarded to children for good work at school)"
    },
    {
      "question": "天丼",
      "answer": "てんどん",
      "meaning": "tempura served over a bowl of rice, (in comedy) repeating the same gag or silly line"
    },
    {
      "question": "筆致",
      "answer": "ひっち",
      "meaning": "stroke of the brush, touch, literary style"
    },
    {
      "question": "肉類",
      "answer": "にくるい",
      "meaning": "(kinds of) meat"
    },
    {
      "question": "駄目元",
      "answer": "だめもと",
      "meaning": "giving something a try because it will not do any harm"
    },
    {
      "question": "芸名",
      "answer": "げいめい",
      "meaning": "stage name"
    },
    {
      "question": "明細",
      "answer": "めいさい",
      "meaning": "details, particulars, specifics, detailed, minute, detailed statement"
    },
    {
      "question": "倦怠期",
      "answer": "けんたいき",
      "meaning": "stage of ennui (esp. in one's married life), period of lassitude, lethargic period, rut"
    },
    {
      "question": "一杯一杯",
      "answer": "いっぱいいっぱい",
      "meaning": "to the limit, to the fullest extent, absolutely the limit, the best one can do, breaking even, one c"
    },
    {
      "question": "首にする",
      "answer": "くびにする",
      "meaning": "to fire from a job"
    },
    {
      "question": "受け持ち",
      "answer": "うけもち",
      "meaning": "charge (of something), matter in one's charge, (one's) assignment, (one's) job"
    },
    {
      "question": "語弊",
      "answer": "ごへい",
      "meaning": "faulty statement, misleading statement, misunderstanding caused by a misleading statement"
    },
    {
      "question": "都庁",
      "answer": "とちょう",
      "meaning": "Tokyo Government Office"
    },
    {
      "question": "補給線",
      "answer": "ほきゅうせん",
      "meaning": "supply line"
    },
    {
      "question": "一遍",
      "answer": "いっぺん",
      "meaning": "once, one time, exclusively, only, alone"
    },
    {
      "question": "角張る",
      "answer": "かどばる,かくばる",
      "meaning": "to be angular, to jut out, to be pointed, to be sharp, to be jagged, to be rugged, to be formal, to"
    },
    {
      "question": "手酌",
      "answer": "てじゃく",
      "meaning": "helping oneself to a drink, pouring one's own drink"
    },
    {
      "question": "人集め",
      "answer": "ひとあつめ",
      "meaning": "throng, gathering of people"
    },
    {
      "question": "童謡",
      "answer": "どうよう",
      "meaning": "children's song, nursery rhyme"
    },
    {
      "question": "嬉し泣き",
      "answer": "うれしなき",
      "meaning": "weeping for joy, crying with happiness"
    },
    {
      "question": "大文字",
      "answer": "おおもじ,だいもんじ",
      "meaning": "uppercase letter, capital letter, large character, large writing, the (kanji) character 'dai' meanin"
    },
    {
      "question": "鉄鋼",
      "answer": "てっこう",
      "meaning": "iron and steel"
    },
    {
      "question": "台帳",
      "answer": "だいちょう",
      "meaning": "account book, ledger, register"
    },
    {
      "question": "実際的",
      "answer": "じっさいてき",
      "meaning": "practical, realistic, pragmatic"
    },
    {
      "question": "市街戦",
      "answer": "しがいせん",
      "meaning": "street fighting, urban warfare"
    },
    {
      "question": "先住民",
      "answer": "せんじゅうみん",
      "meaning": "indigenous people, native people, aborigines"
    },
    {
      "question": "似非",
      "answer": "えせ",
      "meaning": "false, pseudo-, quasi-, would-be, sham, pretended, mock"
    },
    {
      "question": "不興",
      "answer": "ふきょう",
      "meaning": "displeasure, ill humour, ill humor, pique"
    },
    {
      "question": "駿府",
      "answer": "",
      "meaning": ""
    },
    {
      "question": "氷像",
      "answer": "ひょうぞう",
      "meaning": "ice sculpture"
    },
    {
      "question": "印章",
      "answer": "いんしょう",
      "meaning": "stamp, seal"
    },
    {
      "question": "緑髪",
      "answer": "りょくはつ",
      "meaning": "glossy black hair, green hair"
    },
    {
      "question": "敷石",
      "answer": "しきいし",
      "meaning": "paving stone, pavement"
    },
    {
      "question": "作詞",
      "answer": "さくし",
      "meaning": "(writing) song lyrics"
    },
    {
      "question": "蹴倒す",
      "answer": "けたおす",
      "meaning": "to kick over, to kick down"
    },
    {
      "question": "可視",
      "answer": "かし",
      "meaning": "visibility"
    },
    {
      "question": "股関節",
      "answer": "こかんせつ",
      "meaning": "hip joint, coxa"
    },
    {
      "question": "激戦区",
      "answer": "げきせんく",
      "meaning": "closely contested constituency, highly competitive marketplace, battleground"
    },
    {
      "question": "光熱費",
      "answer": "こうねつひ",
      "meaning": "cost of fuel and lighting, cost of heat and electricity, energy bill, utility cost"
    },
    {
      "question": "絵馬",
      "answer": "えま,えうま",
      "meaning": "votive picture (originally of horse)"
    },
    {
      "question": "難破",
      "answer": "なんぱ",
      "meaning": "shipwreck"
    },
    {
      "question": "希う",
      "answer": "こいねがう",
      "meaning": "to beg, to request, to beseech, to implore, to entreat"
    },
    {
      "question": "凶兆",
      "answer": "きょうちょう",
      "meaning": "evil omen"
    },
    {
      "question": "奇矯",
      "answer": "ききょう",
      "meaning": "eccentric"
    },
    {
      "question": "異にする",
      "answer": "ことにする",
      "meaning": "to make a distinction, to differ, to be different"
    },
    {
      "question": "難局",
      "answer": "なんきょく",
      "meaning": "difficult situation"
    },
    {
      "question": "清貧",
      "answer": "せいひん",
      "meaning": "honourable poverty, honorable poverty"
    },
    {
      "question": "日銭",
      "answer": "ひぜに",
      "meaning": "daily income in cash, money paid by daily installments, money paid by daily instalments"
    },
    {
      "question": "一身上",
      "answer": "いっしんじょう",
      "meaning": "personal (affairs, reasons, etc.)"
    },
    {
      "question": "民主",
      "answer": "みんしゅ",
      "meaning": "democracy, popular sovereignty, Democratic Party (esp. DPJ)"
    },
    {
      "question": "古代語",
      "answer": "こだいご",
      "meaning": "ancient Japanese (as spoken in Japan until the Middle Ages)"
    },
    {
      "question": "朝霧",
      "answer": "あさぎり",
      "meaning": "morning fog, morning mist"
    },
    {
      "question": "小冊子",
      "answer": "しょうさっし",
      "meaning": "booklet, pamphlet"
    },
    {
      "question": "礼状",
      "answer": "れいじょう",
      "meaning": "acknowledgment, acknowledgement, letter of thanks"
    },
    {
      "question": "心霊現象",
      "answer": "しんれいげんしょう",
      "meaning": "psychic phenomenon"
    },
    {
      "question": "端役",
      "answer": "はやく",
      "meaning": "minor role, small part"
    },
    {
      "question": "畜産",
      "answer": "ちくさん",
      "meaning": "animal husbandry, livestock industry"
    },
    {
      "question": "因習",
      "answer": "いんしゅう",
      "meaning": "convention, tired tradition, old custom"
    },
    {
      "question": "酒池肉林",
      "answer": "しゅちにくりん",
      "meaning": "sumptuous feast, debauch"
    },
    {
      "question": "個人経営",
      "answer": "こじんけいえい",
      "meaning": "private management"
    },
    {
      "question": "下向く",
      "answer": "したむく",
      "meaning": "to point down, to look down, to get worse, to begin to fall (e.g. of a price)"
    },
    {
      "question": "御恩",
      "answer": "ごおん",
      "meaning": "(received) favor, kindness or blessing (favour)"
    },
    {
      "question": "蔑視",
      "answer": "べっし",
      "meaning": "contempt, derision, slight, disdain"
    },
    {
      "question": "福利厚生",
      "answer": "ふくりこうせい",
      "meaning": "employee welfare, employee benefits, fringe benefits"
    },
    {
      "question": "砂上",
      "answer": "さじょう",
      "meaning": "(built) on sand"
    },
    {
      "question": "冷風",
      "answer": "れいふう",
      "meaning": "cold wind, chilly breeze, (blast of) cold air"
    },
    {
      "question": "胆",
      "answer": "きも,たん",
      "meaning": "liver, innards, courage, spirit, pluck, guts, crux, essential point"
    },
    {
      "question": "画鋲",
      "answer": "がびょう",
      "meaning": "drawing pin, thumb tack"
    },
    {
      "question": "明示",
      "answer": "めいじ",
      "meaning": "elucidation, explicit statement, specification"
    },
    {
      "question": "主体性",
      "answer": "しゅたいせい",
      "meaning": "independence of will or action, self-direction, autonomy, initiative, identity"
    },
    {
      "question": "知る人",
      "answer": "しるひと",
      "meaning": "acquaintance, friend, lover"
    },
    {
      "question": "警視",
      "answer": "けいし",
      "meaning": "police superintendent"
    },
    {
      "question": "椎",
      "answer": "しい",
      "meaning": "any beech tree of genus Castanopsis, chinquapin, chinkapin"
    },
    {
      "question": "腸内",
      "answer": "ちょうない",
      "meaning": "intestinal, inside the intestines"
    },
    {
      "question": "鎧戸",
      "answer": "よろいど",
      "meaning": "slatted shutter, louver door (window)"
    },
    {
      "question": "縁組",
      "answer": "えんぐみ",
      "meaning": "betrothal, wedding, marriage into a family, matrimonial alliance, adoption"
    },
    {
      "question": "持ち時間",
      "answer": "もちじかん",
      "meaning": "amount of time one has"
    },
    {
      "question": "濫用",
      "answer": "らんよう",
      "meaning": "abuse, misuse, misappropriation, using to excess"
    },
    {
      "question": "方法論",
      "answer": "ほうほうろん",
      "meaning": "methodology"
    },
    {
      "question": "荒技",
      "answer": "あらわざ",
      "meaning": "drastic move (e.g. hold or strike in martial arts), power technique, display of power"
    },
    {
      "question": "手落ち",
      "answer": "ておち",
      "meaning": "oversight, omission"
    },
    {
      "question": "独立国",
      "answer": "どくりつこく",
      "meaning": "independent state, independent nation"
    },
    {
      "question": "分化",
      "answer": "ぶんか",
      "meaning": "specialization, specialisation, differentiation"
    },
    {
      "question": "出待ち",
      "answer": "でまち",
      "meaning": "waiting (e.g. at the stage door) for performers or celebrities to exit"
    },
    {
      "question": "色眼鏡",
      "answer": "いろめがね",
      "meaning": "coloured glasses, tinted glasses, sunglasses, biased view, preconceived view"
    },
    {
      "question": "真向かい",
      "answer": "まむかい",
      "meaning": "right opposite, directly across, just in front of, face to face"
    },
    {
      "question": "無臭",
      "answer": "むしゅう",
      "meaning": "odorless, odourless, unscented"
    },
    {
      "question": "二段構え",
      "answer": "にだんがまえ",
      "meaning": "keeping an alternative up one's sleeve, two-stage preparation"
    },
    {
      "question": "不摂生",
      "answer": "ふせっせい",
      "meaning": "neglect of one's health, unhealthy living, intemperance"
    },
    {
      "question": "盆栽",
      "answer": "ぼんさい",
      "meaning": "bonsai, miniature potted plant"
    },
    {
      "question": "遍く",
      "answer": "あまねく",
      "meaning": "widely, extensively, far and wide, everywhere, all around, generally, universally"
    },
    {
      "question": "中略",
      "answer": "ちゅうりゃく",
      "meaning": "omission (of middle part of a text), ellipsis"
    },
    {
      "question": "幽体離脱",
      "answer": "ゆうたいりだつ",
      "meaning": "out-of-body experience"
    },
    {
      "question": "磨耗",
      "answer": "まもう",
      "meaning": "wear, abrasion"
    },
    {
      "question": "淫行",
      "answer": "いんこう",
      "meaning": "obscenity, harlotry"
    },
    {
      "question": "海草",
      "answer": "かいそう,うみくさ,うみぐさ",
      "meaning": "marine plant, seagrass, seaweed"
    },
    {
      "question": "温水",
      "answer": "おんすい",
      "meaning": "warm water"
    },
    {
      "question": "煉瓦造り",
      "answer": "れんがづくり",
      "meaning": "brickwork"
    },
    {
      "question": "座右の銘",
      "answer": "ざゆうのめい",
      "meaning": "favourite motto, pet saying"
    },
    {
      "question": "冷え性",
      "answer": "ひえしょう",
      "meaning": "sensitivity to cold"
    },
    {
      "question": "宗教画",
      "answer": "しゅうきょうが",
      "meaning": "religious painting, religious picture"
    },
    {
      "question": "重ね着",
      "answer": "かさねぎ",
      "meaning": "layering (clothing), wearing one garment over another"
    },
    {
      "question": "黙",
      "answer": "しじま",
      "meaning": "silence, stillness, quietness"
    },
    {
      "question": "荒削り",
      "answer": "あらけずり",
      "meaning": "rough-hewn, incomplete, unrefined, still in the process of being formed"
    },
    {
      "question": "妻帯者",
      "answer": "さいたいしゃ",
      "meaning": "married man"
    },
    {
      "question": "泳ぎ回る",
      "answer": "およぎまわる",
      "meaning": "to swim around"
    },
    {
      "question": "上田",
      "answer": "じょうでん",
      "meaning": "high rice field, very fertile rice field"
    },
    {
      "question": "天帝",
      "answer": "てんてい",
      "meaning": "Shangdi, supreme deity in ancient Chinese religion, God (in Christianity), Shakra, Indra, king of he"
    },
    {
      "question": "火酒",
      "answer": "かしゅ",
      "meaning": "strong drink"
    },
    {
      "question": "迷彩服",
      "answer": "めいさいふく",
      "meaning": "camouflaged clothes"
    },
    {
      "question": "差分",
      "answer": "さぶん",
      "meaning": "incremental difference (e.g. between files), 'diff', difference, subtraction, (finite) differences"
    },
    {
      "question": "垂",
      "answer": "しで",
      "meaning": "zigzag-shaped paper streamer often used to adorn Shinto-related objects, hornbeam (deciduous tree in"
    },
    {
      "question": "累積",
      "answer": "るいせき",
      "meaning": "accumulation"
    },
    {
      "question": "筋骨",
      "answer": "きんこつ,すじぼね",
      "meaning": "muscles and bones, body build, physique, cartilage"
    },
    {
      "question": "刃傷沙汰",
      "answer": "にんじょうざた",
      "meaning": "bloodshed"
    },
    {
      "question": "痩せ我慢",
      "answer": "やせがまん",
      "meaning": "enduring something out of pride, putting up with it, grinning and bearing it"
    },
    {
      "question": "首回り",
      "answer": "くびまわり",
      "meaning": "around the neck, neck size (measurement)"
    },
    {
      "question": "立つ瀬",
      "answer": "たつせ",
      "meaning": "predicament, one's ground, one's position"
    },
    {
      "question": "赤銅",
      "answer": "しゃくどう",
      "meaning": "shakudo, gold-copper alloy, often with a blue patina"
    },
    {
      "question": "激発",
      "answer": "げきはつ",
      "meaning": "fit, spasm, outburst"
    },
    {
      "question": "二八",
      "answer": "にはち,にっぱち",
      "meaning": "sixteen, February and August (times of slow business, sluggish sales, etc.)"
    },
    {
      "question": "義兄弟",
      "answer": "ぎきょうだい",
      "meaning": "brother-in-law, stepbrother, sworn brother"
    },
    {
      "question": "除隊",
      "answer": "じょたい",
      "meaning": "military discharge"
    },
    {
      "question": "約束の地",
      "answer": "やくそくのち",
      "meaning": "Promised Land"
    },
    {
      "question": "申し送る",
      "answer": "もうしおくる",
      "meaning": "to write to, to send word to, to hand over (official business)"
    },
    {
      "question": "横滑り",
      "answer": "よこすべり",
      "meaning": "sideslip, skid, sliding sideways, shifting to another post (at the same level), sideways move (at a"
    },
    {
      "question": "獄中",
      "answer": "ごくちゅう",
      "meaning": "during imprisonment, while in jail"
    },
    {
      "question": "寝物語",
      "answer": "ねものがたり",
      "meaning": "pillow talk, conversation in bed, bedtime story"
    },
    {
      "question": "推参",
      "answer": "すいさん",
      "meaning": "paying an unannounced visit, rudeness"
    },
    {
      "question": "振り込み",
      "answer": "ふりこみ",
      "meaning": "payment made via bank deposit transfer, discarding a tile that becomes another player's winning tile"
    },
    {
      "question": "正味",
      "answer": "しょうみ",
      "meaning": "net weight, useful part, actual content, real, effective, full"
    },
    {
      "question": "老成",
      "answer": "ろうせい",
      "meaning": "mature, becoming precocious"
    },
    {
      "question": "仕損じる",
      "answer": "しそんじる",
      "meaning": "to blunder, to fail, to make a mistake"
    },
    {
      "question": "頸椎",
      "answer": "けいつい",
      "meaning": "cervical vertebrae"
    },
    {
      "question": "蝶よ花よ",
      "answer": "ちょうよはなよ",
      "meaning": "bringing up (one's daughter) like a princess"
    },
    {
      "question": "俺等",
      "answer": "おれら,おいら",
      "meaning": "we, us, I, me"
    },
    {
      "question": "使節",
      "answer": "しせつ",
      "meaning": "envoy, ambassador, delegate, emissary, mission"
    },
    {
      "question": "夏空",
      "answer": "なつぞら",
      "meaning": "summer sky, summery weather, clear, blazing summer weather"
    },
    {
      "question": "以ての外",
      "answer": "もってのほか",
      "meaning": "absurd, unreasonable"
    },
    {
      "question": "防ぎ",
      "answer": "ふせぎ",
      "meaning": "defense, defence, protecting, preventing"
    },
    {
      "question": "明朗",
      "answer": "めいろう",
      "meaning": "cheerful, bright, clear, clean, honest, fair"
    },
    {
      "question": "新羅",
      "answer": "しらぎ,しんら",
      "meaning": "Silla, ancient Korean kingdom (57 BCE-935 CE)"
    },
    {
      "question": "無機的",
      "answer": "むきてき",
      "meaning": "inorganic"
    },
    {
      "question": "葱",
      "answer": "ねぎ,き",
      "meaning": "Welsh onion (Allium fistulosum), green onion, spring onion"
    },
    {
      "question": "安値",
      "answer": "やすね",
      "meaning": "low price"
    },
    {
      "question": "底部",
      "answer": "ていぶ",
      "meaning": "base, bottom"
    },
    {
      "question": "巨悪",
      "answer": "きょあく",
      "meaning": "great evil, scum of the earth, monster, fiend"
    },
    {
      "question": "驚天動地",
      "answer": "きょうてんどうち",
      "meaning": "astounding, startling, world-shaking, amazing, earth-shattering"
    },
    {
      "question": "塾長",
      "answer": "じゅくちょう",
      "meaning": "principal of a private school"
    },
    {
      "question": "航海士",
      "answer": "こうかいし",
      "meaning": "mate, navigation officer"
    },
    {
      "question": "拳闘",
      "answer": "けんとう",
      "meaning": "boxing"
    },
    {
      "question": "懸賞",
      "answer": "けんしょう",
      "meaning": "offering a prize, prize competition, prize, reward"
    },
    {
      "question": "寓話",
      "answer": "ぐうわ",
      "meaning": "fable, allegory"
    },
    {
      "question": "余年",
      "answer": "よねん",
      "meaning": "one's remaining years"
    },
    {
      "question": "拘わる",
      "answer": "こだわる,かかわる",
      "meaning": "to fuss over, to be particular about, to be obsessive about, to be fixated on, to obstruct, to hinde"
    },
    {
      "question": "造反",
      "answer": "ぞうはん",
      "meaning": "rebellion"
    },
    {
      "question": "為にする",
      "answer": "ためにする",
      "meaning": "to have an ulterior motive, to have an axe to grind"
    },
    {
      "question": "手前勝手",
      "answer": "てまえがって",
      "meaning": "self-centered, self-centred, selfish"
    },
    {
      "question": "厚化粧",
      "answer": "あつげしょう",
      "meaning": "thick makeup, heavy makeup"
    },
    {
      "question": "妙技",
      "answer": "みょうぎ",
      "meaning": "exquisite skill, wonderful performance"
    },
    {
      "question": "大味",
      "answer": "おおあじ",
      "meaning": "flat-tasting, bland, lacking in flavor, dull, flat, unimaginative, boring"
    },
    {
      "question": "相手次第",
      "answer": "あいてしだい",
      "meaning": "changing one's attitude or response according who one is talking to or dealing with"
    },
    {
      "question": "幻像",
      "answer": "げんぞう",
      "meaning": "phantom, vision, illusion"
    },
    {
      "question": "工廠",
      "answer": "こうしょう",
      "meaning": "arsenal, arms and ammunition factory"
    },
    {
      "question": "巧",
      "answer": "こう",
      "meaning": "skilfulness, skillfulness, cleverness"
    },
    {
      "question": "西瓜",
      "answer": "すいか",
      "meaning": "watermelon (Citrullus lanatus)"
    },
    {
      "question": "鼻毛",
      "answer": "はなげ",
      "meaning": "nostril hairs, being infatuated with women, fool"
    },
    {
      "question": "優先権",
      "answer": "ゆうせんけん",
      "meaning": "priority, preference, preferential right, right of way"
    },
    {
      "question": "連帯",
      "answer": "れんたい",
      "meaning": "solidarity, joint, collective"
    },
    {
      "question": "曲がり",
      "answer": "まがり",
      "meaning": "curvature, warp, bend"
    },
    {
      "question": "幼心",
      "answer": "おさなごころ",
      "meaning": "child's mind, child's heart, young mind"
    },
    {
      "question": "対艦",
      "answer": "たいかん",
      "meaning": "anti-ship, anti-warship, anti-surface"
    },
    {
      "question": "手仕事",
      "answer": "てしごと",
      "meaning": "handwork, handcraft, manual labor, manual labour, working with one's hands"
    },
    {
      "question": "重機関銃",
      "answer": "じゅうきかんじゅう",
      "meaning": "heavy machine gun"
    },
    {
      "question": "玉手箱",
      "answer": "たまてばこ",
      "meaning": "Urashima's casket (in the story of Urashima Tarō), Pandora's box, one's closely guarded treasure"
    },
    {
      "question": "試供品",
      "answer": "しきょうひん",
      "meaning": "(free) sample, promotional gift"
    },
    {
      "question": "若木",
      "answer": "わかぎ",
      "meaning": "young tree, sapling"
    },
    {
      "question": "内圧",
      "answer": "ないあつ",
      "meaning": "internal pressure"
    },
    {
      "question": "嫌気",
      "answer": "いやき,いやけ,けんき",
      "meaning": "dislike, disgust, disinclination, tired of"
    },
    {
      "question": "主眼",
      "answer": "しゅがん",
      "meaning": "main purpose, chief aim, focus, main point, gist, essence"
    },
    {
      "question": "得意顔",
      "answer": "とくいがお",
      "meaning": "triumphant look"
    },
    {
      "question": "最後通告",
      "answer": "さいごつうこく",
      "meaning": "final warning, ultimatum, last notice"
    },
    {
      "question": "十六夜",
      "answer": "いざよい",
      "meaning": "sixteen-day-old moon"
    },
    {
      "question": "一花",
      "answer": "ひとはな",
      "meaning": "one flower, single flower, success, prosperity"
    },
    {
      "question": "黒影",
      "answer": "こくえい",
      "meaning": "silhouette, dark shadow"
    },
    {
      "question": "当て身",
      "answer": "あてみ",
      "meaning": "blow to a vital point of a person's body, striking techniques (judo)"
    },
    {
      "question": "猜疑",
      "answer": "さいぎ",
      "meaning": "suspicion, jealousy"
    },
    {
      "question": "波瀾万丈",
      "answer": "はらんばんじょう",
      "meaning": "stormy and full of drama, many drastic events in the course of events, full of ups and downs, with m"
    },
    {
      "question": "平々凡々",
      "answer": "へいへいぼんぼん",
      "meaning": "very ordinary, mediocre, all-too-common, quite commonplace"
    },
    {
      "question": "工芸",
      "answer": "こうげい",
      "meaning": "industrial arts, craft"
    },
    {
      "question": "開城",
      "answer": "かいじょう,ケソン",
      "meaning": "capitulation (of fort), Kaesong (North Korea)"
    },
    {
      "question": "拿捕",
      "answer": "だほ",
      "meaning": "capture, seizure, military capture of a foreign vessel, making a prize of"
    },
    {
      "question": "苛め",
      "answer": "いじめ",
      "meaning": "bullying, teasing"
    },
    {
      "question": "有毒",
      "answer": "ゆうどく",
      "meaning": "poisonous, toxic"
    },
    {
      "question": "出欠",
      "answer": "しゅっけつ",
      "meaning": "attendance or absence"
    },
    {
      "question": "上策",
      "answer": "じょうさく",
      "meaning": "excellent plan, best policy"
    },
    {
      "question": "母国語",
      "answer": "ぼこくご",
      "meaning": "language of one's country, mother tongue, native language"
    },
    {
      "question": "惚気話",
      "answer": "のろけばなし",
      "meaning": "boastful talk about one's love life, speaking fondly about one's sweetheart, going on about one's lo"
    },
    {
      "question": "袖の下",
      "answer": "そでのした",
      "meaning": "bribe, money under the table"
    },
    {
      "question": "乙姫",
      "answer": "おとひめ",
      "meaning": "younger princess, Oto Hime, Princess of the Dragon Palace (from the story of Urashima Tarō)"
    },
    {
      "question": "炸薬",
      "answer": "さくやく",
      "meaning": "explosives"
    },
    {
      "question": "支流",
      "answer": "しりゅう",
      "meaning": "tributary, branch"
    },
    {
      "question": "護法",
      "answer": "ごほう",
      "meaning": "defence of Buddhist doctrines, god who defends Buddhist doctrines, defence of the constitution, reli"
    },
    {
      "question": "獅子王",
      "answer": "ししおう",
      "meaning": "lion (king of beasts)"
    },
    {
      "question": "助教授",
      "answer": "じょきょうじゅ",
      "meaning": "assistant professor, associate professor"
    },
    {
      "question": "虚数",
      "answer": "きょすう",
      "meaning": "imaginary number"
    },
    {
      "question": "御前会議",
      "answer": "ごぜんかいぎ",
      "meaning": "Imperial Council"
    },
    {
      "question": "仕種",
      "answer": "しぐさ",
      "meaning": "gesture, movement, action, behavior, behaviour, bearing, mannerism, acting, performance"
    },
    {
      "question": "甚振る",
      "answer": "いたぶる",
      "meaning": "to torment, to harass, to tease"
    },
    {
      "question": "醬油",
      "answer": "しょうゆ,しょうゆう",
      "meaning": "soy sauce, shoyu"
    },
    {
      "question": "地縛霊",
      "answer": "じばくれい",
      "meaning": "ghost bound to a specific physical location (usu. where death occurred)"
    },
    {
      "question": "夜毎",
      "answer": "よごと",
      "meaning": "every night, nightly"
    },
    {
      "question": "道具箱",
      "answer": "どうぐばこ",
      "meaning": "toolbox"
    },
    {
      "question": "俳句",
      "answer": "はいく",
      "meaning": "haiku, 17-mora poem, usu. in 3 lines of 5, 7 and 5 morae"
    },
    {
      "question": "密入国",
      "answer": "みつにゅうこく,みつにゅうごく",
      "meaning": "smuggling oneself into a country, illegal immigration"
    },
    {
      "question": "先取",
      "answer": "せんしゅ,さきどり",
      "meaning": "earning the first (runs), preoccupation, receiving in advance, taking before others, prefetch, antic"
    },
    {
      "question": "寸胴",
      "answer": "ずんどう,ずんど",
      "meaning": "cylindrical container (pot, vase, etc.), having no waist (straight body figure, not curvy), being st"
    },
    {
      "question": "腰だめ",
      "answer": "こしだめ",
      "meaning": "shooting from the hip, starting something without sufficient preparation, acting on a vague estimate"
    },
    {
      "question": "二つ折り",
      "answer": "ふたつおり",
      "meaning": "folded in half, doubled"
    },
    {
      "question": "同年",
      "answer": "どうねん",
      "meaning": "that year, same year, same age"
    },
    {
      "question": "監察",
      "answer": "かんさつ",
      "meaning": "inspection, inspector"
    },
    {
      "question": "間男",
      "answer": "まおとこ",
      "meaning": "married woman's secret lover, paramour, adultery (by a married woman)"
    },
    {
      "question": "既定",
      "answer": "きてい",
      "meaning": "established, fixed, prearranged, predetermined"
    },
    {
      "question": "下座",
      "answer": "げざ,しもざ",
      "meaning": "coming down from one's seat and prostrating oneself (to pay obeisance), musicians' box on the left s"
    },
    {
      "question": "低能",
      "answer": "ていのう",
      "meaning": "low intelligence, feeble-mindedness, imbecility"
    },
    {
      "question": "納税",
      "answer": "のうぜい",
      "meaning": "payment of taxes"
    },
    {
      "question": "夏風邪",
      "answer": "なつかぜ",
      "meaning": "summer cold (illness), summer flu"
    },
    {
      "question": "秋風",
      "answer": "あきかぜ,しゅうふう",
      "meaning": "autumn breeze, fall breeze"
    },
    {
      "question": "組員",
      "answer": "くみいん",
      "meaning": "member (esp. of a criminal organization), gang member, gangster, yakuza, crime syndicate member"
    },
    {
      "question": "人足",
      "answer": "にんそく,ひとあし",
      "meaning": "coolie, laborer, labourer, carrier, pedestrian traffic, kanji 'legs radical' (radical 10)"
    },
    {
      "question": "同門",
      "answer": "どうもん",
      "meaning": "fellow student"
    },
    {
      "question": "土中",
      "answer": "どちゅう",
      "meaning": "in the earth, in the ground, underground"
    },
    {
      "question": "読経",
      "answer": "どきょう,どっきょう",
      "meaning": "sutra chanting"
    },
    {
      "question": "留置場",
      "answer": "りゅうちじょう",
      "meaning": "police cell, place of detention, jail"
    },
    {
      "question": "裏声",
      "answer": "うらごえ",
      "meaning": "falsetto"
    },
    {
      "question": "液状化",
      "answer": "えきじょうか",
      "meaning": "liquefaction, liquefy"
    },
    {
      "question": "幾年",
      "answer": "いくねん,いくとせ",
      "meaning": "number of years"
    },
    {
      "question": "骨休め",
      "answer": "ほねやすめ",
      "meaning": "relaxation, recreation, recess"
    },
    {
      "question": "秀逸",
      "answer": "しゅういつ",
      "meaning": "excellent, superb, first-rate"
    },
    {
      "question": "親離れ",
      "answer": "おやばなれ",
      "meaning": "independence from parents"
    },
    {
      "question": "話の種",
      "answer": "はなしのたね",
      "meaning": "topic of conversation"
    },
    {
      "question": "荒立てる",
      "answer": "あらだてる",
      "meaning": "to aggravate, to make serious"
    },
    {
      "question": "雀の涙",
      "answer": "すずめのなみだ",
      "meaning": "drop in the bucket, very small quantity, chicken feed, insignificant amount, sparrow tears"
    },
    {
      "question": "謡",
      "answer": "うたい",
      "meaning": "noh chanting, recitation"
    },
    {
      "question": "署内",
      "answer": "しょない",
      "meaning": "inside a police station, fire station, tax office etc."
    },
    {
      "question": "公衆浴場",
      "answer": "こうしゅうよくじょう",
      "meaning": "public bathhouse"
    },
    {
      "question": "火打ち石",
      "answer": "ひうちいし",
      "meaning": "flint"
    },
    {
      "question": "許諾",
      "answer": "きょだく",
      "meaning": "consent"
    },
    {
      "question": "手巾",
      "answer": "しゅきん",
      "meaning": "(hand) towel, handkerchief"
    },
    {
      "question": "中味",
      "answer": "なかみ",
      "meaning": "contents, interior, substance, filling, (sword) blade"
    },
    {
      "question": "錫",
      "answer": "すず,しゃく",
      "meaning": "tin (Sn), bishop's staff, khakkhara"
    },
    {
      "question": "坪",
      "answer": "つぼ",
      "meaning": "tsubo, traditional unit of land area, approx. 3.31 square meters, traditional unit of fabric or pape"
    },
    {
      "question": "赤茶",
      "answer": "あかちゃ",
      "meaning": "reddish brown"
    },
    {
      "question": "銅鑼",
      "answer": "どら,どうら",
      "meaning": "gong, tam-tam"
    },
    {
      "question": "乱交",
      "answer": "らんこう",
      "meaning": "promiscuity, group sex"
    },
    {
      "question": "柔術",
      "answer": "じゅうじゅつ",
      "meaning": "jujitsu (classical Japanese martial art, usually referring to fighting without a weapon), jiujitsu,"
    },
    {
      "question": "柄杓",
      "answer": "ひしゃく,ひさく",
      "meaning": "ladle, dipper, scoop"
    },
    {
      "question": "血液検査",
      "answer": "けつえきけんさ",
      "meaning": "blood test, hemanalysis"
    },
    {
      "question": "術後",
      "answer": "じゅつご",
      "meaning": "postoperative, after surgery"
    },
    {
      "question": "嵩張る",
      "answer": "かさばる",
      "meaning": "to be bulky, to be unwieldy, to grow voluminous"
    },
    {
      "question": "粟",
      "answer": "あわ,ぞく",
      "meaning": "foxtail millet (Setaria italica), Italian millet (also Hungarian, German), millet, grain, stipend in"
    },
    {
      "question": "道場破り",
      "answer": "どうじょうやぶり",
      "meaning": "visiting another school (e.g. of kendo) and defeating each member in a fight"
    },
    {
      "question": "碧色",
      "answer": "へきしょく",
      "meaning": "green, emerald"
    },
    {
      "question": "温風",
      "answer": "おんぷう",
      "meaning": "warm air (e.g. from a heater), spring breeze"
    },
    {
      "question": "砂鉄",
      "answer": "さてつ",
      "meaning": "iron sand, magnetite sand"
    },
    {
      "question": "完熟",
      "answer": "かんじゅく",
      "meaning": "full ripeness, full maturity"
    },
    {
      "question": "侮り",
      "answer": "あなどり",
      "meaning": "contempt, scorn"
    },
    {
      "question": "労苦",
      "answer": "ろうく",
      "meaning": "labor, labour, toil, hardship"
    },
    {
      "question": "猶予期間",
      "answer": "ゆうよきかん",
      "meaning": "grace period, moratorium"
    },
    {
      "question": "順守",
      "answer": "じゅんしゅ",
      "meaning": "observance (of laws, rules, etc.), adherence, obeying, following, abiding by, compliance"
    },
    {
      "question": "現代っ子",
      "answer": "げんだいっこ",
      "meaning": "child of the times, modern kid, kids of today, with-it youngster"
    },
    {
      "question": "日本的",
      "answer": "にほんてき",
      "meaning": "(typically) Japanese"
    },
    {
      "question": "上げ下げ",
      "answer": "あげさげ",
      "meaning": "raising and lowering, praising and blaming, modulation"
    },
    {
      "question": "御嬢様",
      "answer": "おじょうさま",
      "meaning": "(another's) daughter, young lady (of pampered upbringing), woman who has never known hardship, naive"
    },
    {
      "question": "茶室",
      "answer": "ちゃしつ",
      "meaning": "tearoom, tea house, tea-ceremony room, tea arbour, tea arbor"
    },
    {
      "question": "キャバ嬢",
      "answer": "キャバじょう",
      "meaning": "hostess (in a hostess bar)"
    },
    {
      "question": "公用語",
      "answer": "こうようご",
      "meaning": "official language"
    },
    {
      "question": "形質",
      "answer": "けいしつ",
      "meaning": "form and nature"
    },
    {
      "question": "唐竹",
      "answer": "とうちく,からたけ",
      "meaning": "Chinese temple bamboo (Sinobambusa tootsik), tootsik bamboo, Chinese bamboo, bamboo imported from Ch"
    },
    {
      "question": "火勢",
      "answer": "かせい",
      "meaning": "force of a fire, force of flames"
    },
    {
      "question": "一夫多妻",
      "answer": "いっぷたさい",
      "meaning": "polygamy, polygyny"
    },
    {
      "question": "苦闘",
      "answer": "くとう",
      "meaning": "hard fight, difficult struggle"
    },
    {
      "question": "愚物",
      "answer": "ぐぶつ",
      "meaning": "fool"
    },
    {
      "question": "直観",
      "answer": "ちょっかん",
      "meaning": "intuition, instinct, insight, hunch, immediacy"
    },
    {
      "question": "滞留",
      "answer": "たいりゅう",
      "meaning": "stagnation, standstill, accumulation, pile-up, stay, sojourn"
    },
    {
      "question": "風光明媚",
      "answer": "ふうこうめいび",
      "meaning": "scenic, beautiful, picturesque"
    },
    {
      "question": "着古す",
      "answer": "きふるす,きぶるす",
      "meaning": "to wear out (clothing)"
    },
    {
      "question": "占術",
      "answer": "せんじゅつ",
      "meaning": "divination, fortune-telling, mantic"
    },
    {
      "question": "圧し潰す",
      "answer": "おしつぶす",
      "meaning": "to squash, to crush, to flatten"
    },
    {
      "question": "東端",
      "answer": "とうたん",
      "meaning": "east end, eastern tip"
    },
    {
      "question": "定理",
      "answer": "ていり",
      "meaning": "theorem, proposition"
    },
    {
      "question": "建て直し",
      "answer": "たてなおし",
      "meaning": "re-erection, rebuilding"
    },
    {
      "question": "偉いさん",
      "answer": "えらいさん",
      "meaning": "big shot, higher-ups"
    },
    {
      "question": "骨になる",
      "answer": "ほねになる",
      "meaning": "to die, to become bones"
    },
    {
      "question": "正教",
      "answer": "せいきょう",
      "meaning": "orthodoxy, (Greek) orthodox church"
    },
    {
      "question": "竜宮",
      "answer": "りゅうぐう",
      "meaning": "Palace of the Dragon King, palace from the story of Urashima Tarō (said to be located at the bottom"
    },
    {
      "question": "伴",
      "answer": "とも",
      "meaning": "companion, follower, attendant, retinue"
    },
    {
      "question": "爆殺",
      "answer": "ばくさつ",
      "meaning": "killing with a bomb, killing in a bombing"
    },
    {
      "question": "山狩り",
      "answer": "やまがり",
      "meaning": "a mountain hunt"
    },
    {
      "question": "刷毛",
      "answer": "はけ",
      "meaning": "brush (e.g. for painting, basting, etc.), whisk"
    },
    {
      "question": "後年",
      "answer": "こうねん",
      "meaning": "future years, in (one's) later years"
    },
    {
      "question": "遭遇戦",
      "answer": "そうぐうせん",
      "meaning": "encounter, engagement, battle"
    },
    {
      "question": "競馬場",
      "answer": "けいばじょう",
      "meaning": "racecourse, race track"
    },
    {
      "question": "遺言状",
      "answer": "ゆいごんじょう",
      "meaning": "will, testament"
    },
    {
      "question": "寄進",
      "answer": "きしん",
      "meaning": "contribution (to a temple, shrine, etc.), donation"
    },
    {
      "question": "酒蔵",
      "answer": "さかぐら",
      "meaning": "sake brewery, wine cellar, bar, bar-room"
    },
    {
      "question": "西洋人",
      "answer": "せいようじん",
      "meaning": "Western people"
    },
    {
      "question": "揉み解す",
      "answer": "もみほぐす",
      "meaning": "to massage"
    },
    {
      "question": "北米",
      "answer": "ほくべい",
      "meaning": "North America"
    },
    {
      "question": "某日",
      "answer": "ぼうじつ",
      "meaning": "certain day"
    },
    {
      "question": "寄り合い",
      "answer": "よりあい",
      "meaning": "meeting, gathering, village assembly, two wrestlers approaching each other"
    },
    {
      "question": "台風の目",
      "answer": "たいふうのめ",
      "meaning": "eye of a typhoon"
    },
    {
      "question": "縮尺",
      "answer": "しゅくしゃく",
      "meaning": "reduced scale, scaling down"
    },
    {
      "question": "主家",
      "answer": "しゅか,しゅけ,おもや",
      "meaning": "employer's house, master's house, main building (of a manor), central room (of a house)"
    },
    {
      "question": "燻す",
      "answer": "いぶす",
      "meaning": "to smoke (something), to fumigate, to oxidize, to oxidise"
    },
    {
      "question": "膝小僧",
      "answer": "ひざこぞう",
      "meaning": "kneecap"
    },
    {
      "question": "標榜",
      "answer": "ひょうぼう",
      "meaning": "standing for, advocating, championing, professing (to be)"
    },
    {
      "question": "凋落",
      "answer": "ちょうらく",
      "meaning": "decline, fall, decay, withering"
    },
    {
      "question": "寄せ",
      "answer": "よせ",
      "meaning": "last moves (in go, shogi, or chess), endgame, gathering, collecting, coming together"
    },
    {
      "question": "家財道具",
      "answer": "かざいどうぐ",
      "meaning": "household belongings, household possession, furniture and household goods, goods and chattels, home"
    },
    {
      "question": "聖火",
      "answer": "せいか",
      "meaning": "sacred fire (torch), Olympic flame"
    },
    {
      "question": "物の怪",
      "answer": "もののけ",
      "meaning": "(vengeful) ghost, specter, spectre"
    },
    {
      "question": "散華",
      "answer": "さんげ",
      "meaning": "rite of scattering flowers, glorious death (in battle), heroic death"
    },
    {
      "question": "土星",
      "answer": "どせい",
      "meaning": "Saturn (planet)"
    },
    {
      "question": "融かす",
      "answer": "とかす",
      "meaning": "to dissolve, to melt"
    },
    {
      "question": "投げ技",
      "answer": "なげわざ",
      "meaning": "throw or throwing technique (sumo, judo)"
    },
    {
      "question": "斬殺",
      "answer": "ざんさつ",
      "meaning": "putting to the sword"
    },
    {
      "question": "解像度",
      "answer": "かいぞうど",
      "meaning": "resolution (of a display, printer, scanner, etc.)"
    },
    {
      "question": "滑落",
      "answer": "かつらく",
      "meaning": "slipping down, avalanche"
    },
    {
      "question": "新体制",
      "answer": "しんたいせい",
      "meaning": "new order, new system"
    },
    {
      "question": "匍匐前進",
      "answer": "ほふくぜんしん",
      "meaning": "crawling along"
    },
    {
      "question": "機巧",
      "answer": "きこう",
      "meaning": "trick, contrivance, cleverness"
    },
    {
      "question": "睦月",
      "answer": "むつき",
      "meaning": "first month of the lunar calendar, January"
    },
    {
      "question": "明鏡止水",
      "answer": "めいきょうしすい",
      "meaning": "clear and serene (as a polished mirror and still water)"
    },
    {
      "question": "鈍",
      "answer": "どん,のろ,なまくら",
      "meaning": "dull, slow, stupid, dull-brained, blunt (e.g. sword), lazy, cowardly, good for nothing"
    },
    {
      "question": "臼",
      "answer": "うす",
      "meaning": "millstone, mortar"
    },
    {
      "question": "圧搾",
      "answer": "あっさく",
      "meaning": "pressure, compression"
    },
    {
      "question": "慚愧",
      "answer": "ざんき,ざんぎ",
      "meaning": "(feeling of) shame"
    },
    {
      "question": "身投げ",
      "answer": "みなげ",
      "meaning": "throwing oneself (e.g. into the water to commit suicide)"
    },
    {
      "question": "拝する",
      "answer": "はいする",
      "meaning": "to bow, to worship, to receive, to see"
    },
    {
      "question": "板状",
      "answer": "ばんじょう",
      "meaning": "board, plank or sheet shaped"
    },
    {
      "question": "無風",
      "answer": "むふう",
      "meaning": "windless, calm, quiet (state of affairs), peaceful, stable, safe (electoral seat)"
    },
    {
      "question": "書体",
      "answer": "しょたい",
      "meaning": "typeface, style of handwriting, calligraphic style"
    },
    {
      "question": "雨天",
      "answer": "うてん",
      "meaning": "rainy weather"
    },
    {
      "question": "社名",
      "answer": "しゃめい",
      "meaning": "company name, name of a company"
    },
    {
      "question": "全敗",
      "answer": "ぜんぱい",
      "meaning": "complete defeat, losing all of one's matches, finishing the tournament with no wins"
    },
    {
      "question": "楽師",
      "answer": "がくし",
      "meaning": "master musician"
    },
    {
      "question": "茨城",
      "answer": "いばらき,いばらぎ",
      "meaning": "Ibaraki (prefecture)"
    },
    {
      "question": "固唾",
      "answer": "かたず,かたづ",
      "meaning": "saliva held in one's mouth during times of tension"
    },
    {
      "question": "仁王",
      "answer": "におう",
      "meaning": "two Deva kings, guardian gods of Buddhism who stand at the entrance of a Buddhist temple"
    },
    {
      "question": "乞食",
      "answer": "こじき,こつじき,ほいと",
      "meaning": "beggar, begging"
    },
    {
      "question": "町工場",
      "answer": "まちこうば,まちこうじょう",
      "meaning": "small factory in town, backstreet (small) workshop"
    },
    {
      "question": "硫酸",
      "answer": "りゅうさん",
      "meaning": "sulfuric acid, sulphuric acid"
    },
    {
      "question": "初潮",
      "answer": "しょちょう",
      "meaning": "first menstruation"
    },
    {
      "question": "要衝",
      "answer": "ようしょう",
      "meaning": "important point, strategic position, key point"
    },
    {
      "question": "手切れ金",
      "answer": "てぎれきん",
      "meaning": "consolation money, compensation for breaking off relations (e.g. with a mistress), settlement"
    },
    {
      "question": "部数",
      "answer": "ぶすう",
      "meaning": "number of copies, circulation"
    },
    {
      "question": "気詰まり",
      "answer": "きづまり",
      "meaning": "constrained, uncomfortable, awkward"
    },
    {
      "question": "裏話",
      "answer": "うらばなし",
      "meaning": "inside story, the real story (behind something), story not generally known"
    },
    {
      "question": "見下げる",
      "answer": "みさげる",
      "meaning": "to look down over, to look down on"
    },
    {
      "question": "百日",
      "answer": "ひゃくにち",
      "meaning": "hundred days, lengthy time"
    },
    {
      "question": "足湯",
      "answer": "あしゆ",
      "meaning": "footbath, hot spring bath designed for soaking one's feet"
    },
    {
      "question": "築城",
      "answer": "ちくじょう",
      "meaning": "castle construction, building a castle, fortification"
    },
    {
      "question": "双眼",
      "answer": "そうがん",
      "meaning": "both eyes, binocular"
    },
    {
      "question": "揺り籠",
      "answer": "ゆりかご",
      "meaning": "cradle"
    },
    {
      "question": "拙速",
      "answer": "せっそく",
      "meaning": "rough-and-ready, knocked-up, hasty, slipshod, slapdash"
    },
    {
      "question": "付け直す",
      "answer": "つけなおす",
      "meaning": "to repair again, to join again"
    },
    {
      "question": "天下一品",
      "answer": "てんかいっぴん",
      "meaning": "best article under heaven, peerless"
    },
    {
      "question": "眉目秀麗",
      "answer": "びもくしゅうれい",
      "meaning": "handsome"
    },
    {
      "question": "飴と鞭",
      "answer": "あめとむち",
      "meaning": "carrot and stick, candy and whip"
    },
    {
      "question": "鬼に金棒",
      "answer": "おににかなぼう",
      "meaning": "making something strong even stronger, solidifying something's chances, (giving) a metal rod to an o"
    },
    {
      "question": "鳴海",
      "answer": "",
      "meaning": ""
    },
    {
      "question": "楽章",
      "answer": "がくしょう",
      "meaning": "(musical) movement"
    },
    {
      "question": "北陸",
      "answer": "ほくりく",
      "meaning": "Hokuriku region of Honshu (incl. Niigata, Toyama, Ishikawa and Fukui prefectures)"
    },
    {
      "question": "擬装",
      "answer": "ぎそう",
      "meaning": "camouflage, disguise, pretense, feigning, masquerade"
    },
    {
      "question": "矜恃",
      "answer": "きょうじ,きんじ",
      "meaning": "pride, dignity, self-respect"
    },
    {
      "question": "鳥獣",
      "answer": "ちょうじゅう",
      "meaning": "birds and wild animals, wildlife"
    },
    {
      "question": "円周",
      "answer": "えんしゅう",
      "meaning": "circumference"
    },
    {
      "question": "引取り",
      "answer": "ひきとり",
      "meaning": "leaving, accepting"
    },
    {
      "question": "軟骨",
      "answer": "なんこつ",
      "meaning": "cartilage, nankotsu, (dish of) gristle (usu. of chicken, deep-fried)"
    },
    {
      "question": "凡百",
      "answer": "ぼんひゃく,ぼんぴゃく",
      "meaning": "many, many kinds"
    },
    {
      "question": "若年",
      "answer": "じゃくねん",
      "meaning": "youth"
    },
    {
      "question": "補助的",
      "answer": "ほじょてき",
      "meaning": "ancillary, auxiliary"
    },
    {
      "question": "一人勝ち",
      "answer": "ひとりがち",
      "meaning": "being the sole winner, winner-take-all"
    },
    {
      "question": "道士",
      "answer": "どうし",
      "meaning": "a person of high morals, a Taoist"
    },
    {
      "question": "血判",
      "answer": "けっぱん,けつばん,ちばん",
      "meaning": "seal of blood, sealing with one's blood"
    },
    {
      "question": "蕎麦屋",
      "answer": "そばや",
      "meaning": "soba restaurant"
    },
    {
      "question": "残照",
      "answer": "ざんしょう",
      "meaning": "afterglow"
    },
    {
      "question": "寒村",
      "answer": "かんそん",
      "meaning": "deserted village, poor village"
    },
    {
      "question": "大脳",
      "answer": "だいのう",
      "meaning": "cerebrum"
    },
    {
      "question": "健脚",
      "answer": "けんきゃく",
      "meaning": "good walker"
    },
    {
      "question": "家宅捜索",
      "answer": "かたくそうさく",
      "meaning": "premises search, household search"
    },
    {
      "question": "不通",
      "answer": "ふつう",
      "meaning": "suspension, interruption, stoppage, tie-up, cessation"
    },
    {
      "question": "切り上げ",
      "answer": "きりあげ",
      "meaning": "end, conclusion, rounding up, revaluation"
    },
    {
      "question": "拘束力",
      "answer": "こうそくりょく",
      "meaning": "binding force"
    },
    {
      "question": "差別化",
      "answer": "さべつか",
      "meaning": "differentiation"
    },
    {
      "question": "持ち越し",
      "answer": "もちこし",
      "meaning": "work, items, etc. carried over from earlier, hangover, what you ate the day before (and is still bei"
    },
    {
      "question": "碁",
      "answer": "ご",
      "meaning": "go, board game of capturing territory"
    },
    {
      "question": "箱舟",
      "answer": "はこぶね",
      "meaning": "ark (i.e. Noah's)"
    },
    {
      "question": "金剛石",
      "answer": "こんごうせき",
      "meaning": "diamond"
    },
    {
      "question": "常設",
      "answer": "じょうせつ",
      "meaning": "standing (committee), permanent (exhibit)"
    },
    {
      "question": "突端",
      "answer": "とったん,とっぱな",
      "meaning": "tip of a headland, point"
    },
    {
      "question": "大一番",
      "answer": "おおいちばん",
      "meaning": "decisive game, important bout, crucial match"
    },
    {
      "question": "映画監督",
      "answer": "えいがかんとく",
      "meaning": "movie director, film director"
    },
    {
      "question": "裸眼",
      "answer": "らがん",
      "meaning": "bare eyes (i.e. without glasses, contact lenses, etc.), uncorrected vision, unaided vision"
    },
    {
      "question": "痛打",
      "answer": "つうだ",
      "meaning": "hard or crushing blow, severe attack"
    },
    {
      "question": "根無し草",
      "answer": "ねなしぐさ",
      "meaning": "duckweed, rootless person, wanderer"
    },
    {
      "question": "うら若い",
      "answer": "うらわかい",
      "meaning": "young, youthful"
    },
    {
      "question": "基部",
      "answer": "きぶ",
      "meaning": "base, foundation"
    },
    {
      "question": "鎌首",
      "answer": "かまくび",
      "meaning": "sickle-shaped neck (e.g. snake, praying mantis), crooked neck, gooseneck"
    },
    {
      "question": "墨汁",
      "answer": "ぼくじゅう",
      "meaning": "India ink, China ink, ink (of a cuttlefish, etc.)"
    },
    {
      "question": "鍛え",
      "answer": "きたえ",
      "meaning": "forging, tempering, drilling, training, disciplining"
    },
    {
      "question": "黒鳥",
      "answer": "こくちょう",
      "meaning": "black swan (Cygnus atratus)"
    },
    {
      "question": "優待",
      "answer": "ゆうたい",
      "meaning": "preferential treatment, hospitality, warm reception, cordial welcome"
    },
    {
      "question": "巨根",
      "answer": "きょこん",
      "meaning": "large penis"
    },
    {
      "question": "核戦争",
      "answer": "かくせんそう",
      "meaning": "nuclear warfare"
    },
    {
      "question": "巻き髪",
      "answer": "まきがみ",
      "meaning": "curly hair, curled hair"
    },
    {
      "question": "北端",
      "answer": "ほくたん",
      "meaning": "northern extremity"
    },
    {
      "question": "冷汗",
      "answer": "ひやあせ,れいかん",
      "meaning": "cold sweat"
    },
    {
      "question": "談合",
      "answer": "だんごう",
      "meaning": "consultation, discussion, conference, collusion, bid-rigging"
    },
    {
      "question": "搬出",
      "answer": "はんしゅつ",
      "meaning": "carrying out (esp. heavy objects, artwork, furniture), taking out"
    },
    {
      "question": "触れ",
      "answer": "ふれ",
      "meaning": "proclamation, official notice, touch, contact"
    },
    {
      "question": "贋",
      "answer": "にせ",
      "meaning": "imitation, fake, phony, counterfeit, forged, bogus, sham, pseudo-"
    },
    {
      "question": "座敷童",
      "answer": "ざしきわらし",
      "meaning": "protective household deity in Tōhoku, appearing as a red-faced child spirit with bobbed hair"
    },
    {
      "question": "金沢",
      "answer": "かなざわ",
      "meaning": "Kanazawa (city in Ishikawa)"
    },
    {
      "question": "徹甲弾",
      "answer": "てっこうだん",
      "meaning": "armor piercing ammunition, armour piercing ammunition"
    },
    {
      "question": "二心",
      "answer": "ふたごころ,にしん,じしん",
      "meaning": "duplicity, treachery, double-dealing"
    },
    {
      "question": "生き証人",
      "answer": "いきしょうにん",
      "meaning": "living witness"
    },
    {
      "question": "情交",
      "answer": "じょうこう",
      "meaning": "intimacy, sexual intercourse"
    },
    {
      "question": "無理解",
      "answer": "むりかい",
      "meaning": "lack of understanding, lack of sympathy"
    },
    {
      "question": "近親相姦",
      "answer": "きんしんそうかん",
      "meaning": "incest"
    },
    {
      "question": "雲散霧消",
      "answer": "うんさんむしょう",
      "meaning": "vanishing like mist"
    },
    {
      "question": "吹き払う",
      "answer": "ふきはらう",
      "meaning": "to blow off"
    },
    {
      "question": "記帳",
      "answer": "きちょう",
      "meaning": "registry, entry, book-keeping, signature"
    },
    {
      "question": "自治権",
      "answer": "じちけん",
      "meaning": "autonomy, right of self-government"
    },
    {
      "question": "這い蹲る",
      "answer": "はいつくばる",
      "meaning": "to grovel, to go down on one's hands and knees"
    },
    {
      "question": "季節感",
      "answer": "きせつかん",
      "meaning": "sense of the seasons, feeling of seasonality"
    },
    {
      "question": "借り切る",
      "answer": "かりきる",
      "meaning": "to hire for exclusive use, to reserve, to charter"
    },
    {
      "question": "数量",
      "answer": "すうりょう",
      "meaning": "quantity, volume, amount"
    },
    {
      "question": "心する",
      "answer": "こころする",
      "meaning": "to take care, to mind, to be attentive"
    },
    {
      "question": "這入る",
      "answer": "はいる",
      "meaning": "to enter, to go into, to break into, to join, to enroll, to contain, to hold, to accommodate, to hav"
    },
    {
      "question": "巡察",
      "answer": "じゅんさつ",
      "meaning": "(making) a round of inspection, patrolling"
    },
    {
      "question": "外遊",
      "answer": "がいゆう",
      "meaning": "foreign travel"
    },
    {
      "question": "本宅",
      "answer": "ほんたく",
      "meaning": "one's principal residence, main home"
    },
    {
      "question": "敗残",
      "answer": "はいざん",
      "meaning": "survival after defeat, decline (of a person, business, etc.), ruin"
    },
    {
      "question": "五色",
      "answer": "ごしき,ごしょく",
      "meaning": "five colors (usu. red, blue, yellow, white and black), five colours, many kinds, varied, melon, gour"
    },
    {
      "question": "水切り",
      "answer": "みずきり",
      "meaning": "straining, draining, drainer, strainer, colander, cutwater (on ship), forefoot, drip (on building),"
    },
    {
      "question": "語句",
      "answer": "ごく",
      "meaning": "words, phrases"
    },
    {
      "question": "骨折る",
      "answer": "ほねおる",
      "meaning": "to exert oneself greatly, to take pains"
    },
    {
      "question": "隧道",
      "answer": "すいどう,ずいどう,ついどう",
      "meaning": "tunnel"
    },
    {
      "question": "戦機",
      "answer": "せんき",
      "meaning": "time for battle, military secrets, strategy"
    },
    {
      "question": "企図",
      "answer": "きと",
      "meaning": "plan, project, scheme"
    },
    {
      "question": "白飯",
      "answer": "はくはん,しろめし",
      "meaning": "cooked white rice"
    },
    {
      "question": "未曽有",
      "answer": "みぞう",
      "meaning": "unprecedented, unheard-of, record-breaking"
    },
    {
      "question": "喧嘩別れ",
      "answer": "けんかわかれ",
      "meaning": "(of a couple) fighting and splitting up"
    },
    {
      "question": "木馬",
      "answer": "もくば,きうま,きんま",
      "meaning": "wooden horse, rocking horse, vaulting horse, horse used in gymnastics, the horse (ancient torture de"
    },
    {
      "question": "油紙",
      "answer": "あぶらがみ,ゆし",
      "meaning": "oil paper, oiled paper"
    },
    {
      "question": "普遍",
      "answer": "ふへん",
      "meaning": "universal, general, ubiquitous, omnipresent"
    },
    {
      "question": "女顔",
      "answer": "おんながお",
      "meaning": "feminine features, having a girl's face (for a man), girly face"
    },
    {
      "question": "蕩かす",
      "answer": "とろかす",
      "meaning": "to melt (steel, etc.), to liquefy, to soften, to melt (one's heart), to disarm"
    },
    {
      "question": "遍歴",
      "answer": "へんれき",
      "meaning": "travels, pilgrimage, itinerancy"
    },
    {
      "question": "無我",
      "answer": "むが",
      "meaning": "selflessness, self-effacement, self-renunciation, anatta, anatman, doctrine that states that humans"
    },
    {
      "question": "汁気",
      "answer": "しるけ",
      "meaning": "juice"
    },
    {
      "question": "石膏",
      "answer": "せっこう",
      "meaning": "plaster, gypsum, calcium sulphate (sulfate)"
    },
    {
      "question": "偽札",
      "answer": "にせさつ,ぎさつ,にせふだ",
      "meaning": "counterfeit paper money, forged document"
    },
    {
      "question": "鵜",
      "answer": "う",
      "meaning": "cormorant (Phalacrocoracidae spp.)"
    },
    {
      "question": "殺人罪",
      "answer": "さつじんざい",
      "meaning": "(the crime of) murder"
    },
    {
      "question": "伝来",
      "answer": "でんらい",
      "meaning": "ancestral, hereditary, imported, transmitted, handed down"
    },
    {
      "question": "役不足",
      "answer": "やくぶそく",
      "meaning": "dissatisfaction with the work (role) given to one, feeling oneself above the given work (role), not"
    },
    {
      "question": "上昇志向",
      "answer": "じょうしょうしこう",
      "meaning": "desire for improvement (in social standing, etc.), ambition to rise in the world"
    },
    {
      "question": "名を汚す",
      "answer": "なをけがす",
      "meaning": "to shame the name (of), to blot the reputation (of)"
    },
    {
      "question": "本島",
      "answer": "ほんとう",
      "meaning": "main island, this island"
    },
    {
      "question": "側溝",
      "answer": "そっこう",
      "meaning": "gutter, ditch"
    },
    {
      "question": "古都",
      "answer": "こと",
      "meaning": "ancient city, former capital"
    },
    {
      "question": "死蔵",
      "answer": "しぞう",
      "meaning": "hoarding, storing away (without using)"
    },
    {
      "question": "文具",
      "answer": "ぶんぐ",
      "meaning": "stationery"
    },
    {
      "question": "宿願",
      "answer": "しゅくがん",
      "meaning": "longstanding desire"
    },
    {
      "question": "凶事",
      "answer": "きょうじ",
      "meaning": "calamity, misfortune"
    },
    {
      "question": "吉兆",
      "answer": "きっちょう",
      "meaning": "lucky omen, good omen"
    },
    {
      "question": "ため口",
      "answer": "ためぐち",
      "meaning": "casual talk, frank, unreserved speech, peer language"
    },
    {
      "question": "口車",
      "answer": "くちぐるま",
      "meaning": "cajolery, wheedling"
    },
    {
      "question": "金鎖",
      "answer": "きんぐさり",
      "meaning": "golden chain"
    },
    {
      "question": "狐火",
      "answer": "きつねび",
      "meaning": "St. Elmo's fire, will-o'-the-wisp"
    },
    {
      "question": "管区",
      "answer": "かんく",
      "meaning": "jurisdiction"
    },
    {
      "question": "強酸",
      "answer": "きょうさん",
      "meaning": "strong acid"
    },
    {
      "question": "娘婿",
      "answer": "むすめむこ",
      "meaning": "son-in-law"
    },
    {
      "question": "滞納",
      "answer": "たいのう",
      "meaning": "falling behind (with a payment), being in arrears, non-payment, default, delinquency"
    },
    {
      "question": "異文化",
      "answer": "いぶんか",
      "meaning": "foreign culture, foreign cultures"
    },
    {
      "question": "一長一短",
      "answer": "いっちょういったん",
      "meaning": "(something having its) merits and demerits, advantages and disadvantages, good points and shortcomin"
    },
    {
      "question": "分相応",
      "answer": "ぶんそうおう",
      "meaning": "within one's means"
    },
    {
      "question": "伝声管",
      "answer": "でんせいかん",
      "meaning": "speaking tube, voice pipe"
    },
    {
      "question": "鬼面",
      "answer": "きめん",
      "meaning": "mask of a devil, startling appearance, devil's face"
    },
    {
      "question": "玻璃",
      "answer": "はり",
      "meaning": "quartz, glass"
    },
    {
      "question": "疵",
      "answer": "きず",
      "meaning": "wound, injury, cut, gash, bruise, scratch, scrape, scar, chip, crack, nick, flaw, defect, weakness,"
    },
    {
      "question": "馬具",
      "answer": "ばぐ",
      "meaning": "horse tack, horse gear, harness"
    },
    {
      "question": "震え声",
      "answer": "ふるえごえ",
      "meaning": "trembling or quavering voice"
    },
    {
      "question": "冥土",
      "answer": "めいど",
      "meaning": "Hades, the underworld, the other world, realm of the dead"
    },
    {
      "question": "不可逆",
      "answer": "ふかぎゃく",
      "meaning": "irreversible"
    },
    {
      "question": "白塗り",
      "answer": "しろぬり",
      "meaning": "something painted white, white makeup (for an actor), painted white"
    },
    {
      "question": "肺腑",
      "answer": "はいふ",
      "meaning": "lungs, bottom of one's heart, vital point"
    },
    {
      "question": "泰然自若",
      "answer": "たいぜんじじゃく",
      "meaning": "having presence of mind, self-possessed, imperturbable, calm and self-possessed"
    },
    {
      "question": "モテ男",
      "answer": "モテお,モテおとこ",
      "meaning": "man who is popular with women"
    },
    {
      "question": "人身御供",
      "answer": "ひとみごくう",
      "meaning": "human sacrifice, victim"
    },
    {
      "question": "親王",
      "answer": "しんのう",
      "meaning": "prince of royal blood, Imperial prince"
    },
    {
      "question": "伏魔殿",
      "answer": "ふくまでん",
      "meaning": "abode of demons, hotbed (of graft), pandemonium"
    },
    {
      "question": "人災",
      "answer": "じんさい",
      "meaning": "man-made calamity"
    },
    {
      "question": "競泳",
      "answer": "きょうえい",
      "meaning": "competitive swimming, swimming race"
    },
    {
      "question": "筋繊維",
      "answer": "きんせんい",
      "meaning": "muscle fiber, muscle fibre"
    },
    {
      "question": "特盛り",
      "answer": "とくもり",
      "meaning": "extra-large portion, extra-sized serving"
    },
    {
      "question": "肩掛け",
      "answer": "かたかけ",
      "meaning": "shawl"
    },
    {
      "question": "急勾配",
      "answer": "きゅうこうばい",
      "meaning": "steep slope"
    },
    {
      "question": "全般的",
      "answer": "ぜんぱんてき",
      "meaning": "universal, general"
    },
    {
      "question": "物分かり",
      "answer": "ものわかり",
      "meaning": "understanding (of people's circumstances and feelings), perceptiveness, sympathy, wisdom"
    },
    {
      "question": "通説",
      "answer": "つうせつ",
      "meaning": "prevailing view, common opinion, commonly accepted theory"
    },
    {
      "question": "羅刹",
      "answer": "らせつ",
      "meaning": "rakshasa, man-eating demon in Hinduism and Buddhism"
    },
    {
      "question": "演壇",
      "answer": "えんだん",
      "meaning": "rostrum, platform"
    },
    {
      "question": "乳児",
      "answer": "にゅうじ",
      "meaning": "infant (below 1 year old), suckling baby"
    },
    {
      "question": "首級",
      "answer": "しゅきゅう,しるし",
      "meaning": "decapitated head of an enemy"
    },
    {
      "question": "歯列",
      "answer": "しれつ",
      "meaning": "row of teeth"
    },
    {
      "question": "古着屋",
      "answer": "ふるぎや",
      "meaning": "second hand clothes shop, somebody who sells second hand clothes"
    },
    {
      "question": "禁制",
      "answer": "きんせい",
      "meaning": "prohibition, ban, embargo"
    },
    {
      "question": "捕われる",
      "answer": "とらわれる",
      "meaning": "to be caught, to be captured, to be taken prisoner, to be arrested, to be apprehended, to be seized"
    },
    {
      "question": "助勢",
      "answer": "じょせい,すけぜい",
      "meaning": "encouragement, backing, reinforcements"
    },
    {
      "question": "入場券",
      "answer": "にゅうじょうけん",
      "meaning": "admission ticket, entrance ticket, platform ticket, ticket allowing a non-traveller access to a rail"
    },
    {
      "question": "横断幕",
      "answer": "おうだんまく",
      "meaning": "horizontal banner"
    },
    {
      "question": "食虫植物",
      "answer": "しょくちゅうしょくぶつ",
      "meaning": "insectivorous plants, carnivorous plants"
    },
    {
      "question": "板チョコ",
      "answer": "いたチョコ",
      "meaning": "chocolate bar, bar of chocolate"
    },
    {
      "question": "皆々様",
      "answer": "みなみなさま",
      "meaning": "Ladies and Gentlemen!, all of you, everyone"
    },
    {
      "question": "絵心",
      "answer": "えごころ",
      "meaning": "artistic taste, aptitude for painting, ability to appreciate art, desire to paint"
    },
    {
      "question": "振り合う",
      "answer": "ふりあう",
      "meaning": "to touch each other"
    },
    {
      "question": "六角",
      "answer": "ろっかく",
      "meaning": "hexagon"
    },
    {
      "question": "七輪",
      "answer": "しちりん",
      "meaning": "earthen charcoal brazier (for cooking)"
    },
    {
      "question": "湖底",
      "answer": "こてい",
      "meaning": "bottom of a lake"
    },
    {
      "question": "未読",
      "answer": "みどく",
      "meaning": "unread"
    },
    {
      "question": "珍品",
      "answer": "ちんぴん",
      "meaning": "curio, rare article"
    },
    {
      "question": "静聴",
      "answer": "せいちょう",
      "meaning": "listening quietly"
    },
    {
      "question": "採光",
      "answer": "さいこう",
      "meaning": "lighting"
    },
    {
      "question": "目深",
      "answer": "まぶか,めぶか",
      "meaning": "(wearing) low over one's eyes"
    },
    {
      "question": "通気性",
      "answer": "つうきせい",
      "meaning": "air-permeability, breathability"
    },
    {
      "question": "人生観",
      "answer": "じんせいかん",
      "meaning": "view of life"
    },
    {
      "question": "函館",
      "answer": "はこだて",
      "meaning": "Hakodate (city in Hokkaido)"
    },
    {
      "question": "胸像",
      "answer": "きょうぞう",
      "meaning": "bust (sculpture), half-length portrait"
    },
    {
      "question": "装具",
      "answer": "そうぐ",
      "meaning": "equipment, harness, fittings"
    },
    {
      "question": "給水塔",
      "answer": "きゅうすいとう",
      "meaning": "water tower"
    },
    {
      "question": "林間学校",
      "answer": "りんかんがっこう",
      "meaning": "outdoors school"
    },
    {
      "question": "武威",
      "answer": "ぶい",
      "meaning": "military power"
    },
    {
      "question": "元年",
      "answer": "がんねん",
      "meaning": "first year (of an imperial era), year something (important) first happened or began"
    },
    {
      "question": "背信",
      "answer": "はいしん",
      "meaning": "betrayal, infidelity"
    },
    {
      "question": "潜り",
      "answer": "もぐり,くぐり",
      "meaning": "diving, diver, unlicensed (doctor, driver, etc.), unregistered, unqualified, outsider, stranger, sid"
    },
    {
      "question": "起こり",
      "answer": "おこり",
      "meaning": "source, origin, cause, beginning, genesis"
    },
    {
      "question": "慧",
      "answer": "え",
      "meaning": "wisdom, enlightenment, prajñā (one of the three divisions of the noble eightfold path)"
    },
    {
      "question": "半獣",
      "answer": "はんじゅう",
      "meaning": "half-human and half-beast"
    },
    {
      "question": "湖上",
      "answer": "こじょう",
      "meaning": "on the lake"
    },
    {
      "question": "貴石",
      "answer": "きせき",
      "meaning": "precious stone, jewel, gem"
    },
    {
      "question": "危地",
      "answer": "きち",
      "meaning": "dangerous position, peril"
    },
    {
      "question": "取り成す",
      "answer": "とりなす",
      "meaning": "to mediate, to intervene, to smooth"
    },
    {
      "question": "初出",
      "answer": "しょしゅつ,うぶだし",
      "meaning": "first appearance"
    },
    {
      "question": "日本列島",
      "answer": "にほんれっとう,にっぽんれっとう",
      "meaning": "the Japanese islands"
    },
    {
      "question": "黴",
      "answer": "かび",
      "meaning": "mold, mould, mildew"
    },
    {
      "question": "生命保険",
      "answer": "せいめいほけん",
      "meaning": "life insurance"
    },
    {
      "question": "消費者",
      "answer": "しょうひしゃ",
      "meaning": "consumer"
    },
    {
      "question": "狼藉者",
      "answer": "ろうぜきもの",
      "meaning": "rioter, ruffian"
    },
    {
      "question": "嫁入る",
      "answer": "よめいる",
      "meaning": "to wed, to marry a man"
    },
    {
      "question": "芙蓉",
      "answer": "ふよう",
      "meaning": "cotton rose (Hibiscus mutabilis), Confederate rose, dixie rosemallow, lotus blossom"
    },
    {
      "question": "聖別",
      "answer": "せいべつ",
      "meaning": "consecration"
    },
    {
      "question": "口籠もる",
      "answer": "くちごもる",
      "meaning": "to hesitate to say, to mumble, to hem and haw, to falter"
    },
    {
      "question": "無精",
      "answer": "ぶしょう",
      "meaning": "indolence, laziness, sloth"
    },
    {
      "question": "椎茸",
      "answer": "しいたけ",
      "meaning": "shiitake mushroom (Lentinula edodes)"
    },
    {
      "question": "民話",
      "answer": "みんわ",
      "meaning": "folk tale, folktale, folk story, folklore"
    },
    {
      "question": "縛り首",
      "answer": "しばりくび",
      "meaning": "(death by) hanging"
    },
    {
      "question": "出席簿",
      "answer": "しゅっせきぼ",
      "meaning": "attendance record"
    },
    {
      "question": "緩衝",
      "answer": "かんしょう",
      "meaning": "buffered"
    },
    {
      "question": "詰襟",
      "answer": "つめえり",
      "meaning": "stand-up collar"
    },
    {
      "question": "原住民",
      "answer": "げんじゅうみん",
      "meaning": "native people, aboriginal, indigenous people"
    },
    {
      "question": "斜線",
      "answer": "しゃせん",
      "meaning": "oblique line, forward slash"
    },
    {
      "question": "死力",
      "answer": "しりょく",
      "meaning": "desperate effort"
    },
    {
      "question": "調理師",
      "answer": "ちょうりし",
      "meaning": "chef, cook"
    },
    {
      "question": "繕い",
      "answer": "つくろい",
      "meaning": "mending, repair, darning, patching up"
    },
    {
      "question": "淫夢",
      "answer": "いんむ",
      "meaning": "lewd dream, salacious fantasy"
    },
    {
      "question": "嘆",
      "answer": "たん",
      "meaning": "sigh, grief, lamentation"
    },
    {
      "question": "決死隊",
      "answer": "けっしたい",
      "meaning": "suicide corps"
    },
    {
      "question": "対物",
      "answer": "たいぶつ",
      "meaning": "pertaining to objects"
    },
    {
      "question": "加齢",
      "answer": "かれい",
      "meaning": "aging, ageing, adding to one's years"
    },
    {
      "question": "一棟",
      "answer": "ひとむね",
      "meaning": "one house, the same house"
    },
    {
      "question": "ぶりっ子",
      "answer": "ぶりっこ",
      "meaning": "woman or girl who acts cute by playing innocent and helpless"
    },
    {
      "question": "堪忍袋",
      "answer": "かんにんぶくろ",
      "meaning": "one's store of patience"
    },
    {
      "question": "引き合い",
      "answer": "ひきあい",
      "meaning": "reference, example, instance, inquiry (about a product, business deal, etc.), enquiry, being summone"
    },
    {
      "question": "水をさす",
      "answer": "みずをさす",
      "meaning": "to pour water (into), to dilute with water, to hinder, to hamper, to throw cold water on, to put a d"
    },
    {
      "question": "巾",
      "answer": "はば,べき,きん",
      "meaning": "width, breadth, freedom (e.g. of thought), latitude, gap, difference (e.g. in price), range (e.g. of"
    },
    {
      "question": "浮揚",
      "answer": "ふよう",
      "meaning": "floating (e.g. in air, water), floatation, buoyancy, buoying up (e.g. economy)"
    },
    {
      "question": "地殻",
      "answer": "ちかく",
      "meaning": "(Earth's) crust"
    },
    {
      "question": "番兵",
      "answer": "ばんぺい",
      "meaning": "sentry, guard"
    },
    {
      "question": "容赦無く",
      "answer": "ようしゃなく",
      "meaning": "mercilessly, relentlessly, unsparingly"
    },
    {
      "question": "薪割り",
      "answer": "まきわり",
      "meaning": "hatchet, axe, wood-chopping, wood-splitting"
    },
    {
      "question": "水割り",
      "answer": "みずわり",
      "meaning": "cutting an alcoholic beverage (usu. whisky or shōchū), diluting an alcoholic beverage, cut drink, di"
    },
    {
      "question": "年表",
      "answer": "ねんぴょう",
      "meaning": "chronological table"
    },
    {
      "question": "悪政",
      "answer": "あくせい",
      "meaning": "misgovernment, misrule, bad government"
    },
    {
      "question": "純粋培養",
      "answer": "じゅんすいばいよう",
      "meaning": "clean (pure) culture"
    },
    {
      "question": "建立",
      "answer": "こんりゅう,けんりつ",
      "meaning": "(act of) building (temple, monument, etc.), erection"
    },
    {
      "question": "仮称",
      "answer": "かしょう",
      "meaning": "temporary name, provisional name"
    },
    {
      "question": "誤爆",
      "answer": "ごばく",
      "meaning": "bombing (shelling) the wrong target, (be killed by) friendly fire"
    },
    {
      "question": "湯上り",
      "answer": "ゆあがり",
      "meaning": "after a bath, after taking a bath, large towel used after taking a bath, yukata worn after taking a"
    },
    {
      "question": "騙し",
      "answer": "だまし",
      "meaning": "deceiving, cheating, fooling"
    },
    {
      "question": "箝口令",
      "answer": "かんこうれい",
      "meaning": "gag order, gag rule, gag law"
    },
    {
      "question": "蓬",
      "answer": "よもぎ",
      "meaning": "Japanese mugwort (Artemisia princeps), mugwort (any plant of genus Artemisia), wormwood, sagebrush"
    },
    {
      "question": "賛",
      "answer": "さん",
      "meaning": "praise, tribute, inscription (on a painting)"
    },
    {
      "question": "揚陸",
      "answer": "ようりく",
      "meaning": "unloading (a ship), landing, disembarkation"
    },
    {
      "question": "襟巻き",
      "answer": "えりまき",
      "meaning": "muffler (often fur), scarf, comforter"
    },
    {
      "question": "拝殿",
      "answer": "はいでん",
      "meaning": "front shrine, hall of worship"
    },
    {
      "question": "爆雷",
      "answer": "ばくらい",
      "meaning": "depth charge"
    },
    {
      "question": "死病",
      "answer": "しびょう",
      "meaning": "fatal disease"
    },
    {
      "question": "草取り",
      "answer": "くさとり",
      "meaning": "weeding, weeder, weeding fork"
    },
    {
      "question": "本船",
      "answer": "ほんせん",
      "meaning": "mother ship, this ship"
    },
    {
      "question": "栗鼠",
      "answer": "りす",
      "meaning": "squirrel (any mammal of family Sciuridae), Japanese squirrel (Sciurus lis)"
    },
    {
      "question": "強化合宿",
      "answer": "きょうかがっしゅく",
      "meaning": "training camp"
    },
    {
      "question": "縛め",
      "answer": "いましめ",
      "meaning": "bonds, bondage, binding"
    },
    {
      "question": "小船",
      "answer": "こぶね",
      "meaning": "small boat"
    },
    {
      "question": "入寮",
      "answer": "にゅうりょう",
      "meaning": "moving into a dormitory"
    },
    {
      "question": "野放図",
      "answer": "のほうず",
      "meaning": "unregulated, unruly, wild, unbridled"
    },
    {
      "question": "絞り取る",
      "answer": "しぼりとる",
      "meaning": "to exploit, to extort, to squeeze (someone), to squeeze (e.g. oil, juice), to wring out, to press ou"
    },
    {
      "question": "山歩き",
      "answer": "やまあるき",
      "meaning": "mountain-walking, hiking"
    },
    {
      "question": "祓",
      "answer": "はらい,はらえ",
      "meaning": "purification, exorcism"
    },
    {
      "question": "凝集",
      "answer": "ぎょうしゅう",
      "meaning": "agglomeration, clumping together, cohesion (of ions, etc.), flocculation (of colloidal particles), a"
    },
    {
      "question": "夜桜",
      "answer": "よざくら",
      "meaning": "cherry blossoms at night"
    },
    {
      "question": "超新星",
      "answer": "ちょうしんせい",
      "meaning": "supernova"
    },
    {
      "question": "緩衝地帯",
      "answer": "かんしょうちたい",
      "meaning": "buffer zone"
    },
    {
      "question": "急報",
      "answer": "きゅうほう",
      "meaning": "urgent report, urgent message"
    },
    {
      "question": "焦げ茶",
      "answer": "こげちゃ",
      "meaning": "dark brown, olive brown"
    },
    {
      "question": "指圧",
      "answer": "しあつ",
      "meaning": "shiatsu, acupressure, form of Japanese finger-pressure therapy"
    },
    {
      "question": "絞まる",
      "answer": "しまる",
      "meaning": "to be strangled, to be constricted"
    },
    {
      "question": "射竦める",
      "answer": "いすくめる",
      "meaning": "to pin the enemy down, to glare another down (and render impotent)"
    },
    {
      "question": "跡を追う",
      "answer": "あとをおう",
      "meaning": "to follow, to pursue, to chase, to run after, to die right after a loved one, to kill oneself after"
    },
    {
      "question": "公共施設",
      "answer": "こうきょうしせつ",
      "meaning": "public facilities, utilities"
    },
    {
      "question": "所構わず",
      "answer": "ところかまわず",
      "meaning": "irrespective of the occasion, indiscriminately"
    },
    {
      "question": "貯水池",
      "answer": "ちょすいち",
      "meaning": "reservoir"
    },
    {
      "question": "火刑",
      "answer": "かけい",
      "meaning": "burning at the stake, execution by burning"
    },
    {
      "question": "封入",
      "answer": "ふうにゅう",
      "meaning": "enclose (in letter)"
    },
    {
      "question": "居直る",
      "answer": "いなおる",
      "meaning": "to sit upright, to sit up straight, to take a defiant attitude, to become aggressive, to take the of"
    },
    {
      "question": "山程",
      "answer": "やまほど",
      "meaning": "lots of, a ton of, a mountain of, piles of, heaps of, so many, so much"
    },
    {
      "question": "但し書き",
      "answer": "ただしがき",
      "meaning": "proviso"
    },
    {
      "question": "帯状",
      "answer": "おびじょう,たいじょう",
      "meaning": "belt-shaped"
    },
    {
      "question": "食い入る",
      "answer": "くいいる",
      "meaning": "to eat into"
    },
    {
      "question": "手心",
      "answer": "てごころ",
      "meaning": "discretion, consideration, allowance"
    },
    {
      "question": "悔やみ",
      "answer": "くやみ",
      "meaning": "condolence, condolences"
    },
    {
      "question": "落ち込み",
      "answer": "おちこみ",
      "meaning": "decline, downturn, drop, fall, (mental) depression, low spirits"
    },
    {
      "question": "緩まる",
      "answer": "ゆるまる",
      "meaning": "to become loose, to slacken, to soften"
    },
    {
      "question": "副将軍",
      "answer": "ふくしょうぐん",
      "meaning": "lieutenant general, vice-shogun"
    },
    {
      "question": "庶務",
      "answer": "しょむ",
      "meaning": "general affairs"
    },
    {
      "question": "岩戸",
      "answer": "いわと",
      "meaning": "rock door (to a cave)"
    },
    {
      "question": "十戒",
      "answer": "じっかい",
      "meaning": "the 10 precepts, Ten Commandments, Decalogue, Decalog"
    },
    {
      "question": "決算",
      "answer": "けっさん",
      "meaning": "settlement of accounts, closing accounts, financial results, reporting (of accounts)"
    },
    {
      "question": "白髪頭",
      "answer": "しらがあたま",
      "meaning": "gray or silver haired (grey)"
    },
    {
      "question": "落盤",
      "answer": "らくばん",
      "meaning": "cave-in"
    },
    {
      "question": "未成年者",
      "answer": "みせいねんしゃ",
      "meaning": "minor, person under age"
    },
    {
      "question": "脊椎",
      "answer": "せきつい",
      "meaning": "spine, vertebral column"
    },
    {
      "question": "永らえる",
      "answer": "ながらえる",
      "meaning": "to have a long life, to live a long time"
    },
    {
      "question": "御年",
      "answer": "おんとし",
      "meaning": "age"
    },
    {
      "question": "和える",
      "answer": "あえる",
      "meaning": "to dress (vegetables, salad, etc.)"
    },
    {
      "question": "取り組み",
      "answer": "とりくみ",
      "meaning": "bout (in sports, etc.), match, effort, initiative, dealing with, grappling with, wrestling with"
    },
    {
      "question": "僧衣",
      "answer": "そうい",
      "meaning": "priest's garb"
    },
    {
      "question": "剣帯",
      "answer": "けんたい",
      "meaning": "sword belt"
    },
    {
      "question": "増額",
      "answer": "ぞうがく",
      "meaning": "increase (in an amount of money)"
    },
    {
      "question": "電撃的",
      "answer": "でんげきてき",
      "meaning": "sudden, lightning, immediate, shocking"
    },
    {
      "question": "中古品",
      "answer": "ちゅうこひん",
      "meaning": "secondhand article, secondhand goods, used item"
    },
    {
      "question": "百歳",
      "answer": "ももとせ",
      "meaning": "century, hundred years, a long time"
    },
    {
      "question": "恨み節",
      "answer": "うらみぶし",
      "meaning": "song with lyrics about resentment and a sorrowful tune, resentful complaint"
    },
    {
      "question": "擦り込む",
      "answer": "すりこむ",
      "meaning": "to rub in (e.g. cream into the skin), to grind and mix (e.g. pepper into miso)"
    },
    {
      "question": "二律背反",
      "answer": "にりつはいはん",
      "meaning": "antinomy, self-contradiction, either-or situation, choice between mutually exclusive alternatives"
    },
    {
      "question": "前評判",
      "answer": "まえひょうばん",
      "meaning": "(degree of) public interest in forthcoming event or performance, advance reviews"
    },
    {
      "question": "凝り性",
      "answer": "こりしょう",
      "meaning": "fastidiousness, enthusiasm for one thing, meticulousness, monomania, obsession, susceptibility for a"
    },
    {
      "question": "飲み口",
      "answer": "のみくち,のみぐち",
      "meaning": "taste (of a liquid, esp. alcoholic beverages), someone who enjoys alcohol, place one's lips touch on"
    },
    {
      "question": "戦ぐ",
      "answer": "そよぐ",
      "meaning": "to rustle, to sway, to stir, to flutter"
    },
    {
      "question": "出直し",
      "answer": "でなおし",
      "meaning": "adjustment, touch up"
    },
    {
      "question": "肆",
      "answer": "し,ほしいまま",
      "meaning": "four, selfish, self-indulgent, arbitrary"
    },
    {
      "question": "火の神",
      "answer": "ひのかみ",
      "meaning": "god of fire (in Japanese mythology, usu. Kagutsuchi no Kami)"
    },
    {
      "question": "最高神",
      "answer": "さいこうしん",
      "meaning": "supreme deity"
    },
    {
      "question": "東国",
      "answer": "とうごく",
      "meaning": "eastern country, eastern provinces, Kanto provinces"
    },
    {
      "question": "開廷",
      "answer": "かいてい",
      "meaning": "court session, trial"
    },
    {
      "question": "風防",
      "answer": "ふうぼう",
      "meaning": "protection against wind, windbreak"
    },
    {
      "question": "仕様書",
      "answer": "しようしょ",
      "meaning": "specification document"
    },
    {
      "question": "美観",
      "answer": "びかん",
      "meaning": "fine view, beautiful sight"
    },
    {
      "question": "下船",
      "answer": "げせん",
      "meaning": "disembarkation, getting off a ship, going ashore"
    },
    {
      "question": "鉄屑",
      "answer": "てつくず",
      "meaning": "scrap iron"
    },
    {
      "question": "微粒子",
      "answer": "びりゅうし",
      "meaning": "corpuscle, minute particle, particulate"
    },
    {
      "question": "血気",
      "answer": "けっき",
      "meaning": "vigor, vigour, ardor, ardour, high spirits"
    },
    {
      "question": "生乾き",
      "answer": "なまがわき",
      "meaning": "half-dried"
    },
    {
      "question": "不適",
      "answer": "ふてき",
      "meaning": "inadequacy, inappropriateness, unfitness, impropriety"
    },
    {
      "question": "柔ら",
      "answer": "やわら",
      "meaning": "judo, jujutsu"
    },
    {
      "question": "空力",
      "answer": "くうりき",
      "meaning": "aerodynamics"
    },
    {
      "question": "火炎瓶",
      "answer": "かえんびん",
      "meaning": "Molotov cocktail, petrol bomb, gasoline bomb"
    },
    {
      "question": "山吹色",
      "answer": "やまぶきいろ",
      "meaning": "bright golden yellow"
    },
    {
      "question": "食休み",
      "answer": "しょくやすみ",
      "meaning": "rest after a meal"
    },
    {
      "question": "弓引く",
      "answer": "ゆみひく",
      "meaning": "to bend a bow, to shoot an arrow, to rise up against, to rebel against"
    },
    {
      "question": "飛燕",
      "answer": "ひえん",
      "meaning": "swallow in flight"
    },
    {
      "question": "自然科学",
      "answer": "しぜんかがく",
      "meaning": "natural science"
    },
    {
      "question": "見取る",
      "answer": "みとる",
      "meaning": "to perceive, to understand"
    },
    {
      "question": "認知症",
      "answer": "にんちしょう",
      "meaning": "cognitive impairment, senility, dementia"
    },
    {
      "question": "大麦",
      "answer": "おおむぎ",
      "meaning": "barley (Hordeum vulgare)"
    },
    {
      "question": "倅",
      "answer": "せがれ",
      "meaning": "son, punk, brat, penis"
    },
    {
      "question": "赤錆",
      "answer": "あかさび",
      "meaning": "rust"
    },
    {
      "question": "教習所",
      "answer": "きょうしゅうじょ,きょうしゅうしょ",
      "meaning": "training institute"
    },
    {
      "question": "平衡",
      "answer": "へいこう",
      "meaning": "even scale, equilibrium, balance, equalization, equalisation"
    },
    {
      "question": "法人",
      "answer": "ほうじん",
      "meaning": "corporate body, corporation, (legal) person, (juridical) person"
    },
    {
      "question": "神の国",
      "answer": "かみのくに",
      "meaning": "land of the gods, Japan, Heaven (in Christianity)"
    },
    {
      "question": "限定版",
      "answer": "げんていばん",
      "meaning": "limited edition"
    },
    {
      "question": "尻軽",
      "answer": "しりがる",
      "meaning": "loose, promiscuous, unfaithful, wanton, of loose morals, quick, brisk, energetic, active, rash, thou"
    },
    {
      "question": "典",
      "answer": "てん,のり",
      "meaning": "ceremony, celebration, law code, rule, law"
    },
    {
      "question": "初日の出",
      "answer": "はつひので",
      "meaning": "first sunrise of the year, sunrise on New Year's Day"
    },
    {
      "question": "立太子",
      "answer": "りったいし",
      "meaning": "investiture of the Crown Prince"
    },
    {
      "question": "小節",
      "answer": "しょうせつ,こぶし",
      "meaning": "bar, measure, short pause (in writing), petty principles, minor details, undulating melodic ornament"
    },
    {
      "question": "別動隊",
      "answer": "べつどうたい",
      "meaning": "flying column, detached force"
    },
    {
      "question": "校正",
      "answer": "こうせい",
      "meaning": "proofreading, correction of press, calibration"
    },
    {
      "question": "華道",
      "answer": "かどう",
      "meaning": "flower arrangement"
    },
    {
      "question": "役作り",
      "answer": "やくづくり",
      "meaning": "study (for a role), preparation for a part (in a play, etc.)"
    },
    {
      "question": "死肉",
      "answer": "しにく",
      "meaning": "dead flesh, carrion"
    },
    {
      "question": "協賛",
      "answer": "きょうさん",
      "meaning": "support, mutual aid, cooperation, approval, authorization, authorisation"
    },
    {
      "question": "斜陽",
      "answer": "しゃよう",
      "meaning": "setting sun, decline (e.g. of industry)"
    },
    {
      "question": "返す返す",
      "answer": "かえすがえす",
      "meaning": "repeatedly, to a tremendous extent"
    },
    {
      "question": "侘しい",
      "answer": "わびしい",
      "meaning": "miserable, wretched, lonely, dreary, shabby, comfortless"
    },
    {
      "question": "深窓",
      "answer": "しんそう",
      "meaning": "secluded inner room"
    },
    {
      "question": "見知り",
      "answer": "みしり",
      "meaning": "recognition, acquaintance"
    },
    {
      "question": "汚し",
      "answer": "よごし",
      "meaning": "soiling, polluting, being dirty, shame, disgrace, dishonor, dishonour, chopped fish, shellfish or ve"
    },
    {
      "question": "師父",
      "answer": "しふ",
      "meaning": "fatherly master"
    },
    {
      "question": "後援会",
      "answer": "こうえんかい",
      "meaning": "support group, fan club, (election) committee"
    },
    {
      "question": "風神",
      "answer": "ふうじん",
      "meaning": "wind god"
    },
    {
      "question": "入植",
      "answer": "にゅうしょく",
      "meaning": "settlement, immigration"
    },
    {
      "question": "性転換",
      "answer": "せいてんかん",
      "meaning": "sex change"
    },
    {
      "question": "判事",
      "answer": "はんじ",
      "meaning": "judge, judiciary"
    },
    {
      "question": "国際空港",
      "answer": "こくさいくうこう",
      "meaning": "international airport"
    },
    {
      "question": "化学物質",
      "answer": "かがくぶっしつ",
      "meaning": "chemical substances, chemicals"
    },
    {
      "question": "茶褐色",
      "answer": "ちゃかっしょく",
      "meaning": "dark reddish-brown, liver color"
    },
    {
      "question": "静々",
      "answer": "しずしず",
      "meaning": "quietly, slowly, gracefully"
    },
    {
      "question": "完済",
      "answer": "かんさい",
      "meaning": "full payment, liquidation"
    },
    {
      "question": "公共事業",
      "answer": "こうきょうじぎょう",
      "meaning": "public works, public-works projects, public utilities"
    },
    {
      "question": "深刻化",
      "answer": "しんこくか",
      "meaning": "becoming more serious or severe, aggravation, intensification"
    },
    {
      "question": "七五三",
      "answer": "しちごさん,しめ",
      "meaning": "festival (shrine visit) by children aged 7, 5 and 3, lucky numbers 7, 5 and 3, rope used to cordon o"
    },
    {
      "question": "熱唱",
      "answer": "ねっしょう",
      "meaning": "singing enthusiastically"
    },
    {
      "question": "屋形",
      "answer": "やかた",
      "meaning": "mansion, palace, manor house, castle, nobleman, noblewoman, dignitary, cabin (on a boat, carriage, e"
    },
    {
      "question": "凶相",
      "answer": "きょうそう",
      "meaning": "bad luck (result from fortune telling), evil countenance"
    },
    {
      "question": "勤め人",
      "answer": "つとめにん",
      "meaning": "office worker, salaried worker, white-collar worker"
    },
    {
      "question": "子牛",
      "answer": "こうし,こうじ",
      "meaning": "calf, small cow"
    },
    {
      "question": "空輸",
      "answer": "くうゆ",
      "meaning": "air transport, air lift, airlift"
    },
    {
      "question": "自家発電",
      "answer": "じかはつでん",
      "meaning": "private power generation, masturbation"
    },
    {
      "question": "不親切",
      "answer": "ふしんせつ",
      "meaning": "unkindness, unfriendliness"
    },
    {
      "question": "効",
      "answer": "こう,かい",
      "meaning": "efficacy, benefit, efficiency, effect, result, success, worth, use, avail, Kai (former province loca"
    },
    {
      "question": "日本式",
      "answer": "にほんしき",
      "meaning": "Japanese style"
    },
    {
      "question": "詰まり",
      "answer": "つまり",
      "meaning": "that is to say, that is, in other words, I mean, that (this, it) means, in short, in brief, to sum u"
    },
    {
      "question": "掌を返す",
      "answer": "てのひらをかえす,たなごころをかえす,しょうをかえす",
      "meaning": "to flip-flop, to do an about-face, to flip over one's hand, to do something easy"
    },
    {
      "question": "霊獣",
      "answer": "れいじゅう",
      "meaning": "sacred beast"
    },
    {
      "question": "叛乱",
      "answer": "はんらん",
      "meaning": "insurrection, mutiny, rebellion, revolt, uprising"
    },
    {
      "question": "詐術",
      "answer": "さじゅつ",
      "meaning": "swindling"
    },
    {
      "question": "進路指導",
      "answer": "しんろしどう",
      "meaning": "guidance counseling"
    },
    {
      "question": "月下",
      "answer": "げっか",
      "meaning": "in the moonlight"
    },
    {
      "question": "蹴立てる",
      "answer": "けたてる",
      "meaning": "to kick up"
    },
    {
      "question": "貯水",
      "answer": "ちょすい",
      "meaning": "storage of water"
    },
    {
      "question": "暗闘",
      "answer": "あんとう",
      "meaning": "secret feud, wordless pantomime performed in the dark (in kabuki)"
    },
    {
      "question": "代理戦争",
      "answer": "だいりせんそう",
      "meaning": "war by proxy, proxy war"
    },
    {
      "question": "出土",
      "answer": "しゅつど",
      "meaning": "archeological excavation (archaeological)"
    },
    {
      "question": "保母",
      "answer": "ほぼ",
      "meaning": "childcare worker, kindergarten teacher"
    },
    {
      "question": "草刈り",
      "answer": "くさかり",
      "meaning": "mowing, mower"
    },
    {
      "question": "欲深",
      "answer": "よくふか,よくぶか",
      "meaning": "greedy, avaricious, covetous"
    },
    {
      "question": "流転",
      "answer": "るてん,りゅうてん",
      "meaning": "vicissitudes, continual change, transmigration, metempsychosis"
    },
    {
      "question": "参考人",
      "answer": "さんこうにん",
      "meaning": "person given as a reference, witness, potential suspect, person of interest"
    },
    {
      "question": "恩情",
      "answer": "おんじょう",
      "meaning": "compassion, affection"
    },
    {
      "question": "和人",
      "answer": "わじん,わひと",
      "meaning": "Japanese person, you"
    },
    {
      "question": "鉄剣",
      "answer": "てっけん",
      "meaning": "iron sword"
    },
    {
      "question": "家老",
      "answer": "かろう",
      "meaning": "chief retainer, daimyo's minister"
    },
    {
      "question": "火縄銃",
      "answer": "ひなわじゅう",
      "meaning": "matchlock, arquebus"
    },
    {
      "question": "大全",
      "answer": "たいぜん",
      "meaning": "encyclopedia, complete works"
    },
    {
      "question": "動力炉",
      "answer": "どうりょくろ",
      "meaning": "nuclear power reactor"
    },
    {
      "question": "九六",
      "answer": "くんろく",
      "meaning": "ozeki ranked wrestler unable to live up to the expectations of his rank"
    },
    {
      "question": "仮想現実",
      "answer": "かそうげんじつ",
      "meaning": "VR, Virtual Reality"
    },
    {
      "question": "土木工事",
      "answer": "どぼくこうじ",
      "meaning": "public works"
    },
    {
      "question": "釣果",
      "answer": "ちょうか",
      "meaning": "catch (fishing), amount of fish caught, caught fish"
    },
    {
      "question": "女学校",
      "answer": "じょがっこう",
      "meaning": "girls' school"
    },
    {
      "question": "即座",
      "answer": "そくざ",
      "meaning": "immediate, right there on the spot, impromptu, instant, instantaneous"
    },
    {
      "question": "轡",
      "answer": "くつわ,くつばみ",
      "meaning": "bit (mouthpiece)"
    },
    {
      "question": "難事",
      "answer": "なんじ",
      "meaning": "difficulty"
    },
    {
      "question": "券売機",
      "answer": "けんばいき",
      "meaning": "ticket machine, ticket-vending machine"
    },
    {
      "question": "接岸",
      "answer": "せつがん",
      "meaning": "coming alongside a pier, quay, etc., reaching land (of a boat)"
    },
    {
      "question": "踝",
      "answer": "くるぶし",
      "meaning": "ankle, malleolus, ankle bone"
    },
    {
      "question": "盗み食い",
      "answer": "ぬすみぐい",
      "meaning": "sneaking a bite, snitching food"
    },
    {
      "question": "書置き",
      "answer": "かきおき",
      "meaning": "note (letter) left behind, will"
    },
    {
      "question": "死に目",
      "answer": "しにめ",
      "meaning": "moment of death"
    },
    {
      "question": "旅商人",
      "answer": "たびしょうにん,たびあきんど",
      "meaning": "peddler"
    },
    {
      "question": "湯殿",
      "answer": "ゆどの",
      "meaning": "bathroom, bathing, bathing attendant (for a noble)"
    },
    {
      "question": "好景気",
      "answer": "こうけいき",
      "meaning": "good times, boom, (wave of) prosperity"
    },
    {
      "question": "風呂桶",
      "answer": "ふろおけ",
      "meaning": "bathtub (esp. wooden and bucket-shaped), small bucket used while bathing"
    },
    {
      "question": "絞首刑",
      "answer": "こうしゅけい",
      "meaning": "death by hanging, execution by hanging"
    },
    {
      "question": "平泳ぎ",
      "answer": "ひらおよぎ",
      "meaning": "breaststroke (swimming)"
    },
    {
      "question": "風速",
      "answer": "ふうそく",
      "meaning": "wind speed"
    },
    {
      "question": "否認",
      "answer": "ひにん",
      "meaning": "denial, negation, repudiation, disapproval"
    },
    {
      "question": "醸成",
      "answer": "じょうせい",
      "meaning": "brewing, fermenting, arousing, causing, creating, bringing about"
    },
    {
      "question": "夜露",
      "answer": "よつゆ,やろ",
      "meaning": "evening dew, night dew"
    },
    {
      "question": "沽券",
      "answer": "こけん,うりけん",
      "meaning": "dignity, credit, public estimation, face, honor, reputation, deed of sale (for a land, forest or hou"
    },
    {
      "question": "手話",
      "answer": "しゅわ",
      "meaning": "sign language"
    },
    {
      "question": "敵中",
      "answer": "てきちゅう",
      "meaning": "in the midst of the enemy"
    },
    {
      "question": "湯治",
      "answer": "とうじ",
      "meaning": "hot-spring cure, taking the baths"
    },
    {
      "question": "非通知",
      "answer": "ひつうち",
      "meaning": "number-withheld phone calls"
    },
    {
      "question": "駄洒落",
      "answer": "だじゃれ",
      "meaning": "feeble joke, bad pun"
    },
    {
      "question": "末弟",
      "answer": "ばってい,まってい",
      "meaning": "youngest brother, last disciple"
    },
    {
      "question": "裁可",
      "answer": "さいか",
      "meaning": "sanction, approval"
    },
    {
      "question": "針千本",
      "answer": "はりせんぼん",
      "meaning": "porcupinefish (Diodon holacanthus), balloonfish"
    },
    {
      "question": "並み居る",
      "answer": "なみいる",
      "meaning": "to sit in a row, to be present (and lined up)"
    },
    {
      "question": "短絡",
      "answer": "たんらく",
      "meaning": "short circuit, short, illogical jump, drawing a hasty inference (between two events), jumping to con"
    },
    {
      "question": "屋台骨",
      "answer": "やたいぼね",
      "meaning": "framework (of a building), foundation, mainstay, support, supporter, fortune"
    },
    {
      "question": "気が長い",
      "answer": "きがながい",
      "meaning": "patient, having a long fuse"
    },
    {
      "question": "竜騎兵",
      "answer": "りゅうきへい",
      "meaning": "dragoon"
    },
    {
      "question": "法典",
      "answer": "ほうてん",
      "meaning": "code of law, body of law"
    },
    {
      "question": "野花",
      "answer": "",
      "meaning": ""
    },
    {
      "question": "仮縫い",
      "answer": "かりぬい",
      "meaning": "temporary sewing, basting"
    },
    {
      "question": "酔いどれ",
      "answer": "よいどれ",
      "meaning": "drunkard, drunk"
    },
    {
      "question": "機織り",
      "answer": "はたおり",
      "meaning": "weaving, weaver"
    },
    {
      "question": "受信機",
      "answer": "じゅしんき",
      "meaning": "(television, radio, etc.) receiver"
    },
    {
      "question": "漫画喫茶",
      "answer": "まんがきっさ",
      "meaning": "manga cafe, coffee shop with a manga library (usu. has Internet facilities and charges by the hour)"
    },
    {
      "question": "女系",
      "answer": "じょけい,にょけい",
      "meaning": "female line, matrilinear"
    },
    {
      "question": "異郷",
      "answer": "いきょう",
      "meaning": "foreign country, foreign land, strange land, far-off land"
    },
    {
      "question": "顔文字",
      "answer": "かおもじ",
      "meaning": "emoticon, smiley, kaomoji"
    },
    {
      "question": "頓狂",
      "answer": "とんきょう",
      "meaning": "wild, in disarray"
    },
    {
      "question": "加点",
      "answer": "かてん",
      "meaning": "adding points, addition of marks and symbols to a classical Chinese text to aid reading in Japanese"
    },
    {
      "question": "暴利",
      "answer": "ぼうり",
      "meaning": "excessive profits, usury"
    },
    {
      "question": "垂れ",
      "answer": "たれ,だれ,しだれ",
      "meaning": "sauce (esp. soy or mirin-based dipping sauce), hanging, something hanging (flap, lappet, etc.), (ken"
    },
    {
      "question": "皇都",
      "answer": "こうと",
      "meaning": "imperial capital"
    },
    {
      "question": "氷菓",
      "answer": "ひょうか",
      "meaning": "ice cream, flavoured ice, sherbet"
    },
    {
      "question": "曙光",
      "answer": "しょこう",
      "meaning": "dawn, daybreak, first light of day, first indication, glimpse, gleam, flash, prospects"
    },
    {
      "question": "横綱",
      "answer": "よこづな",
      "meaning": "yokozuna (highest rank in sumo), grand champion, best in its field, crème de la crème, cream of the"
    },
    {
      "question": "板の間",
      "answer": "いたのま",
      "meaning": "wooden floor, room with a wooden floor, changing room (at a public bath)"
    },
    {
      "question": "塩素",
      "answer": "えんそ",
      "meaning": "chlorine (Cl)"
    },
    {
      "question": "還暦",
      "answer": "かんれき",
      "meaning": "60th birthday"
    },
    {
      "question": "手抜かり",
      "answer": "てぬかり",
      "meaning": "oversight, omission, mistake"
    },
    {
      "question": "難癖",
      "answer": "なんくせ",
      "meaning": "fault"
    },
    {
      "question": "院生",
      "answer": "いんせい",
      "meaning": "graduate student, insei, apprentice go professional"
    },
    {
      "question": "石積み",
      "answer": "いしづみ",
      "meaning": "masonry, stonework"
    },
    {
      "question": "乾坤一擲",
      "answer": "けんこんいってき",
      "meaning": "stake all (on something), play for all or nothing, throwing all into a task"
    },
    {
      "question": "胴上げ",
      "answer": "どうあげ",
      "meaning": "tossing (someone) into the air (in celebration)"
    },
    {
      "question": "余所行き",
      "answer": "よそゆき,よそいき",
      "meaning": "going out, one's best clothes, formal (e.g. language), best (behaviour, manners, etc.)"
    },
    {
      "question": "空中分解",
      "answer": "くうちゅうぶんかい",
      "meaning": "mid-air breakage or disintegration"
    },
    {
      "question": "文才",
      "answer": "ぶんさい",
      "meaning": "literary talent"
    },
    {
      "question": "骨張る",
      "answer": "ほねばる",
      "meaning": "to be bony, to be angular"
    },
    {
      "question": "片肘",
      "answer": "かたひじ",
      "meaning": "one elbow"
    },
    {
      "question": "正常化",
      "answer": "せいじょうか",
      "meaning": "normalization, normalisation"
    },
    {
      "question": "大任",
      "answer": "たいにん",
      "meaning": "important task, important duty, important mission, heavy responsibility"
    },
    {
      "question": "煮炊き",
      "answer": "にたき",
      "meaning": "cooking"
    },
    {
      "question": "同伴者",
      "answer": "どうはんしゃ",
      "meaning": "companion"
    },
    {
      "question": "三郎",
      "answer": "さぶろう",
      "meaning": "third son, Occella iburia (species of poacher)"
    },
    {
      "question": "馬丁",
      "answer": "ばてい",
      "meaning": "stable boy, stable hand, groom"
    },
    {
      "question": "農薬",
      "answer": "のうやく",
      "meaning": "agricultural chemical (i.e. pesticide, herbicide, fungicide, etc.), agrochemical, agrichemical"
    },
    {
      "question": "鎖帷子",
      "answer": "くさりかたびら",
      "meaning": "chain mail (armor, armour)"
    },
    {
      "question": "投網",
      "answer": "とあみ,なげあみ",
      "meaning": "cast net, casting net"
    },
    {
      "question": "外注",
      "answer": "がいちゅう",
      "meaning": "outside order, outsourcing, custom (manufacture)"
    },
    {
      "question": "一字",
      "answer": "いちじ",
      "meaning": "(one) letter, (one) character"
    },
    {
      "question": "貫徹",
      "answer": "かんてつ",
      "meaning": "accomplishment, realization, realisation, penetration"
    },
    {
      "question": "情報管理",
      "answer": "じょうほうかんり",
      "meaning": "information management"
    },
    {
      "question": "慰撫",
      "answer": "いぶ",
      "meaning": "pacification, soothing"
    },
    {
      "question": "解熱剤",
      "answer": "げねつざい",
      "meaning": "fever medicine, antipyretic, antifebrile"
    },
    {
      "question": "愛欲",
      "answer": "あいよく",
      "meaning": "passion, sexual desire, lust, attachment (esp. to one's family or a member of the opposite sex)"
    },
    {
      "question": "転ずる",
      "answer": "てんずる",
      "meaning": "to turn, to shift, to alter, to distract"
    },
    {
      "question": "勤務先",
      "answer": "きんむさき",
      "meaning": "place of employment"
    },
    {
      "question": "手を通す",
      "answer": "てをとおす",
      "meaning": "to put on (clothing, esp. new)"
    },
    {
      "question": "下知",
      "answer": "げじ,げち,げぢ",
      "meaning": "command, order"
    },
    {
      "question": "興信所",
      "answer": "こうしんじょ",
      "meaning": "detective agency"
    },
    {
      "question": "行間",
      "answer": "ぎょうかん",
      "meaning": "line-spacing in text, between the lines"
    },
    {
      "question": "戦禍",
      "answer": "せんか",
      "meaning": "war damage, ravages of war, horrors of war"
    },
    {
      "question": "酔い止め",
      "answer": "よいどめ",
      "meaning": "anti-travel sickness (medicine)"
    },
    {
      "question": "主立つ",
      "answer": "おもだつ",
      "meaning": "to be main, to be principal, to be important, to be conspicuous, to be prominent"
    },
    {
      "question": "死に神",
      "answer": "しにがみ",
      "meaning": "god of death, death deity, Death"
    },
    {
      "question": "閑職",
      "answer": "かんしょく",
      "meaning": "leisurely post, do-nothing job, sinecure"
    },
    {
      "question": "満足度",
      "answer": "まんぞくど",
      "meaning": "(degree of) satisfaction"
    },
    {
      "question": "祭礼",
      "answer": "さいれい",
      "meaning": "(religious) festival"
    },
    {
      "question": "勲",
      "answer": "いさお,くん",
      "meaning": "distinguished service, meritorious service, merit (esp. order of merit)"
    },
    {
      "question": "闇鍋",
      "answer": "やみなべ",
      "meaning": "stew prepared from ingredients contributed by members of a party, and eaten in the dark for fun"
    },
    {
      "question": "麻婆豆腐",
      "answer": "マーボーどうふ,マーボどうふ",
      "meaning": "mapo doufu, mapo tofu, spicy Sichuan dish of tofu and minced meat"
    },
    {
      "question": "一局",
      "answer": "いっきょく",
      "meaning": "one game (checkers, etc.)"
    },
    {
      "question": "退る",
      "answer": "しさる,しざる",
      "meaning": "to step back, to walk backwards"
    },
    {
      "question": "摑み取る",
      "answer": "つかみとる",
      "meaning": "to grasp, to get"
    },
    {
      "question": "在野",
      "answer": "ざいや",
      "meaning": "out of office, out of power, in opposition, unaffiliated (e.g. researcher, scientist), in private pr"
    },
    {
      "question": "中小企業",
      "answer": "ちゅうしょうきぎょう",
      "meaning": "small and medium-sized enterprises, small and medium-sized businesses"
    },
    {
      "question": "八万",
      "answer": "はちまん,やよろず",
      "meaning": "80000, many"
    },
    {
      "question": "除籍",
      "answer": "じょせき",
      "meaning": "removing a name, expelling (e.g. from school), decommissioning"
    },
    {
      "question": "玉葱",
      "answer": "たまねぎ",
      "meaning": "onion (Allium cepa)"
    },
    {
      "question": "小首",
      "answer": "こくび",
      "meaning": "head"
    },
    {
      "question": "先駆者",
      "answer": "せんくしゃ",
      "meaning": "pioneer, trailblazer, leader, groundbreaker, pathfinder, forerunner"
    },
    {
      "question": "要項",
      "answer": "ようこう",
      "meaning": "important points, main points"
    },
    {
      "question": "何奴",
      "answer": "どいつ,どちつ,どやつ",
      "meaning": "who?"
    },
    {
      "question": "横隔膜",
      "answer": "おうかくまく",
      "meaning": "diaphragm"
    },
    {
      "question": "運転免許",
      "answer": "うんてんめんきょ",
      "meaning": "driver's license, driver's licence"
    },
    {
      "question": "耳寄り",
      "answer": "みみより",
      "meaning": "welcome (news), inviting, encouraging, tempting, hopeful"
    },
    {
      "question": "売り文句",
      "answer": "うりもんく",
      "meaning": "sales pitch, sales lure, catchphrase"
    },
    {
      "question": "散在",
      "answer": "さんざい",
      "meaning": "to be scattered, to straggle, to be found here and there"
    },
    {
      "question": "言付かる",
      "answer": "いいつかる,ことづかる",
      "meaning": "to be ordered (to do), to be entrusted with, to be asked to"
    },
    {
      "question": "気密",
      "answer": "きみつ",
      "meaning": "airtight"
    },
    {
      "question": "何れ",
      "answer": "どれ,いずれ,いづれ",
      "meaning": "which (of three or more), well, now, c'mon, where, which, who, anyway, anyhow, at any rate, sooner o"
    },
    {
      "question": "牝",
      "answer": "めす,めん,め",
      "meaning": "female (animal, plant), female, smaller (of the two), weaker, woman, wife"
    },
    {
      "question": "彫刻刀",
      "answer": "ちょうこくとう",
      "meaning": "graver, chisel"
    },
    {
      "question": "回診",
      "answer": "かいしん",
      "meaning": "doctor's hospital rounds"
    },
    {
      "question": "乗馬服",
      "answer": "じょうばふく",
      "meaning": "riding habit"
    },
    {
      "question": "写生",
      "answer": "しゃせい",
      "meaning": "sketching, drawing from nature, portrayal, description"
    },
    {
      "question": "画集",
      "answer": "がしゅう",
      "meaning": "book of pictures (paintings, drawings, etc.), collection of pictures"
    },
    {
      "question": "口蓋",
      "answer": "こうがい",
      "meaning": "palate"
    },
    {
      "question": "財界",
      "answer": "ざいかい",
      "meaning": "financial world, business circles"
    },
    {
      "question": "咽び泣く",
      "answer": "むせびなく",
      "meaning": "to sob, to be choked with tears"
    },
    {
      "question": "同額",
      "answer": "どうがく",
      "meaning": "the same amount"
    },
    {
      "question": "減額",
      "answer": "げんがく",
      "meaning": "reduction, diminution, abatement"
    },
    {
      "question": "職人気質",
      "answer": "しょくにんかたぎ,しょくにんきしつ",
      "meaning": "spirit of a true artisan, (a craftsman's) pride in one's work"
    },
    {
      "question": "楢",
      "answer": "なら",
      "meaning": "oak (esp. Quercus serrata)"
    },
    {
      "question": "双翼",
      "answer": "そうよく",
      "meaning": "both wings"
    },
    {
      "question": "有翼",
      "answer": "ゆうよく",
      "meaning": "winged"
    },
    {
      "question": "合一",
      "answer": "ごういつ",
      "meaning": "unification, union, oneness"
    },
    {
      "question": "摂政",
      "answer": "せっしょう,せっせい",
      "meaning": "regency, regent, advisor (to the Ryukyuan King)"
    },
    {
      "question": "夜番",
      "answer": "やばん,よばん",
      "meaning": "night watch, night sentry"
    },
    {
      "question": "蒼天",
      "answer": "そうてん",
      "meaning": "blue sky, azure sky, spring sky"
    },
    {
      "question": "推敲",
      "answer": "すいこう",
      "meaning": "polishing (e.g. essay), revision, elaboration, refinement, improvement"
    },
    {
      "question": "日当",
      "answer": "にっとう,ひあたり",
      "meaning": "daily allowance, daily wages, exposure to the sun, sunny place, per day"
    },
    {
      "question": "好悪",
      "answer": "こうお",
      "meaning": "likes and dislikes"
    },
    {
      "question": "道化る",
      "answer": "どうける",
      "meaning": "to jest, to clown (around)"
    },
    {
      "question": "名誉職",
      "answer": "めいよしょく",
      "meaning": "honorary position"
    },
    {
      "question": "刑法",
      "answer": "けいほう",
      "meaning": "criminal law, penal code"
    },
    {
      "question": "艱難辛苦",
      "answer": "かんなんしんく",
      "meaning": "trial and tribulation, hardships, privations, difficulties"
    },
    {
      "question": "外向き",
      "answer": "そとむき",
      "meaning": "facing outward"
    },
    {
      "question": "又聞き",
      "answer": "またぎき",
      "meaning": "hearsay, learning by hearsay"
    },
    {
      "question": "山積",
      "answer": "さんせき",
      "meaning": "piling up, accumulating, forming a (huge) pile, lying in piles"
    },
    {
      "question": "弔い合戦",
      "answer": "とむらいがっせん",
      "meaning": "battle of revenge"
    },
    {
      "question": "貧する",
      "answer": "ひんする",
      "meaning": "to become poor, to be poor"
    },
    {
      "question": "巻き返し",
      "answer": "まきかえし",
      "meaning": "rally, recovery, rollback, rewind"
    },
    {
      "question": "塗り直す",
      "answer": "ぬりなおす",
      "meaning": "to repaint, to paint again"
    },
    {
      "question": "臨検",
      "answer": "りんけん",
      "meaning": "on-the-spot investigation or inspection, raid"
    },
    {
      "question": "防衛省",
      "answer": "ぼうえいしょう",
      "meaning": "Ministry of Defense"
    },
    {
      "question": "制式",
      "answer": "せいしき",
      "meaning": "defined style, predetermined style, official style, rule"
    },
    {
      "question": "気の所為",
      "answer": "きのせい",
      "meaning": "in one's imagination"
    },
    {
      "question": "苑",
      "answer": "その,えん",
      "meaning": "garden (esp. man-made), orchard, park, plantation, place, location"
    },
    {
      "question": "榛",
      "answer": "はしばみ,はり,はぎ",
      "meaning": "Asian hazel (Corylus heterophylla var. thunbergii), Siberian hazel, Japanese alder (Alnus japonica)"
    },
    {
      "question": "千枚",
      "answer": "せんまい",
      "meaning": "1000 sheets (of paper), many pages, book tripe, bible tripe, leaf tripe, beef omasum, cow omasum, co"
    },
    {
      "question": "喚声",
      "answer": "かんせい",
      "meaning": "shout"
    },
    {
      "question": "戒厳令",
      "answer": "かいげんれい",
      "meaning": "martial law"
    },
    {
      "question": "瞬発",
      "answer": "しゅんぱつ",
      "meaning": "instantaneous"
    },
    {
      "question": "病原体",
      "answer": "びょうげんたい",
      "meaning": "pathogen"
    },
    {
      "question": "引越す",
      "answer": "ひきこす",
      "meaning": "to move (house), to change residence"
    },
    {
      "question": "俯す",
      "answer": "うつぶす,ふす",
      "meaning": "to lie face down (e.g. on the ground, napping on a desk), to lie prone, to lower (one's head, gaze,"
    },
    {
      "question": "開脚",
      "answer": "かいきゃく",
      "meaning": "spreading the legs (wide apart), opening the legs"
    },
    {
      "question": "長雨",
      "answer": "ながあめ,ながめ",
      "meaning": "long spell of rain"
    },
    {
      "question": "単純化",
      "answer": "たんじゅんか",
      "meaning": "simplification"
    },
    {
      "question": "雌伏",
      "answer": "しふく",
      "meaning": "remaining in obscurity"
    },
    {
      "question": "俗説",
      "answer": "ぞくせつ",
      "meaning": "common saying, popular version, folklore, tradition"
    },
    {
      "question": "浮気性",
      "answer": "うわきしょう",
      "meaning": "prone to adultery, flirtatious"
    },
    {
      "question": "独り歩き",
      "answer": "ひとりあるき",
      "meaning": "taking on a life of its own (of a rumour, etc.), walking by oneself, talking a walk by oneself, walk"
    },
    {
      "question": "執政官",
      "answer": "しっせいかん",
      "meaning": "consul"
    }
  ]
}
